[
    {
        "question": "In an international tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            0,
            3,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A family is going on a vacation to Chicago in a bus. There were 6 men, 6 women, 8 children of less than 10 years, 8 old people of age above 60 years.How many of the people can drive??",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            118,
            28,
            0,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 16 years old in the year 1880.In his greatest win, he looted 483626438 of 9144657538 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1873,
            1889,
            1881,
            1864
        ],
        "answer": 1864
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $7 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-tenth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 40.6 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            363.4,
            442,
            408,
            446
        ],
        "answer": 363.4
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 59 miles in 8 hours and 36 minutes?",
        "options": [
            7.806696366467952,
            0.11434108527131782,
            3.646687409296502,
            6.019138819608108
        ],
        "answer": 0.11434108527131782
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            20,
            14,
            6,
            -20
        ],
        "answer": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Ice Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 4 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            12,
            3,
            2,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 7 years old in the year 1793.In his greatest win, he looted 635831301 of 5627961530 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins were actually present in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            635831301,
            -4992130229,
            5627961530,
            6263792831
        ],
        "answer": 5627961530
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 6 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            3,
            -24,
            24,
            21
        ],
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -25,
            23,
            2,
            25
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 7 feet by 5 feet?",
        "options": [
            7292,
            5331,
            5040,
            8931
        ],
        "answer": 5040
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            4,
            28,
            24,
            -28
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 34 miles in 10 hours and 23 minutes?",
        "options": [
            7.227508453461705,
            8.498445317550267,
            9.243583500393413,
            3.274478330658106
        ],
        "answer": 3.274478330658106
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Ice Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 4 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            3,
            1,
            12,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 46 ohms and 16 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 3 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            46,
            3,
            62,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Angel wants to buy a pair of pants. If his waist size is 32cm, what available pair of pants may fit him?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            32,
            10,
            15,
            43
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If dog can eat 16 apples , how many apples can a man eat?",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            16,
            18,
            34,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 78. When the sun is at 87 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            86,
            102,
            79,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 fan, 31 tubelight, 34 pair of shoes, 3 cockroaches, and 1 bed bugs? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            46,
            4,
            37,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international cricket game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 10 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            5,
            0,
            14,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            21,
            -21,
            19,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 21
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 4 couch, 3 broom, 73 bed, 1 plants, and 13 cat? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            33,
            87,
            82
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            19,
            9,
            10,
            -19
        ],
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Boxing game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            0,
            2,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Vivaan wants to buy a pair of shoes. If his foot size is 8cm, what available pair of shoes may fit him?",
        "answer": 21,
        "options": [
            21,
            20,
            4,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hernandez wants to put a luggage in a car trunk.The car trunk is 8.139 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the luggage?",
        "answer": 2.6,
        "options": [
            8.139,
            2.7,
            26.0,
            2.6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $2 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-eighth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 5.9 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            404,
            41.2,
            113,
            437
        ],
        "answer": 41.2
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $8 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-tenth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 11.2 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            289,
            99.8,
            329,
            127
        ],
        "answer": 99.8
    },
    {
        "question": "White wants to buy a Hand glove. If his Palm-size is 38cm, what available Hand glove may fit him?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            43,
            26,
            33,
            29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 62000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 543000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            150,
            114.18,
            196,
            611
        ],
        "answer": 114.18
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            21,
            -21,
            19,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 21
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 fan, 14 tubelight, 29 broom, 13 cat, and 14 pigeons? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            35,
            14,
            30,
            43
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 11 years old in the year 1243.In his greatest win, he looted 496052587 of 5389166212 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins were actually present in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            5389166212,
            5885218799,
            496052587,
            -4893113625
        ],
        "answer": 5389166212
    },
    {
        "question": "Darsh wants to buy a necklace. If his neck circumference is 21cm, what available necklace may fit him?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            23,
            28,
            21,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Snyder wants to buy a a ring. If his finger circumference is 13cm, what available a ring may fit him?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            41,
            26,
            42,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 22. When the sun is at 154 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 94,
        "options": [
            94,
            8,
            8,
            21
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $2 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-eighth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 46.1 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            362.8,
            365,
            391,
            465
        ],
        "answer": 362.8
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kph if you travel 65 miles in 10 hours and 53 minutes?",
        "options": [
            2.238026665166244,
            3.910984270442626,
            7.511085599521532,
            9.555895865237366
        ],
        "answer": 9.555895865237366
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 19 years old in the year 1845.In his greatest win, he looted 80869601 of 2030792196 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins are remaining in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            2111661797,
            2030792196,
            1949922595,
            80869601
        ],
        "answer": 1949922595
    },
    {
        "question": "Nguyen wants to put a house in a street.The street is 8.061 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the house?",
        "answer": 5.73,
        "options": [
            5.73,
            5.83,
            57.300000000000004,
            8.061
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of Ryan increased from 789 per month to 924 per month while the salary of Jimenez increased from 503 to 962 and of Ananya increased from 961 to 977 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Ananya",
        "options": [
            "Ryan",
            "Jimenez",
            "Ananya",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 6 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            7,
            -17,
            10,
            17
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 10 years old in the year 1796.In his greatest win, he looted 126588341 of 2072840991 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1810,
            1848,
            1786,
            1819
        ],
        "answer": 1786
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            11,
            -29,
            29,
            18
        ],
        "answer": 29
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 39 miles in 4 hours and 13 minutes?",
        "options": [
            9.24901185770751,
            5.132563207333196,
            6.663443324517848,
            7.618911779099713
        ],
        "answer": 9.24901185770751
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            1,
            2,
            0,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 53. When the sun is at 59 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 47,
        "options": [
            73,
            53,
            47,
            94
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 20 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -30,
            11,
            30,
            19
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 8 years old in the year 1655.In his greatest win, he looted 13536377 of 1964703136 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins were actually present in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            -1951166759,
            13536377,
            1978239513,
            1964703136
        ],
        "answer": 1964703136
    },
    {
        "question": "Nguyen wants to buy a Belt. If his waist size is 24cm, what available Belt may fit him?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            43,
            28,
            41,
            38
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 sofa, 16 bed, 93 pair of shoes, 9 algae spots, and 10 dog? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 19,
        "options": [
            21,
            102,
            19,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Friday and returns to the bank 12years later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Wednesday",
        "options": [
            "Wednesday",
            "Thursday",
            "Thursday",
            "Monday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            18,
            -26,
            8,
            26
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "Woods wants to buy a hat. If his head circumference is 40cm, what available hat may fit him?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            43,
            36,
            44,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 23 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            15,
            -15,
            4,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "question": "Butler began counting from 0. She skip-counted by tens. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 560,
        "options": [
            561,
            0,
            562,
            560
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 7 fan, 3 cycles, 49 flower vase, 12 cat, and 4 human beings? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            17,
            61,
            10,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Fox wants to buy a hat. If his head circumference is 30cm, what available hat may fit him?",
        "answer": 35,
        "options": [
            35,
            32,
            33,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 broom, 5 empty boxes, 53 table, 13 bed bugs, and 1 trees? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            15,
            6,
            66,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If pigeon can eat 8 chocolates , how many chocolates can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 27,
        "options": [
            8,
            27,
            35,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Fox wants to put a Table in a Room.The Room is 6.481 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Table?",
        "answer": 3.55,
        "options": [
            6.481,
            35.5,
            3.65,
            3.55
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 flower vase, 14 chair, 32 cycles, 14 pigeons, and 14 bed bugs? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 64,
        "options": [
            100,
            109,
            64,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international baseball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 3 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            5,
            5,
            14,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Robinson earns $7 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $3 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Robinson was paid $4270, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            278,
            457,
            180,
            148
        ],
        "answer": 457
    },
    {
        "question": "If giraffee can eat 18 watermelon , how many watermelon can a dog eat?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            18,
            9,
            27,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 19000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 501000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            0.038,
            616,
            126,
            17
        ],
        "answer": 0.038
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 42 ohms and 18 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 20 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 21,
        "options": [
            756,
            41,
            18,
            60,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 6 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            3,
            -24,
            24,
            21
        ],
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "Boyd wants to buy a pair of shorts. If his waist size is 7cm, what available pair of shorts may fit him?",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            8,
            5,
            6,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 couch, 15 flower vase, 55 refrigerator, 2 trees, and 13 bed bugs? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 61,
        "options": [
            95,
            97,
            61,
            93
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            0,
            3,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 23 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -27,
            23,
            4,
            27
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "Anaya began counting from 0. She skip-counted by tens. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 810,
        "options": [
            811,
            810,
            812,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 75000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 908000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            511,
            407,
            201,
            82.599
        ],
        "answer": 82.599
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 79 miles in 9 hours and 49 minutes?",
        "options": [
            2.9863505767730776,
            9.918203496467807,
            8.047538200339558,
            9.170518815442108
        ],
        "answer": 8.047538200339558
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 sofa, 16 bed, 93 pair of shoes, 9 algae spots, and 10 dog? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 19,
        "options": [
            111,
            127,
            47,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Dhruv began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fives. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 285,
        "options": [
            286,
            0,
            285,
            287
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 16 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            21,
            22,
            -22,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 22
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 flower vase, 86 chair, 59 empty boxes, 13 human beings, and 3 trees? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 84,
        "options": [
            389,
            204,
            84,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Brooks began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fives. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 215,
        "options": [
            215,
            217,
            0,
            216
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 4 feet by 6 feet?",
        "options": [
            3456,
            9480,
            6087,
            4479
        ],
        "answer": 3456
    },
    {
        "question": "Aaryan began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fives. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 350,
        "options": [
            0,
            352,
            351,
            350
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $5 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-fifth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 49.4 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            489,
            361,
            198.6,
            306
        ],
        "answer": 198.6
    },
    {
        "question": "If dog can eat 24 chocolates , how many chocolates can a pigeon eat?",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            24,
            12,
            36,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 5 feet by 6 feet?",
        "options": [
            5820,
            3539,
            4320,
            719
        ],
        "answer": 4320
    },
    {
        "question": "Washington wants to put a car in a road.The road is 10.0 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the car?",
        "answer": 4.29,
        "options": [
            4.29,
            42.9,
            10.0,
            4.39
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international golf game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            0,
            2,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 sofa, 33 empty boxes, 13 bed, 2 bed bugs, and 15 fungi spots? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 48,
        "options": [
            68,
            58,
            48,
            68
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 16 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            21,
            22,
            -22,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 22
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $2 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional quarter mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 16.1 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            275,
            107,
            62.4,
            154
        ],
        "answer": 62.4
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 6 years old in the year 1876.In his greatest win, he looted 179891474 of 3709546021 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1879,
            1872,
            1870,
            1899
        ],
        "answer": 1870
    },
    {
        "question": "If snail can eat 78 grapes , how many grapes can a ants eat?",
        "answer": 50,
        "options": [
            78,
            50,
            128,
            28
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A family is going on a vacation to Chicago in a bus. There were 10 men, 8 women, 6 children of less than 10 years, 5 old people of age above 60 years.How many of the people can drive??",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            103,
            29,
            0,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Parker began counting from 0. She skip-counted by twos. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 146,
        "options": [
            146,
            147,
            0,
            148
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 15 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -26,
            19,
            7,
            26
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "If man can eat 24 chocolates , how many chocolates can a pigeon eat?",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            24,
            14,
            38,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 26 ohms and 20 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 25 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 26,
        "options": [
            51,
            520,
            46,
            20,
            25
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If pigeon can eat 3 cake , how many cake can a elephant eat?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            3,
            9,
            12,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 10000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 875000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            626,
            18,
            352,
            11.429
        ],
        "answer": 11.429
    },
    {
        "question": "If a child can eat 15 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a snail eat?",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            15,
            12,
            27,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $66 to the charity and a total of $16492 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was quadrupled?",
        "options": [
            56,
            997,
            249,
            450
        ],
        "answer": 249
    },
    {
        "question": "Hamilton wants to put a Car in a Garage.The Garage is 9.261 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Car?",
        "answer": 3.02,
        "options": [
            3.12,
            9.261,
            3.02,
            30.2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 2 flower vase, 85 table, 85 pair of shoes, 3 cat, and 9 crows? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 155,
        "options": [
            347,
            337,
            155,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -25,
            23,
            2,
            25
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "Wells wants to buy a pair of shorts. If his waist size is 21cm, what available pair of shorts may fit him?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            37,
            28,
            29,
            27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 19 years old in the year 1330.In his greatest win, he looted 225300950 of 5509053344 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins are remaining in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            225300950,
            5734354294,
            5283752394,
            5509053344
        ],
        "answer": 5283752394
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $2 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-eighth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 47.9 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            458,
            420,
            492,
            377.2
        ],
        "answer": 377.2
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 couch, 74 cycles, 90 empty boxes, 5 bed bugs, and 14 snail? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 152,
        "options": [
            152,
            175,
            174,
            177
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            15,
            -26,
            26,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 24 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            17,
            23,
            6,
            -23
        ],
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "Mills wants to buy a pair of socks. If his foot size is 7cm, what available pair of socks may fit him?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            6,
            5,
            4,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Prisha wants to buy a Belt. If his waist size is 28cm, what available Belt may fit him?",
        "answer": 34,
        "options": [
            17,
            29,
            34,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 32 ohms and 29 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 8 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            928,
            8,
            61,
            0,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kph if you travel 30 miles in 9 hours and 26 minutes?",
        "options": [
            5.088339222614842,
            7.060452899765174,
            4.085248143002212,
            3.0490926436111008
        ],
        "answer": 5.088339222614842
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 40 ohms and 39 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 2 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            39,
            2,
            40,
            79
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international footbal game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 7 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            7,
            8,
            4,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international golf game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            -1,
            0,
            0,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A family is going on a vacation to Chicago in a bus. There were 6 men, 6 women, 9 children of less than 10 years, 8 old people of age above 60 years.How many of the people can drive??",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            107,
            29,
            0,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 5 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            14,
            4,
            10,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 7 feet by 8 feet?",
        "options": [
            8064,
            4301,
            7518,
            6170
        ],
        "answer": 8064
    },
    {
        "question": "If cow can eat 6 cake , how many cake can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            6,
            3,
            9,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 49 ohms and 27 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 9 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            27,
            9,
            1323,
            76,
            29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of Arnold increased from 730 per month to 770 per month while the salary of Graham increased from 933 to 990 and of Graham increased from 631 to 749 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Graham",
        "options": [
            "Arnold",
            "Graham",
            "Graham",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 90 miles in 6 hours and 46 minutes?",
        "options": [
            7.398567436554936,
            6.431476063340163,
            8.528621749821792,
            0.35467980295566504
        ],
        "answer": 0.35467980295566504
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -25,
            23,
            2,
            25
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "If cat can eat 29 lemons , how many lemons can a ants eat?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            29,
            16,
            45,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 6 feet by 5 feet?",
        "options": [
            4320,
            9255,
            6660,
            779
        ],
        "answer": 4320
    },
    {
        "question": "Vasquez wants to buy a necklace. If his neck circumference is 16cm, what available necklace may fit him?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            26,
            5,
            28,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 16 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            21,
            22,
            -22,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 22
    },
    {
        "question": "If pigeon can eat 5 cake , how many cake can a giraffee eat?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            5,
            9,
            14,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -25,
            23,
            2,
            25
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 flower vase, 42 empty boxes, 68 bed, 12 pigeons, and 15 cockroaches? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 118,
        "options": [
            80,
            118,
            50,
            119
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A family is going on a vacation to Chicago in a bus. There were 5 men, 10 women, 6 children of less than 10 years, 2 old people of age above 60 years.How many of the people can drive??",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            105,
            23,
            0,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international volley ball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 5 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            5,
            4,
            0,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            11,
            -29,
            29,
            18
        ],
        "answer": 29
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Badminton game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            1,
            4,
            2,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 4 broom, 73 cycles, 61 mat, 14 bed bugs, and 9 cat? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 19,
        "options": [
            149,
            152,
            19,
            147
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 empty boxes, 20 bed, 15 refrigerator, 8 dog, and 7 pigeons? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            23,
            16,
            34,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Stewart wants to put a book in a bag.The bag is 5.092 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the book?",
        "answer": 1.44,
        "options": [
            1.44,
            14.399999999999999,
            5.092,
            1.54
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 16 years old in the year 1298.In his greatest win, he looted 722469330 of 1633282191 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins are remaining in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            2355751521,
            722469330,
            910812861,
            1633282191
        ],
        "answer": 910812861
    },
    {
        "question": "Robinson wants to put a Drawer in a Table.The Table is 3.277 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Drawer?",
        "answer": 2.27,
        "options": [
            22.7,
            2.27,
            2.37,
            3.277
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 fan, 31 tubelight, 34 pair of shoes, 3 cockroaches, and 1 bed bugs? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            4,
            53,
            5,
            72
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 18 ohms and 31 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 25 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            49,
            558,
            25,
            53,
            31
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 80 miles in 9 hours and 40 minutes?",
        "options": [
            0.2206896551724138,
            4.785887112981329,
            7.4981758165383745,
            1.2937098208296542
        ],
        "answer": 0.2206896551724138
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international cricket game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 6 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            22,
            5,
            0,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 15 ohms and 23 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 24 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 30,
        "options": [
            23,
            54,
            345,
            38,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $66 to the charity and a total of $14610 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was tripled?",
        "options": [
            248,
            478,
            810,
            221
        ],
        "answer": 221
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 37 ohms and 11 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 3 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            0,
            48,
            3,
            7,
            407
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            20,
            -30,
            30,
            10
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 16 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            16,
            6,
            10,
            -16
        ],
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 mat, 26 cycles, 66 fan, 11 bed bugs, and 12 algae spots? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 21,
        "options": [
            64,
            48,
            21,
            72
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 bed, 4 couch, 91 tubelight, 13 people, and 3 snail? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            186,
            42,
            0,
            363
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ruiz wants to buy a Belt. If his waist size is 29cm, what available Belt may fit him?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            13,
            6,
            23,
            39
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 18 ohms and 46 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 8 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            8,
            46,
            828,
            31,
            64
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 73000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 413000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            168,
            176.755,
            368,
            204
        ],
        "answer": 176.755
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 6 flower vase, 42 tubelight, 6 refrigerator, 2 dog, and 12 plants? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 54,
        "options": [
            8,
            55,
            48,
            54
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international cricket game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 3 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            21,
            3,
            10,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 19 years old in the year 1365.In his greatest win, he looted 477038510 of 8327276334 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins were actually present in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            8804314844,
            477038510,
            8327276334,
            -7850237824
        ],
        "answer": 8327276334
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 tubelight, 57 fan, 67 broom, 5 snail, and 4 bed bugs? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 129,
        "options": [
            130,
            72,
            62,
            129
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Henry began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fives. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 175,
        "options": [
            177,
            0,
            175,
            176
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 32. When the sun is at 100 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            87,
            109,
            22,
            33
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A family is going on a vacation to Chicago in a bus. There were 6 men, 7 women, 10 children of less than 10 years, 3 old people of age above 60 years.How many of the people can drive??",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            109,
            26,
            0,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 bed, 11 cycles, 61 empty boxes, 6 crows, and 11 pigeons? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            18,
            24,
            67,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Brown wants to buy a shirt. If his body size is 10cm, what available shirt may fit him?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            11,
            16,
            22,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 44 miles in 1 hours and 60 minutes?",
        "options": [
            4.911423630713126,
            6.206291834627034,
            8.757335664990215,
            22.0
        ],
        "answer": 22.0
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 11 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            8,
            1,
            -9,
            9
        ],
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 mat, 26 cycles, 66 fan, 11 bed bugs, and 12 algae spots? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            195,
            161,
            0,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Allen wants to buy a Hand glove. If his Palm-size is 12cm, what available Hand glove may fit him?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            38,
            9,
            2,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 18000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 427000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            705,
            42.155,
            953,
            990
        ],
        "answer": 42.155
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 74. When the sun is at 23 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 97,
        "options": [
            25,
            34,
            97,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Aarohi wants to buy a Belt. If his waist size is 36cm, what available Belt may fit him?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            8,
            7,
            30,
            39
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 76 miles in 8 hours and 20 minutes?",
        "options": [
            4.29867984438259,
            9.342483766283618,
            1.7034609450196188,
            9.12
        ],
        "answer": 9.12
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 couch, 66 flower vase, 15 cycles, 14 cat, and 15 dog? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 96,
        "options": [
            29,
            97,
            81,
            96
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 3 couch, 77 flower vase, 90 empty boxes, 2 bed bugs, and 15 cat? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            16,
            149,
            156,
            22
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ryan earns $15 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $5 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Ryan was paid $3991, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            377,
            419,
            62,
            224
        ],
        "answer": 224
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 5 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            6,
            18,
            2,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $3 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-third mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 24.2 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            437,
            246,
            72.6,
            470
        ],
        "answer": 72.6
    },
    {
        "question": "Perry wants to buy a cap. If his head circumference is 31cm, what available cap may fit him?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            6,
            41,
            19,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 7 flower vase, 39 cycles, 36 tubelight, 10 cockroaches, and 10 human beings? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            16,
            100,
            65,
            69
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Gomez wants to put a house in a street.The street is 7.909 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the house?",
        "answer": 4.17,
        "options": [
            7.909,
            4.27,
            41.7,
            4.17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $9 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-fifth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 13.6 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            349,
            472,
            59.4,
            360
        ],
        "answer": 59.4
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 17 years old in the year 1519.In his greatest win, he looted 900951520 of 4127340844 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1502,
            1703,
            1603,
            1861
        ],
        "answer": 1502
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $82 to the charity and a total of $13928 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was quadrupled?",
        "options": [
            540,
            755,
            594,
            169
        ],
        "answer": 169
    },
    {
        "question": "Anaya wants to put a Car in a Garage.The Garage is 4.516 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Car?",
        "answer": 3.37,
        "options": [
            33.7,
            4.516,
            3.47,
            3.37
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of Hughes increased from 432 per month to 815 per month while the salary of Palmer increased from 450 to 967 and of Coleman increased from 433 to 720 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Coleman",
        "options": [
            "Hughes",
            "Palmer",
            "Coleman",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 refrigerator, 23 empty boxes, 83 couch, 7 cat, and 9 algae spots? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            76,
            2,
            58,
            69
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 17 years old in the year 1320.In his greatest win, he looted 169198821 of 1356931224 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1303,
            1545,
            1875,
            1813
        ],
        "answer": 1303
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of Reyansh increased from 550 per month to 967 per month while the salary of Ahana increased from 451 to 662 and of Cooper increased from 593 to 937 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Cooper",
        "options": [
            "Reyansh",
            "Ahana",
            "Cooper",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $28 to the charity and a total of $15292 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was quadrupled?",
        "options": [
            437,
            635,
            850,
            546
        ],
        "answer": 546
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $22 to the charity and a total of $18880 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was quadrupled?",
        "options": [
            927,
            680,
            122,
            858
        ],
        "answer": 858
    },
    {
        "question": "Arnold wants to put a fruit in a basket.The basket is 4.268 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the fruit?",
        "answer": 2.52,
        "options": [
            2.52,
            25.2,
            4.268,
            2.62
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            3,
            1,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 refrigerator, 47 empty boxes, 12 bed, 2 cat, and 5 bed bugs? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            69,
            74,
            69,
            28
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $88 to the charity and a total of $4690 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was doubled?",
        "options": [
            53,
            990,
            711,
            402
        ],
        "answer": 53
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 24 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            13,
            -17,
            17,
            4
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 11 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            8,
            1,
            -9,
            9
        ],
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $5 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-third mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 46.4 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            141.2,
            436,
            237,
            309
        ],
        "answer": 141.2
    },
    {
        "question": "Perez began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fours. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 272,
        "options": [
            274,
            273,
            272,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Ice Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            3,
            4,
            4,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 mat, 26 cycles, 66 fan, 11 bed bugs, and 12 algae spots? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            49,
            39,
            91
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            19,
            9,
            10,
            -19
        ],
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 couch, 74 cycles, 90 empty boxes, 5 bed bugs, and 14 snail? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 172,
        "options": [
            173,
            172,
            95,
            82
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 20 ohms and 48 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 15 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            15,
            68,
            37,
            48,
            960
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 flower vase, 42 empty boxes, 68 bed, 12 pigeons, and 15 cockroaches? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 27,
        "options": [
            28,
            50,
            27,
            80
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If elephant can eat 98 grapes , how many grapes can a dog eat?",
        "answer": 54,
        "options": [
            98,
            54,
            152,
            44
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $2 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-tenth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 30.5 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            282,
            284,
            267.5,
            305
        ],
        "answer": 267.5
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $3 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-third mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 29.1 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            87.3,
            277,
            192,
            287
        ],
        "answer": 87.3
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 sofa, 82 tubelight, 76 mat, 7 plants, and 6 bed bugs? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 86,
        "options": [
            178,
            174,
            170,
            86
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Iraa wants to put a phone in a pocket.The pocket is 9.447 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the phone?",
        "answer": 3.28,
        "options": [
            9.447,
            3.38,
            32.8,
            3.28
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international footbal game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 3 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            21,
            9,
            10,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 20 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -30,
            11,
            30,
            19
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 empty boxes, 9 couch, 71 sofa, 12 algae spots, and 2 plants? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            83,
            23,
            15,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If dog can eat 27 apples , how many apples can a snail eat?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            27,
            22,
            49,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $6 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-eighth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 9.3 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            148,
            489,
            72.4,
            413
        ],
        "answer": 72.4
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $4 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-eighth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 15.2 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            314,
            117.6,
            283,
            291
        ],
        "answer": 117.6
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Table-Tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            4,
            1,
            1,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Carter wants to buy a hoodie. If his chest size is 38cm, what available hoodie may fit him?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            38,
            30,
            39,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 3 bed, 59 flower vase, 12 refrigerator, 4 trees, and 14 human beings? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 48,
        "options": [
            48,
            180,
            0,
            100
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $10 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-fifth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 7.5 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            164,
            239,
            36.0,
            74
        ],
        "answer": 36.0
    },
    {
        "question": "If giraffee can eat 28 lemons , how many lemons can a snail eat?",
        "answer": 13,
        "options": [
            28,
            13,
            41,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international baseball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 7 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            4,
            0,
            10,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 15 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -26,
            19,
            7,
            26
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 63000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 473000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            535,
            23,
            133.192,
            586
        ],
        "answer": 133.192
    },
    {
        "question": "Reed wants to buy a Hand glove. If his Palm-size is 35cm, what available Hand glove may fit him?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            12,
            12,
            37,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 19 years old in the year 1700.In his greatest win, he looted 840833899 of 8299477129 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins are remaining in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            9140311028,
            840833899,
            8299477129,
            7458643230
        ],
        "answer": 7458643230
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 flower vase, 46 refrigerator, 87 couch, 2 snail, and 14 bed bugs? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            54,
            16,
            17,
            89
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $68 to the charity and a total of $9594 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was doubled?",
        "options": [
            70,
            429,
            141,
            273
        ],
        "answer": 141
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $10 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-sixth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 25.0 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            262,
            154.0,
            228,
            387
        ],
        "answer": 154.0
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 11 years old in the year 1329.In his greatest win, he looted 570410466 of 1547295181 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1370,
            1603,
            1318,
            1741
        ],
        "answer": 1318
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 54 gallons. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 3/10 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            48,
            17,
            91,
            16.2
        ],
        "answer": 16.2
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 7 fan, 3 cycles, 49 flower vase, 12 cat, and 4 human beings? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 59,
        "options": [
            60,
            61,
            10,
            59
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kph if you travel 45 miles in 2 hours and 55 minutes?",
        "options": [
            24.685714285714287,
            3.010888419089358,
            3.89592333356367,
            6.370611451136118
        ],
        "answer": 24.685714285714287
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 12 fan, 97 tubelight, 86 empty boxes, 6 cat, and 10 trees? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 195,
        "options": [
            92,
            196,
            195,
            109
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Diya wants to put a chocolate in a jar.The jar is 4.07 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the chocolate?",
        "answer": 1.05,
        "options": [
            1.1500000000000001,
            10.5,
            1.05,
            4.07
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Graham wants to put a picture in a frame.The frame is 4.974 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the picture?",
        "answer": 3.81,
        "options": [
            3.91,
            38.1,
            3.81,
            4.974
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Freeman wants to buy a Belt. If his waist size is 22cm, what available Belt may fit him?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            38,
            42,
            23,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international footbal game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 9 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            2,
            3,
            4,
            21
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 24 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            17,
            23,
            6,
            -23
        ],
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 flower vase, 14 chair, 32 cycles, 14 pigeons, and 14 bed bugs? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 57,
        "options": [
            58,
            57,
            46,
            25
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Vivaan wants to buy a Hand glove. If his Palm-size is 23cm, what available Hand glove may fit him?",
        "answer": 26,
        "options": [
            6,
            26,
            22,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 27 ohms and 17 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 2 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            44,
            17,
            27,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Advik wants to buy a hoodie. If his chest size is 15cm, what available hoodie may fit him?",
        "answer": 19,
        "options": [
            16,
            13,
            19,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If giraffee can eat 153 grapes , how many grapes can a man eat?",
        "answer": 90,
        "options": [
            153,
            90,
            243,
            63
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 89 miles in 8 hours and 23 minutes?",
        "options": [
            9.272732903928398,
            0.2831013916500994,
            5.996689928951474,
            7.471044593161938
        ],
        "answer": 0.2831013916500994
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $5 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional quarter mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 24.5 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            229,
            488,
            147,
            99.0
        ],
        "answer": 99.0
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international basketball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 3 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            5,
            4,
            6,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Monday and returns to the bank 9years later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Wednesday",
        "options": [
            "Friday",
            "Thursday",
            "Wednesday",
            "tuesday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Table-Tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            -1,
            4,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 18 years old in the year 1142.In his greatest win, he looted 614451906 of 3381704035 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1396,
            1561,
            1804,
            1124
        ],
        "answer": 1124
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 refrigerator, 47 empty boxes, 12 bed, 2 cat, and 5 bed bugs? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            8,
            14,
            55,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Badminton game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            2,
            4,
            0,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "James wants to buy a pair of socks. If his foot size is 10cm, what available pair of socks may fit him?",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            9,
            7,
            4,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 8 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            0,
            6,
            7,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 24 miles in 7 hours and 16 minutes?",
        "options": [
            0.08807339449541286,
            7.9341234815238195,
            7.047255813321363,
            9.508927844994533
        ],
        "answer": 0.08807339449541286
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 12 sofa, 28 bed, 16 empty boxes, 7 trees, and 13 crows? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            67,
            41,
            63,
            58
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 27 ohms and 17 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 4 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            4,
            0,
            459,
            6,
            44
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international footbal game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 10 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            0,
            16,
            4,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Table-Tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            1,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Peterson began counting from 0. She skip-counted by sevens. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 84,
        "options": [
            86,
            85,
            84,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 12 years old in the year 1515.In his greatest win, he looted 197779199 of 7602609956 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1858,
            1503,
            1828,
            1603
        ],
        "answer": 1503
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 14 years old in the year 1507.In his greatest win, he looted 590161739 of 4423182681 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1824,
            1766,
            1493,
            1658
        ],
        "answer": 1493
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 20 years old in the year 1582.In his greatest win, he looted 339343984 of 2587397533 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1605,
            1624,
            1562,
            1641
        ],
        "answer": 1562
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            21,
            -21,
            19,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 21
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 3 bed, 59 flower vase, 12 refrigerator, 4 trees, and 14 human beings? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            16,
            62,
            18,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $20 to the charity and a total of $14061 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was tripled?",
        "options": [
            703,
            206,
            869,
            839
        ],
        "answer": 703
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $72 to the charity and a total of $14280 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was quadrupled?",
        "options": [
            684,
            931,
            198,
            29
        ],
        "answer": 198
    },
    {
        "question": "Marshall wants to buy a pair of shorts. If his waist size is 39cm, what available pair of shorts may fit him?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            27,
            3,
            43,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 24 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            17,
            23,
            6,
            -23
        ],
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 18 years old in the year 1635.In his greatest win, he looted 583118837 of 1395688146 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins were actually present in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            1395688146,
            1978806983,
            583118837,
            -812569309
        ],
        "answer": 1395688146
    },
    {
        "question": "If a child can eat 19 watermelon , how many watermelon can a man eat?",
        "answer": 30,
        "options": [
            19,
            30,
            49,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ward wants to buy a Belt. If his waist size is 25cm, what available Belt may fit him?",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            29,
            2,
            5,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Table-Tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            0,
            3,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Badminton game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            3,
            0,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 sofa, 33 empty boxes, 13 bed, 2 bed bugs, and 15 fungi spots? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            42,
            70,
            31
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Spencer wants to buy a cap. If his head circumference is 31cm, what available cap may fit him?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            29,
            3,
            40,
            35
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 5 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            1,
            8,
            7,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Lopez wants to buy a pair of shorts. If his waist size is 33cm, what available pair of shorts may fit him?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            35,
            38,
            3,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Vivaan wants to buy a Phone. If his Palm size is 24cm, what available Phone may fit him?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            14,
            16,
            9,
            28
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 33 ohms and 19 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 8 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            8,
            52,
            627,
            12,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of Price increased from 784 per month to 898 per month while the salary of Gordon increased from 662 to 916 and of Cunningham increased from 625 to 673 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Cunningham",
        "options": [
            "Price",
            "Gordon",
            "Cunningham",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 12 sofa, 28 bed, 16 empty boxes, 7 trees, and 13 crows? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            40,
            21,
            20,
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hernandez wants to put a car in a car parking space.The car parking space is 4.518 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the car?",
        "answer": 3.19,
        "options": [
            31.9,
            3.19,
            3.29,
            4.518
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Black began counting from 0. She skip-counted by sevens. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 266,
        "options": [
            266,
            268,
            0,
            267
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Iraa wants to put a car in a road.The road is 8.807 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the car?",
        "answer": 7.26,
        "options": [
            8.807,
            72.6,
            7.359999999999999,
            7.26
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 tubelight, 69 pair of shoes, 71 couch, 15 human beings, and 5 crows? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 107,
        "options": [
            190,
            107,
            0,
            390
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 6 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            23,
            1,
            -23,
            22
        ],
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "Ananya began counting from 0. She skip-counted by tens. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 690,
        "options": [
            692,
            691,
            690,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 mat, 10 table, 90 chair, 6 trees, and 4 fungi spots? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 105,
        "options": [
            106,
            105,
            96,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 4 broom, 73 cycles, 61 mat, 14 bed bugs, and 9 cat? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 48,
        "options": [
            314,
            48,
            367,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If ants can eat 5 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a man eat?",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            5,
            12,
            17,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 12 years old in the year 1849.In his greatest win, he looted 188477309 of 8697944522 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins were actually present in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            8886421831,
            188477309,
            8697944522,
            -8509467213
        ],
        "answer": 8697944522
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 6 flower vase, 42 tubelight, 6 refrigerator, 2 dog, and 12 plants? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            14,
            8,
            48,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 broom, 5 empty boxes, 53 table, 13 bed bugs, and 1 trees? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            66,
            14,
            6,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 4 flower vase, 85 empty boxes, 30 mat, 9 crows, and 9 snail? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 119,
        "options": [
            119,
            39,
            89,
            120
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 47. When the sun is at 124 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            3,
            65,
            53,
            107
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Diya wants to buy a a ring. If his finger circumference is 19cm, what available a ring may fit him?",
        "answer": 30,
        "options": [
            29,
            5,
            30,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 couch, 15 flower vase, 55 refrigerator, 2 trees, and 13 bed bugs? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 84,
        "options": [
            57,
            29,
            85,
            84
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international basketball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            3,
            9,
            4,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ferguson wants to put a house in a street.The street is 7.36 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the house?",
        "answer": 1.08,
        "options": [
            10.8,
            1.1800000000000002,
            7.36,
            1.08
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Powell earns $11 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $1 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Powell was paid $4988, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            195,
            424,
            72,
            191
        ],
        "answer": 424
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 34000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 750000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            351,
            292,
            45.333,
            222
        ],
        "answer": 45.333
    },
    {
        "question": "If elephant can eat 29 watermelon , how many watermelon can a pigeon eat?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            29,
            22,
            51,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            11,
            -29,
            29,
            18
        ],
        "answer": 29
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 tubelight, 41 refrigerator, 93 mat, 8 cockroaches, and 8 human beings? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            101,
            17,
            51,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 bed, 4 couch, 91 tubelight, 13 people, and 3 snail? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            16,
            17,
            104,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 6 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            3,
            -24,
            24,
            21
        ],
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "Grant began counting from 0. She skip-counted by sevens. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 35,
        "options": [
            36,
            37,
            35,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 couch, 66 flower vase, 15 cycles, 14 cat, and 15 dog? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            81,
            29,
            29,
            30
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 16 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            21,
            22,
            -22,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 22
    },
    {
        "question": "Hunt wants to put a phone in a pocket.The pocket is 8.754 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the phone?",
        "answer": 2.26,
        "options": [
            8.754,
            2.26,
            2.36,
            22.599999999999998
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 broom, 5 empty boxes, 53 table, 13 bed bugs, and 1 trees? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 53,
        "options": [
            53,
            71,
            63,
            68
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international baseball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            17,
            1,
            6,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If man can eat 25 chocolates , how many chocolates can a cow eat?",
        "answer": 26,
        "options": [
            25,
            26,
            51,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Butler wants to put a Drawer in a Table.The Table is 9.344 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Drawer?",
        "answer": 3.0,
        "options": [
            3.1,
            30.0,
            9.344,
            3.0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Fisher began counting from 0. She skip-counted by threes. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 177,
        "options": [
            177,
            178,
            179,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Collins wants to buy a cap. If his head circumference is 25cm, what available cap may fit him?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            45,
            7,
            10,
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If snail can eat 62 grapes , how many grapes can a dog eat?",
        "answer": 93,
        "options": [
            62,
            93,
            155,
            31
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Marshall wants to buy a pair of shorts. If his waist size is 15cm, what available pair of shorts may fit him?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            24,
            40,
            36,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Navya wants to put a Table in a Room.The Room is 7.273 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Table?",
        "answer": 1.45,
        "options": [
            14.5,
            1.55,
            1.45,
            7.273
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If snail can eat 20 chocolates , how many chocolates can a cat eat?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            20,
            23,
            43,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 12 years old in the year 1236.In his greatest win, he looted 385508955 of 7896726110 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins are remaining in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            7511217155,
            7896726110,
            385508955,
            8282235065
        ],
        "answer": 7511217155
    },
    {
        "question": "Schmidt wants to buy a cap. If his head circumference is 26cm, what available cap may fit him?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            37,
            45,
            39,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 1 feet by 9 feet?",
        "options": [
            1296,
            5661,
            3694,
            9287
        ],
        "answer": 1296
    },
    {
        "question": "Mohammed wants to buy a Belt. If his waist size is 22cm, what available Belt may fit him?",
        "answer": 34,
        "options": [
            20,
            21,
            34,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A family is going on a vacation to Chicago in a bus. There were 9 men, 10 women, 7 children of less than 10 years, 7 old people of age above 60 years.How many of the people can drive??",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            116,
            33,
            0,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international cricket game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            9,
            10,
            15,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international baseball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 5 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            9,
            11,
            1,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Arjun wants to buy a Phone. If his Palm size is 21cm, what available Phone may fit him?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            17,
            30,
            41,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international basketball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            4,
            3,
            5,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of Howard increased from 559 per month to 678 per month while the salary of Ramos increased from 331 to 679 and of Advik increased from 984 to 990 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Advik",
        "options": [
            "Howard",
            "Ramos",
            "Advik",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jones wants to buy a cap. If his head circumference is 15cm, what available cap may fit him?",
        "answer": 19,
        "options": [
            9,
            19,
            13,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Vihaan wants to put a chocolate in a jar.The jar is 9.523 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the chocolate?",
        "answer": 1.46,
        "options": [
            9.523,
            1.56,
            14.6,
            1.46
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 3 couch, 77 flower vase, 90 empty boxes, 2 bed bugs, and 15 cat? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            46,
            132,
            133
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            21,
            -21,
            19,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 21
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 49 ohms and 27 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 9 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            27,
            9,
            76,
            49
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 6 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            7,
            -17,
            10,
            17
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 fan, 14 tubelight, 29 broom, 13 cat, and 14 pigeons? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            266,
            0,
            17,
            390
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Aarav wants to buy a cap. If his head circumference is 11cm, what available cap may fit him?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            22,
            35,
            40,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 2 feet by 2 feet?",
        "options": [
            6531,
            2794,
            576,
            7262
        ],
        "answer": 576
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $6 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-third mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 47.0 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            479,
            483,
            365,
            144.0
        ],
        "answer": 144.0
    },
    {
        "question": "Aarav wants to buy a pair of shorts. If his waist size is 16cm, what available pair of shorts may fit him?",
        "answer": 21,
        "options": [
            5,
            21,
            9,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Grant wants to put a chocolate in a jar.The jar is 9.428 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the chocolate?",
        "answer": 6.89,
        "options": [
            68.89999999999999,
            6.89,
            9.428,
            6.989999999999999
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kph if you travel 31 miles in 2 hours and 52 minutes?",
        "options": [
            17.30232558139535,
            7.927255253967914,
            8.188359018808539,
            4.522447356976805
        ],
        "answer": 17.30232558139535
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of Sai increased from 630 per month to 861 per month while the salary of Arjun increased from 798 to 863 and of Green increased from 581 to 681 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Green",
        "options": [
            "Sai",
            "Arjun",
            "Green",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 67000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 503000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            876,
            212,
            133.201,
            49
        ],
        "answer": 133.201
    },
    {
        "question": "If a child can eat 27 apples , how many apples can a cat eat?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            27,
            23,
            50,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international squash game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            0,
            2,
            -1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 empty boxes, 20 bed, 15 refrigerator, 8 dog, and 7 pigeons? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            13,
            36,
            40
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Aarav wants to buy a pair of socks. If his foot size is 40cm, what available pair of socks may fit him?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            24,
            38,
            45,
            32
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kyra wants to put a car in a car parking space.The car parking space is 5.727 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the car?",
        "answer": 4.73,
        "options": [
            4.73,
            5.727,
            4.83,
            47.300000000000004
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Boxing game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            0,
            2,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $5 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-third mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 12.2 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            250,
            130,
            55,
            38.6
        ],
        "answer": 38.6
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Boxing game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            0,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Olson wants to buy a necklace. If his neck circumference is 18cm, what available necklace may fit him?",
        "answer": 30,
        "options": [
            25,
            5,
            30,
            25
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Weaver wants to buy a a ring. If his finger circumference is 19cm, what available a ring may fit him?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            10,
            37,
            19,
            43
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 23 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            9,
            -9,
            4,
            5
        ],
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 6 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            3,
            -24,
            24,
            21
        ],
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 88. When the sun is at 33 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 96,
        "options": [
            28,
            10,
            68,
            96
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 11 ohms and 19 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 2 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            2,
            19,
            11,
            30
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 empty boxes, 37 chair, 82 refrigerator, 8 cockroaches, and 5 dog? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 13,
        "options": [
            14,
            13,
            48,
            90
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 16 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            21,
            22,
            -22,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 22
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 3 mat, 74 broom, 79 flower vase, 11 algae spots, and 15 cockroaches? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 60,
        "options": [
            159,
            60,
            161,
            170
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 86 gallons. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 5/9 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            29,
            61,
            17,
            47.78
        ],
        "answer": 47.78
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international footbal game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 3 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            1,
            7,
            8,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 empty boxes, 95 bed, 83 sofa, 4 pigeons, and 3 plants? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 184,
        "options": [
            196,
            193,
            193,
            184
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 5 feet by 1 feet?",
        "options": [
            720,
            1487,
            5291,
            7067
        ],
        "answer": 720
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 1 feet by 1 feet?",
        "options": [
            5039,
            9225,
            144,
            8748
        ],
        "answer": 144
    },
    {
        "question": "Diya wants to buy a pair of shoes. If his foot size is 5cm, what available pair of shoes may fit him?",
        "answer": 32,
        "options": [
            26,
            13,
            16,
            32
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 42000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 615000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            68292.683,
            542,
            262,
            73
        ],
        "answer": 68292.683
    },
    {
        "question": "Stephens began counting from 0. She skip-counted by eights. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 448,
        "options": [
            448,
            449,
            0,
            450
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Carter wants to buy a pair of socks. If his foot size is 6cm, what available pair of socks may fit him?",
        "answer": 19,
        "options": [
            10,
            16,
            19,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 42 miles in 5 hours and 23 minutes?",
        "options": [
            2.3944708939641455,
            0.13003095975232198,
            8.551207694974547,
            6.349440619218911
        ],
        "answer": 0.13003095975232198
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 14 years old in the year 1623.In his greatest win, he looted 677685235 of 7547369880 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins were actually present in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            7547369880,
            8225055115,
            677685235,
            -6869684645
        ],
        "answer": 7547369880
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international rugby game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 3 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            13,
            14,
            30,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 fan, 31 tubelight, 34 pair of shoes, 3 cockroaches, and 1 bed bugs? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 75,
        "options": [
            75,
            82,
            84,
            82
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 23 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            9,
            -9,
            4,
            5
        ],
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 23 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -27,
            23,
            4,
            27
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 sofa, 33 empty boxes, 13 bed, 2 bed bugs, and 15 fungi spots? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            41,
            18,
            17,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If elephant can eat 22 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a cow eat?",
        "answer": 21,
        "options": [
            22,
            21,
            43,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If dog can eat 7 cake , how many cake can a giraffee eat?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            7,
            9,
            16,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Badminton game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            3,
            0,
            1,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $10 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-tenth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 29.1 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            480,
            350,
            363,
            262.9
        ],
        "answer": 262.9
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 empty boxes, 37 chair, 82 refrigerator, 8 cockroaches, and 5 dog? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 130,
        "options": [
            131,
            48,
            130,
            90
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Tran wants to buy a pair of shoes. If his foot size is 19cm, what available pair of shoes may fit him?",
        "answer": 26,
        "options": [
            17,
            26,
            4,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 5 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -25,
            16,
            25,
            9
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "Sanchez wants to put a fruit in a basket.The basket is 8.071 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the fruit?",
        "answer": 6.25,
        "options": [
            6.35,
            6.25,
            8.071,
            62.5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Peters wants to buy a necklace. If his neck circumference is 20cm, what available necklace may fit him?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            10,
            43,
            15,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $26 to the charity and a total of $13456 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was quadrupled?",
        "options": [
            517,
            35,
            676,
            972
        ],
        "answer": 517
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 44 pints. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 2/9 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            9.78,
            88,
            62,
            96
        ],
        "answer": 9.78
    },
    {
        "question": "Hawkins wants to buy a shirt. If his body size is 20cm, what available shirt may fit him?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            23,
            3,
            25,
            28
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 37 ohms and 11 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 6 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            6,
            11,
            37,
            48
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Boxing game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            2,
            1,
            0,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jackson wants to put a fruit in a basket.The basket is 9.894 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the fruit?",
        "answer": 1.69,
        "options": [
            1.69,
            1.79,
            16.9,
            9.894
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 75 miles in 5 hours and 54 minutes?",
        "options": [
            9.820042743589298,
            6.237865047635333,
            2.8466486062235274,
            0.3389830508474576
        ],
        "answer": 0.3389830508474576
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -17,
            4,
            17,
            13
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $60 to the charity and a total of $9270 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was doubled?",
        "options": [
            288,
            154,
            433,
            302
        ],
        "answer": 154
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of Peterson increased from 682 per month to 900 per month while the salary of Krishna increased from 374 to 840 and of Chavez increased from 334 to 953 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Chavez",
        "options": [
            "Peterson",
            "Krishna",
            "Chavez",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 refrigerator, 23 empty boxes, 83 couch, 7 cat, and 9 algae spots? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 116,
        "options": [
            33,
            116,
            90,
            117
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 broom, 10 sofa, 90 tubelight, 9 cat, and 12 algae spots? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            134,
            118,
            15,
            75
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 flower vase, 95 mat, 40 empty boxes, 10 dog, and 14 cockroaches? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 148,
        "options": [
            149,
            108,
            50,
            148
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If snail can eat 17 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a giraffee eat?",
        "answer": 21,
        "options": [
            17,
            21,
            38,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -25,
            23,
            2,
            25
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "Prisha wants to buy a hat. If his head circumference is 32cm, what available hat may fit him?",
        "answer": 33,
        "options": [
            27,
            33,
            5,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            20,
            14,
            6,
            -20
        ],
        "answer": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "If elephant can eat 56 grapes , how many grapes can a cow eat?",
        "answer": 80,
        "options": [
            56,
            80,
            136,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            21,
            -21,
            19,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 21
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 23 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -27,
            23,
            4,
            27
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international footbal game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 3 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            10,
            9,
            16,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $72 to the charity and a total of $4472 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was doubled?",
        "options": [
            350,
            62,
            82,
            357
        ],
        "answer": 62
    },
    {
        "question": "Lopez began counting from 0. She skip-counted by threes. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 300,
        "options": [
            302,
            300,
            301,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If cow can eat 16 apples , how many apples can a man eat?",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            16,
            5,
            21,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 flower vase, 46 refrigerator, 87 couch, 2 snail, and 14 bed bugs? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 141,
        "options": [
            142,
            54,
            141,
            89
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Burns wants to buy a a ring. If his finger circumference is 28cm, what available a ring may fit him?",
        "answer": 30,
        "options": [
            30,
            11,
            7,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Ice Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 6 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            9,
            2,
            0,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Friday and returns to the bank 5881days later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Saturday",
        "options": [
            "Thursday",
            "Saturday",
            "Sunday",
            "Thursday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 7 feet by 7 feet?",
        "options": [
            6557,
            7056,
            3805,
            7627
        ],
        "answer": 7056
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 broom, 5 empty boxes, 53 table, 13 bed bugs, and 1 trees? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            54,
            2,
            38,
            60
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 16 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            16,
            6,
            10,
            -16
        ],
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 23 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            15,
            -15,
            4,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "question": "Advik wants to put a car in a road.The road is 9.452 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the car?",
        "answer": 5.75,
        "options": [
            57.5,
            9.452,
            5.75,
            5.85
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Vivaan began counting from 0. She skip-counted by nine's. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 891,
        "options": [
            891,
            892,
            893,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Cook wants to put a Card in a Envelope.The Envelope is 6.751 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Card?",
        "answer": 1.42,
        "options": [
            6.751,
            14.2,
            1.42,
            1.52
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            20,
            14,
            6,
            -20
        ],
        "answer": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "Rose wants to buy a hat. If his head circumference is 16cm, what available hat may fit him?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            34,
            18,
            39,
            43
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 46000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 88000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            821,
            516,
            522727.273,
            247
        ],
        "answer": 522727.273
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 17 miles in 8 hours and 37 minutes?",
        "options": [
            3.5137576538547464,
            8.349529412391224,
            4.605939708654456,
            1.9729206963249515
        ],
        "answer": 1.9729206963249515
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 60. When the sun is at 47 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 25,
        "options": [
            101,
            106,
            25,
            64
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Wednesday and returns to the bank 6years later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "tuesday",
        "options": [
            "Saturday",
            "Thursday",
            "tuesday",
            "Saturday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 60000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 986000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            662,
            246,
            0.061,
            760
        ],
        "answer": 0.061
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 7 fan, 3 cycles, 49 flower vase, 12 cat, and 4 human beings? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            36,
            24,
            14,
            31
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Myra wants to put a luggage in a car trunk.The car trunk is 9.067 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the luggage?",
        "answer": 2.42,
        "options": [
            9.067,
            2.52,
            2.42,
            24.2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 5 years old in the year 1598.In his greatest win, he looted 914225203 of 1738827883 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins were actually present in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            1738827883,
            -824602680,
            914225203,
            2653053086
        ],
        "answer": 1738827883
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            4,
            28,
            24,
            -28
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kph if you travel 41 miles in 4 hours and 42 minutes?",
        "options": [
            3.008583809065482,
            3.199181072492265,
            13.95744680851064,
            8.974414311718416
        ],
        "answer": 13.95744680851064
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 24 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            13,
            -17,
            17,
            4
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 6 feet by 8 feet?",
        "options": [
            9596,
            1542,
            6912,
            6245
        ],
        "answer": 6912
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 84. When the sun is at 89 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 56,
        "options": [
            106,
            86,
            98,
            56
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Diya wants to buy a a ring. If his finger circumference is 38cm, what available a ring may fit him?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            14,
            14,
            41,
            28
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $2 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-seventh mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 40.6 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            279.2,
            474,
            454,
            282
        ],
        "answer": 279.2
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 9 years old in the year 1447.In his greatest win, he looted 714664535 of 4224985971 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1490,
            1502,
            1624,
            1438
        ],
        "answer": 1438
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            11,
            -29,
            29,
            18
        ],
        "answer": 29
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 18 years old in the year 1351.In his greatest win, he looted 63376057 of 2648341027 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1859,
            1848,
            1466,
            1333
        ],
        "answer": 1333
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 fan, 31 tubelight, 34 pair of shoes, 3 cockroaches, and 1 bed bugs? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            14,
            21,
            22
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Wright wants to put a Car in a Garage.The Garage is 3.275 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Car?",
        "answer": 1.15,
        "options": [
            11.5,
            3.275,
            1.15,
            1.25
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If dog can eat 23 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 26,
        "options": [
            23,
            26,
            49,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If snail can eat 74 grapes , how many grapes can a cat eat?",
        "answer": 98,
        "options": [
            74,
            98,
            172,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 15 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -26,
            19,
            7,
            26
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Badminton game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            4,
            1,
            0,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If cat can eat 93 grapes , how many grapes can a man eat?",
        "answer": 122,
        "options": [
            93,
            122,
            215,
            29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Johnson wants to put a phone in a pocket.The pocket is 9.127 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the phone?",
        "answer": 4.81,
        "options": [
            4.909999999999999,
            9.127,
            4.81,
            48.099999999999994
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 6 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            7,
            -17,
            10,
            17
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 empty boxes, 9 couch, 71 sofa, 12 algae spots, and 2 plants? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 93,
        "options": [
            0,
            93,
            121,
            356
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international baseball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            8,
            13,
            2,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 tubelight, 41 refrigerator, 93 mat, 8 cockroaches, and 8 human beings? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            124,
            93,
            36,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 couch, 27 chair, 12 cycles, 10 plants, and 13 cockroaches? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 26,
        "options": [
            51,
            47,
            46,
            26
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a child can eat 27 watermelon , how many watermelon can a cat eat?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            27,
            9,
            36,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 2000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 534000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            225,
            234,
            3745.318,
            524
        ],
        "answer": 3745.318
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 4 broom, 73 cycles, 61 mat, 14 bed bugs, and 9 cat? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            65,
            112,
            29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Boxing game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            0,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 12 ohms and 5 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 19 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            5,
            19,
            48,
            60,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ward began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fives. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 130,
        "options": [
            0,
            131,
            132,
            130
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -30,
            13,
            17,
            30
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 42 miles in 6 hours and 18 minutes?",
        "options": [
            0.17777777777777778,
            6.3591293787897625,
            5.587496116329487,
            3.2556834659368787
        ],
        "answer": 0.17777777777777778
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 96. When the sun is at 2 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 97,
        "options": [
            5,
            49,
            97,
            36
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 4 broom, 73 cycles, 61 mat, 14 bed bugs, and 9 cat? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 138,
        "options": [
            77,
            75,
            138,
            139
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Simpson wants to put a Statue in a River.The River is 7.005 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Statue?",
        "answer": 4.64,
        "options": [
            46.4,
            4.64,
            7.005,
            4.739999999999999
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 46000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 454000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            0.101,
            657,
            604,
            385
        ],
        "answer": 0.101
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 6 pair of shoes, 88 couch, 24 tubelight, 13 dog, and 4 plants? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 96,
        "options": [
            0,
            341,
            393,
            96
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 flower vase, 95 mat, 40 empty boxes, 10 dog, and 14 cockroaches? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 148,
        "options": [
            148,
            293,
            297,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Boxing game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            -1,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Table-Tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            3,
            1,
            0,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 couch, 74 cycles, 90 empty boxes, 5 bed bugs, and 14 snail? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 19,
        "options": [
            95,
            19,
            20,
            82
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 3 feet by 3 feet?",
        "options": [
            5730,
            1296,
            7541,
            2062
        ],
        "answer": 1296
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 4 flower vase, 85 empty boxes, 30 mat, 9 crows, and 9 snail? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 83,
        "options": [
            137,
            83,
            122,
            120
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Krishna wants to put a phone in a pocket.The pocket is 6.883 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the phone?",
        "answer": 3.51,
        "options": [
            3.61,
            35.099999999999994,
            6.883,
            3.51
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 20 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -30,
            11,
            30,
            19
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            21,
            -21,
            19,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 21
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 2 mat, 53 table, 8 flower vase, 1 bed bugs, and 10 dog? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            19,
            53,
            60
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "West wants to put a house in a street.The street is 6.353 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the house?",
        "answer": 1.01,
        "options": [
            10.1,
            1.01,
            6.353,
            1.11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Aayan wants to put a fruit in a basket.The basket is 3.337 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the fruit?",
        "answer": 1.77,
        "options": [
            1.77,
            17.7,
            1.87,
            3.337
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            15,
            -26,
            26,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 11 ohms and 49 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 17 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            60,
            539,
            17,
            49,
            41
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international golf game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            0,
            -1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kph if you travel 26 miles in 7 hours and 28 minutes?",
        "options": [
            5.571428571428571,
            9.166993965763199,
            2.2505625121310455,
            3.8917141109205584
        ],
        "answer": 5.571428571428571
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 3 mat, 74 broom, 79 flower vase, 11 algae spots, and 15 cockroaches? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 26,
        "options": [
            26,
            27,
            77,
            90
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ross wants to buy a Phone. If his Palm size is 38cm, what available Phone may fit him?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            10,
            40,
            41,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If elephant can eat 8 cake , how many cake can a cat eat?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            8,
            7,
            15,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Rose wants to buy a necklace. If his neck circumference is 36cm, what available necklace may fit him?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            17,
            2,
            42,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Stevens wants to put a luggage in a car trunk.The car trunk is 6.802 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the luggage?",
        "answer": 5.5,
        "options": [
            55.0,
            6.802,
            5.5,
            5.6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kph if you travel 95 miles in 1 hours and 54 minutes?",
        "options": [
            8.674687440892702,
            5.375245053084942,
            4.297687419912363,
            80.0
        ],
        "answer": 80.0
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 couch, 66 flower vase, 15 cycles, 14 cat, and 15 dog? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 96,
        "options": [
            96,
            97,
            29,
            81
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 mat, 10 table, 90 chair, 6 trees, and 4 fungi spots? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            96,
            15,
            11,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international footbal game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 10 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            0,
            21,
            4,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 6 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            23,
            1,
            -23,
            22
        ],
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international footbal game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 4 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            19,
            5,
            11,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 58 gallons. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 4/8 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            29.0,
            37,
            96,
            19
        ],
        "answer": 29.0
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -25,
            23,
            2,
            25
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 41 gallons. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 1/7 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            56,
            31,
            83,
            5.86
        ],
        "answer": 5.86
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 6 years old in the year 1327.In his greatest win, he looted 878846154 of 4476388574 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins were actually present in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            878846154,
            -3597542420,
            5355234728,
            4476388574
        ],
        "answer": 4476388574
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 12 years old in the year 1693.In his greatest win, he looted 788950713 of 9490956965 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1685,
            1850,
            1681,
            1791
        ],
        "answer": 1681
    },
    {
        "question": "A family is going on a vacation to Chicago in a bus. There were 3 men, 5 women, 7 children of less than 10 years, 6 old people of age above 60 years.How many of the people can drive??",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            108,
            21,
            0,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 72000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 518000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            138.996,
            332,
            220,
            245
        ],
        "answer": 138.996
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 broom, 5 empty boxes, 53 table, 13 bed bugs, and 1 trees? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            5,
            326,
            82,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Gonzalez wants to buy a Hand glove. If his Palm-size is 14cm, what available Hand glove may fit him?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            40,
            3,
            14,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 15 years old in the year 1841.In his greatest win, he looted 717984761 of 7047515081 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1826,
            1863,
            1840,
            1877
        ],
        "answer": 1826
    },
    {
        "question": "Turner wants to put a Car in a Garage.The Garage is 5.732 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Car?",
        "answer": 1.92,
        "options": [
            2.02,
            5.732,
            1.92,
            19.2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If ants can eat 14 watermelon , how many watermelon can a cat eat?",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            14,
            29,
            43,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 18 ohms and 31 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 10 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            49,
            0,
            558,
            10,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 100 miles in 3 hours and 42 minutes?",
        "options": [
            3.5206390428220073,
            27.027027027027028,
            4.046061338738259,
            1.7001501057493527
        ],
        "answer": 27.027027027027028
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 7 cycles, 45 sofa, 68 chair, 11 plants, and 8 bed bugs? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 19,
        "options": [
            52,
            19,
            20,
            79
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 24 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            13,
            -17,
            17,
            4
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "Evans began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fours. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 204,
        "options": [
            0,
            205,
            204,
            206
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 bed, 11 cycles, 61 empty boxes, 6 crows, and 11 pigeons? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            48,
            69,
            12,
            67
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 34000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 257000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            809,
            876,
            132.296,
            527
        ],
        "answer": 132.296
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $4 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-eighth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 23.0 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            231,
            180.0,
            445,
            378
        ],
        "answer": 180.0
    },
    {
        "question": "Schmidt wants to buy a hoodie. If his chest size is 13cm, what available hoodie may fit him?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            38,
            41,
            37,
            28
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 34000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 178000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            191.011,
            926,
            354,
            493
        ],
        "answer": 191.011
    },
    {
        "question": "Mcdonald wants to put a Statue in a River.The River is 6.52 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Statue?",
        "answer": 2.66,
        "options": [
            26.6,
            6.52,
            2.66,
            2.7600000000000002
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $78 to the charity and a total of $7340 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was doubled?",
        "options": [
            94,
            647,
            796,
            373
        ],
        "answer": 94
    },
    {
        "question": "Vivaan wants to buy a Hand glove. If his Palm-size is 23cm, what available Hand glove may fit him?",
        "answer": 33,
        "options": [
            10,
            27,
            9,
            33
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 empty boxes, 9 couch, 71 sofa, 12 algae spots, and 2 plants? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            95,
            28,
            106
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Reyansh wants to buy a pair of socks. If his foot size is 33cm, what available pair of socks may fit him?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            18,
            40,
            16,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 74 miles in 10 hours and 44 minutes?",
        "options": [
            9.650032041424394,
            6.696321542569157,
            4.204260979239246,
            6.894409937888199
        ],
        "answer": 6.894409937888199
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 55000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 171000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            249,
            0.322,
            399,
            358
        ],
        "answer": 0.322
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 flower vase, 95 mat, 40 empty boxes, 10 dog, and 14 cockroaches? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            154,
            80,
            109,
            22
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 15 years old in the year 1155.In his greatest win, he looted 331991280 of 360960493 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1319,
            1341,
            1140,
            1688
        ],
        "answer": 1140
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 49 ohms and 27 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 4 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            49,
            76,
            4,
            27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $8 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-third mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 22.9 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            212,
            156,
            73.7,
            218
        ],
        "answer": 73.7
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Boxing game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            0,
            2,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 6 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            3,
            -24,
            24,
            21
        ],
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 empty boxes, 95 bed, 83 sofa, 4 pigeons, and 3 plants? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            87,
            109,
            7,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Castro wants to put a Table in a Room.The Room is 5.628 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Table?",
        "answer": 2.66,
        "options": [
            5.628,
            26.6,
            2.7600000000000002,
            2.66
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A family is going on a vacation to Chicago in a bus. There were 6 men, 8 women, 6 children of less than 10 years, 5 old people of age above 60 years.How many of the people can drive??",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            112,
            25,
            0,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If pigeon can eat 15 chocolates , how many chocolates can a cow eat?",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            15,
            29,
            44,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ford wants to buy a pair of pants. If his waist size is 21cm, what available pair of pants may fit him?",
        "answer": 26,
        "options": [
            20,
            24,
            26,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If snail can eat 16 lemons , how many lemons can a elephant eat?",
        "answer": 21,
        "options": [
            16,
            21,
            37,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of Daniels increased from 749 per month to 849 per month while the salary of Aarohi increased from 671 to 846 and of Dixon increased from 710 to 881 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Dixon",
        "options": [
            "Daniels",
            "Aarohi",
            "Dixon",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            11,
            -29,
            29,
            18
        ],
        "answer": 29
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 11 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            8,
            1,
            -9,
            9
        ],
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "Myra wants to buy a hoodie. If his chest size is 18cm, what available hoodie may fit him?",
        "answer": 36,
        "options": [
            35,
            36,
            36,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 16. When the sun is at 179 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 90,
        "options": [
            11,
            11,
            90,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Knight wants to buy a pair of socks. If his foot size is 29cm, what available pair of socks may fit him?",
        "answer": 32,
        "options": [
            13,
            32,
            23,
            30
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 6 feet by 6 feet?",
        "options": [
            7236,
            5184,
            6840,
            123
        ],
        "answer": 5184
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 11 years old in the year 1716.In his greatest win, he looted 836326661 of 8675669182 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1765,
            1760,
            1705,
            1764
        ],
        "answer": 1705
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 tubelight, 41 refrigerator, 93 mat, 8 cockroaches, and 8 human beings? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 128,
        "options": [
            160,
            154,
            146,
            128
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            19,
            9,
            10,
            -19
        ],
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international squash game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            1,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 93 gallons. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 4/7 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            14,
            86,
            53.14,
            81
        ],
        "answer": 53.14
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 4 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            3,
            11,
            10,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 2 flower vase, 85 table, 85 pair of shoes, 3 cat, and 9 crows? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            88,
            13,
            12,
            87
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Peterson wants to buy a cap. If his head circumference is 38cm, what available cap may fit him?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            8,
            41,
            28,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Badminton game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            0,
            4,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Angel began counting from 0. She skip-counted by nine's. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 657,
        "options": [
            659,
            0,
            658,
            657
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 83 miles in 3 hours and 26 minutes?",
        "options": [
            5.166149480355457,
            8.55707258424523,
            1.4521720215739138,
            0.6446601941747573
        ],
        "answer": 0.6446601941747573
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 12 fan, 97 tubelight, 86 empty boxes, 6 cat, and 10 trees? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 59,
        "options": [
            202,
            210,
            59,
            204
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kennedy earns $6 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $3 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Kennedy was paid $3420, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            87,
            413,
            158,
            262
        ],
        "answer": 413
    },
    {
        "question": "Porter wants to buy a a ring. If his finger circumference is 12cm, what available a ring may fit him?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            6,
            17,
            20,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            19,
            9,
            10,
            -19
        ],
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Boxing game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            -1,
            2,
            0,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Gibson wants to put a Car in a Garage.The Garage is 7.23 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Car?",
        "answer": 5.92,
        "options": [
            7.23,
            6.02,
            59.2,
            5.92
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 sofa, 16 bed, 93 pair of shoes, 9 algae spots, and 10 dog? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 19,
        "options": [
            102,
            19,
            20,
            21
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If man can eat 22 lemons , how many lemons can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 19,
        "options": [
            22,
            19,
            41,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Griffin wants to buy a Belt. If his waist size is 7cm, what available Belt may fit him?",
        "answer": 25,
        "options": [
            21,
            3,
            18,
            25
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 5 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            22,
            10,
            4,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Vivaan wants to buy a pair of pants. If his waist size is 38cm, what available pair of pants may fit him?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            11,
            13,
            41,
            41
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 15 ohms and 23 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 7 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            345,
            38,
            7,
            0,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 89. When the sun is at 58 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            96,
            101,
            28,
            99
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international rugby game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 12 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            9,
            0,
            20,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international basketball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 4 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            1,
            2,
            0,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If giraffee can eat 30 apples , how many apples can a man eat?",
        "answer": 25,
        "options": [
            30,
            25,
            55,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 1 feet by 4 feet?",
        "options": [
            9481,
            4809,
            576,
            3833
        ],
        "answer": 576
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander wants to buy a hoodie. If his chest size is 16cm, what available hoodie may fit him?",
        "answer": 30,
        "options": [
            11,
            27,
            23,
            30
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 97 gallons. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 1/6 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            16.17,
            35,
            94,
            41
        ],
        "answer": 16.17
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 23 ohms and 50 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 3 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            23,
            73,
            3,
            50
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If elephant can eat 6 cake , how many cake can a cow eat?",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            6,
            5,
            11,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international footbal game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 3 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            8,
            2,
            7,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Burns wants to buy a hoodie. If his chest size is 30cm, what available hoodie may fit him?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            20,
            43,
            24,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If pigeon can eat 7 cake , how many cake can a cow eat?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            7,
            10,
            17,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 44 ohms and 6 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 4 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            6,
            44,
            50,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 4 couch, 3 broom, 73 bed, 1 plants, and 13 cat? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 65,
        "options": [
            90,
            65,
            92,
            87
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 23 miles in 8 hours and 11 minutes?",
        "options": [
            1.2209396463007858,
            1.313646063940467,
            0.04684317718940937,
            5.03671377529056
        ],
        "answer": 0.04684317718940937
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 44 ohms and 6 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 5 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            264,
            50,
            22,
            5,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $9 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional half mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 10.3 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            350,
            118,
            27.6,
            166
        ],
        "answer": 27.6
    },
    {
        "question": "Hoffman wants to buy a pair of pants. If his waist size is 21cm, what available pair of pants may fit him?",
        "answer": 36,
        "options": [
            28,
            11,
            36,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 4 couch, 18 tubelight, 51 broom, 14 snail, and 9 cat? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            24,
            22,
            23,
            65
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Weaver wants to put a Table in a Room.The Room is 5.712 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Table?",
        "answer": 1.96,
        "options": [
            1.96,
            5.712,
            19.6,
            2.06
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 flower vase, 86 chair, 59 empty boxes, 13 human beings, and 3 trees? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            54,
            4,
            146
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Harrison wants to buy a necklace. If his neck circumference is 10cm, what available necklace may fit him?",
        "answer": 19,
        "options": [
            12,
            14,
            19,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Moore wants to buy a Hand glove. If his Palm-size is 38cm, what available Hand glove may fit him?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            12,
            43,
            37,
            41
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 flower vase, 42 empty boxes, 68 bed, 12 pigeons, and 15 cockroaches? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            137,
            129,
            122,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $88 to the charity and a total of $8484 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was quadrupled?",
        "options": [
            721,
            795,
            96,
            432
        ],
        "answer": 96
    },
    {
        "question": "Bailey wants to buy a hoodie. If his chest size is 7cm, what available hoodie may fit him?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            4,
            2,
            20,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If ants can eat 10 apples , how many apples can a cow eat?",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            10,
            14,
            24,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 6 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            23,
            1,
            -23,
            22
        ],
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 72 miles in 6 hours and 18 minutes?",
        "options": [
            0.3047619047619048,
            4.875375803148323,
            8.654101177317687,
            8.88532840577085
        ],
        "answer": 0.3047619047619048
    },
    {
        "question": "Cook wants to put a Pizza Box in a Refrigerator.The Refrigerator is 3.528 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Pizza Box?",
        "answer": 1.93,
        "options": [
            1.93,
            2.03,
            19.3,
            3.528
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Gibson wants to buy a shirt. If his body size is 18cm, what available shirt may fit him?",
        "answer": 26,
        "options": [
            11,
            10,
            16,
            26
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 3 bed, 59 flower vase, 12 refrigerator, 4 trees, and 14 human beings? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 74,
        "options": [
            75,
            16,
            62,
            74
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Tran wants to put a Card in a Envelope.The Envelope is 6.532 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Card?",
        "answer": 4.81,
        "options": [
            48.099999999999994,
            4.909999999999999,
            6.532,
            4.81
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 empty boxes, 37 chair, 82 refrigerator, 8 cockroaches, and 5 dog? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 85,
        "options": [
            234,
            85,
            171,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kph if you travel 88 miles in 6 hours and 31 minutes?",
        "options": [
            9.281752374961414,
            3.575734338673637,
            21.606138107416882,
            1.7738708768226235
        ],
        "answer": 21.606138107416882
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 12 broom, 32 flower vase, 25 mat, 13 human beings, and 13 people? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 69,
        "options": [
            69,
            70,
            38,
            44
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            15,
            -26,
            26,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 6 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            23,
            1,
            -23,
            22
        ],
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Ice Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 4 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            1,
            11,
            2,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If cat can eat 12 watermelon , how many watermelon can a ants eat?",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            12,
            5,
            17,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 3000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 700000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            885,
            674,
            0.004,
            855
        ],
        "answer": 0.004
    },
    {
        "question": "If cow can eat 16 apples , how many apples can a snail eat?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            16,
            6,
            22,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If cat can eat 8 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a giraffee eat?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            8,
            16,
            24,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Henry wants to buy a pair of shoes. If his foot size is 38cm, what available pair of shoes may fit him?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            39,
            29,
            12,
            27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $7 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-tenth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 5.8 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            240,
            184,
            50.2,
            74
        ],
        "answer": 50.2
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 3 feet by 8 feet?",
        "options": [
            3456,
            6550,
            1005,
            2913
        ],
        "answer": 3456
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 5 feet by 10 feet?",
        "options": [
            6049,
            7200,
            9948,
            4018
        ],
        "answer": 7200
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 32 ohms and 29 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 7 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            7,
            29,
            61,
            32
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ryan wants to put a Statue in a River.The River is 7.602 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Statue?",
        "answer": 3.13,
        "options": [
            3.23,
            3.13,
            31.299999999999997,
            7.602
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 20 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -30,
            11,
            30,
            19
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "Mason wants to buy a pair of socks. If his foot size is 12cm, what available pair of socks may fit him?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            9,
            28,
            23,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Moore wants to put a Pizza Box in a Refrigerator.The Refrigerator is 8.363 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Pizza Box?",
        "answer": 7.14,
        "options": [
            71.39999999999999,
            7.14,
            7.239999999999999,
            8.363
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Martin wants to buy a hat. If his head circumference is 40cm, what available hat may fit him?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            18,
            11,
            21,
            45
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 17 miles in 6 hours and 20 minutes?",
        "options": [
            5.451028966656703,
            0.07157894736842106,
            2.2353240832337553,
            6.724419692775457
        ],
        "answer": 0.07157894736842106
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 flower vase, 86 chair, 59 empty boxes, 13 human beings, and 3 trees? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 159,
        "options": [
            100,
            72,
            160,
            159
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Green wants to buy a Phone. If his Palm size is 8cm, what available Phone may fit him?",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            3,
            12,
            6,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 71000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 394000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            697,
            180.203,
            793,
            701
        ],
        "answer": 180.203
    },
    {
        "question": "Davis wants to buy a Hand glove. If his Palm-size is 11cm, what available Hand glove may fit him?",
        "answer": 33,
        "options": [
            32,
            4,
            13,
            33
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of Jenkins increased from 549 per month to 898 per month while the salary of Perez increased from 944 to 991 and of Spencer increased from 409 to 766 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Spencer",
        "options": [
            "Jenkins",
            "Perez",
            "Spencer",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 12 fan, 97 tubelight, 86 empty boxes, 6 cat, and 10 trees? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 195,
        "options": [
            196,
            92,
            109,
            195
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 96 gallons. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 1/6 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            95,
            48,
            63,
            16.0
        ],
        "answer": 16.0
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Saturday and returns to the bank 1793days later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Sunday",
        "options": [
            "tuesday",
            "Sunday",
            "Wednesday",
            "Monday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 50 pints. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 3/9 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            59,
            63,
            16.67,
            85
        ],
        "answer": 16.67
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international cricket game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 10 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            17,
            9,
            8,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 16 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            21,
            22,
            -22,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 22
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 18 ohms and 46 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 3 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            3,
            46,
            18,
            64
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 42 ohms and 18 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 7 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            0,
            60,
            7,
            9,
            756
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 cycles, 61 broom, 13 empty boxes, 1 pigeons, and 6 snail? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            0,
            134,
            334,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If elephant can eat 167 grapes , how many grapes can a cat eat?",
        "answer": 76,
        "options": [
            167,
            76,
            243,
            91
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Thursday and returns to the bank 11years later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Monday",
        "options": [
            "Monday",
            "Thursday",
            "Sunday",
            "Sunday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 67 miles in 6 hours and 43 minutes?",
        "options": [
            7.07166986747159,
            9.583894294920611,
            9.975186104218361,
            7.243147091119206
        ],
        "answer": 9.975186104218361
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 3 bed, 59 flower vase, 12 refrigerator, 4 trees, and 14 human beings? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 31,
        "options": [
            85,
            89,
            31,
            87
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Diya began counting from 0. She skip-counted by twos. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            20,
            19,
            0,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 49 ohms and 27 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 10 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            0,
            1323,
            10,
            11,
            76
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 78. When the sun is at 43 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 92,
        "options": [
            4,
            92,
            62,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 broom, 10 sofa, 90 tubelight, 9 cat, and 12 algae spots? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            125,
            3,
            124,
            127
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If cow can eat 26 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a cat eat?",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            26,
            17,
            43,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Walker began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fours. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 300,
        "options": [
            301,
            300,
            302,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a child can eat 10 chocolates , how many chocolates can a ants eat?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            10,
            9,
            19,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 2 flower vase, 85 table, 85 pair of shoes, 3 cat, and 9 crows? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 172,
        "options": [
            87,
            173,
            88,
            172
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            11,
            -29,
            29,
            18
        ],
        "answer": 29
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 4 flower vase, 85 empty boxes, 30 mat, 9 crows, and 9 snail? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            19,
            39,
            89,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Gonzalez wants to put a picture in a frame.The frame is 3.651 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the picture?",
        "answer": 1.41,
        "options": [
            1.41,
            3.651,
            14.1,
            1.51
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 bed, 4 couch, 91 tubelight, 13 people, and 3 snail? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            6,
            37,
            81,
            83
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 10 years old in the year 1494.In his greatest win, he looted 543240569 of 3305885437 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins were actually present in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            -2762644868,
            3849126006,
            543240569,
            3305885437
        ],
        "answer": 3305885437
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Friday and returns to the bank 8months later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Sunday",
        "options": [
            "Wednesday",
            "Thursday",
            "Monday",
            "Sunday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Wilson wants to buy a Hand glove. If his Palm-size is 22cm, what available Hand glove may fit him?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            21,
            23,
            34,
            38
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "White wants to put a Card in a Envelope.The Envelope is 7.308 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Card?",
        "answer": 5.7,
        "options": [
            5.7,
            7.308,
            5.8,
            57.0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $8 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional half mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 27.3 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            289,
            60.6,
            283,
            399
        ],
        "answer": 60.6
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $92 to the charity and a total of $10890 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was tripled?",
        "options": [
            575,
            574,
            897,
            118
        ],
        "answer": 118
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 7 cycles, 45 sofa, 68 chair, 11 plants, and 8 bed bugs? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            84,
            50,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 7 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            5,
            0,
            6,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If cow can eat 11 chocolates , how many chocolates can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            11,
            5,
            16,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 23 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            15,
            -15,
            4,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $9 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional quarter mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 25.5 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            135,
            180,
            107.0,
            302
        ],
        "answer": 107.0
    },
    {
        "question": "Cunningham began counting from 0. She skip-counted by tens. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 440,
        "options": [
            0,
            441,
            440,
            442
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 7 fan, 3 cycles, 49 flower vase, 12 cat, and 4 human beings? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            38,
            12,
            26
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Angel wants to put a Pizza Box in a Refrigerator.The Refrigerator is 6.734 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Pizza Box?",
        "answer": 3.66,
        "options": [
            36.6,
            3.7600000000000002,
            3.66,
            6.734
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Griffin wants to buy a pair of socks. If his foot size is 37cm, what available pair of socks may fit him?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            38,
            43,
            41,
            44
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 2 flower vase, 85 table, 85 pair of shoes, 3 cat, and 9 crows? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 100,
        "options": [
            100,
            179,
            173,
            177
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 couch, 43 table, 77 mat, 13 cockroaches, and 6 fungi spots? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 134,
        "options": [
            135,
            90,
            134,
            57
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 3 couch, 77 flower vase, 90 empty boxes, 2 bed bugs, and 15 cat? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            17,
            92,
            18,
            80
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 3 couch, 77 flower vase, 90 empty boxes, 2 bed bugs, and 15 cat? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 170,
        "options": [
            170,
            171,
            92,
            80
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 79000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 174000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            997,
            900,
            454022.989,
            59
        ],
        "answer": 454022.989
    },
    {
        "question": "If man can eat 27 watermelon , how many watermelon can a dog eat?",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            27,
            8,
            35,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 tubelight, 57 fan, 67 broom, 5 snail, and 4 bed bugs? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 69,
        "options": [
            69,
            136,
            136,
            134
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $9 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-seventh mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 7.0 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            51.0,
            218,
            484,
            172
        ],
        "answer": 51.0
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            15,
            -26,
            26,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 cycles, 61 broom, 13 empty boxes, 1 pigeons, and 6 snail? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            17,
            7,
            68
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Thompson began counting from 0. She skip-counted by twos. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 104,
        "options": [
            104,
            106,
            0,
            105
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a child can eat 21 lemons , how many lemons can a ants eat?",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            21,
            11,
            32,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 flower vase, 95 mat, 40 empty boxes, 10 dog, and 14 cockroaches? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            50,
            108,
            25,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 9 feet by 7 feet?",
        "options": [
            2004,
            9072,
            1029,
            438
        ],
        "answer": 9072
    },
    {
        "question": "Hansen wants to buy a Hand glove. If his Palm-size is 29cm, what available Hand glove may fit him?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            24,
            6,
            43,
            27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Friday and returns to the bank 1007days later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Thursday",
        "options": [
            "Sunday",
            "Saturday",
            "Saturday",
            "Thursday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $7 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional half mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 26.1 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            196,
            319,
            343,
            57.2
        ],
        "answer": 57.2
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 9 feet by 1 feet?",
        "options": [
            3087,
            1296,
            2273,
            169
        ],
        "answer": 1296
    },
    {
        "question": "Gonzalez wants to buy a necklace. If his neck circumference is 17cm, what available necklace may fit him?",
        "answer": 33,
        "options": [
            19,
            6,
            24,
            33
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            20,
            14,
            6,
            -20
        ],
        "answer": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "Kabir began counting from 0. She skip-counted by threes. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 225,
        "options": [
            227,
            226,
            0,
            225
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Anvi began counting from 0. She skip-counted by eights. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 192,
        "options": [
            0,
            193,
            192,
            194
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international squash game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            -1,
            0,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Badminton game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            3,
            0,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            20,
            -30,
            30,
            10
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "Carter wants to put a picture in a frame.The frame is 7.049 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the picture?",
        "answer": 3.07,
        "options": [
            7.049,
            3.17,
            30.7,
            3.07
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 couch, 43 table, 77 mat, 13 cockroaches, and 6 fungi spots? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            100,
            24,
            144
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 24 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            17,
            23,
            6,
            -23
        ],
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 5 years old in the year 1461.In his greatest win, he looted 944796134 of 3298058599 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins are remaining in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            4242854733,
            3298058599,
            2353262465,
            944796134
        ],
        "answer": 2353262465
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 24 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            17,
            23,
            6,
            -23
        ],
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $2 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-tenth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 13.6 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            336,
            475,
            499,
            115.4
        ],
        "answer": 115.4
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Table-Tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            1,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Badminton game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            3,
            2,
            0,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a tuesday and returns to the bank 4years later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Saturday",
        "options": [
            "tuesday",
            "tuesday",
            "Wednesday",
            "Saturday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 52000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 666000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            359,
            794,
            78078.078,
            622
        ],
        "answer": 78078.078
    },
    {
        "question": "Bailey began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fours. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 164,
        "options": [
            165,
            166,
            0,
            164
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 40 ohms and 39 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 5 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            5,
            79,
            40,
            39
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $6 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-sixth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 36.9 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            393,
            491,
            247,
            221.4
        ],
        "answer": 221.4
    },
    {
        "question": "Sara wants to put a Statue in a River.The River is 4.74 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Statue?",
        "answer": 1.83,
        "options": [
            1.83,
            1.9300000000000002,
            4.74,
            18.3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 4 couch, 18 tubelight, 51 broom, 14 snail, and 9 cat? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            43,
            216,
            144,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Table-Tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            0,
            3,
            -1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 20 miles in 8 hours and 27 minutes?",
        "options": [
            7.446097563808226,
            3.6421517824078995,
            0.03944773175542406,
            5.653285537856459
        ],
        "answer": 0.03944773175542406
    },
    {
        "question": "If snail can eat 16 apples , how many apples can a giraffee eat?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            16,
            20,
            36,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international volley ball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            5,
            4,
            5,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 16 years old in the year 1475.In his greatest win, he looted 288747952 of 6728820684 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1808,
            1823,
            1459,
            1505
        ],
        "answer": 1459
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 flower vase, 42 empty boxes, 68 bed, 12 pigeons, and 15 cockroaches? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 27,
        "options": [
            28,
            80,
            50,
            27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 cycles, 61 broom, 13 empty boxes, 1 pigeons, and 6 snail? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 88,
        "options": [
            89,
            88,
            75,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Table-Tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            4,
            1,
            2,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If pigeon can eat 6 cake , how many cake can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            6,
            9,
            15,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 39 miles in 4 hours and 4 minutes?",
        "options": [
            4.013822969440263,
            4.026363269914716,
            5.479070970474272,
            0.1598360655737705
        ],
        "answer": 0.1598360655737705
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international footbal game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 8 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            1,
            16,
            5,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 14 years old in the year 1507.In his greatest win, he looted 590161739 of 4423182681 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1824,
            1766,
            1493,
            1658
        ],
        "answer": 1493
    },
    {
        "question": "Parker wants to buy a a ring. If his finger circumference is 32cm, what available a ring may fit him?",
        "answer": 35,
        "options": [
            18,
            35,
            9,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Friday and returns to the bank 12months later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Friday",
        "options": [
            "Thursday",
            "Friday",
            "Thursday",
            "Sunday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If man can eat 26 lemons , how many lemons can a ants eat?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            26,
            23,
            49,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Vivaan wants to put a fruit in a basket.The basket is 5.06 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the fruit?",
        "answer": 3.86,
        "options": [
            3.96,
            38.6,
            3.86,
            5.06
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Romero wants to buy a pair of shorts. If his waist size is 6cm, what available pair of shorts may fit him?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            2,
            3,
            9,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Payne wants to put a picture in a frame.The frame is 3.267 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the picture?",
        "answer": 1.92,
        "options": [
            2.02,
            3.267,
            1.92,
            19.2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 18000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 74000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            962,
            636,
            779,
            243.243
        ],
        "answer": 243.243
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -25,
            23,
            2,
            25
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $44 to the charity and a total of $4632 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was doubled?",
        "options": [
            425,
            392,
            105,
            468
        ],
        "answer": 105
    },
    {
        "question": "If giraffee can eat 24 apples , how many apples can a cat eat?",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            24,
            5,
            29,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Palmer began counting from 0. She skip-counted by nine's. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 846,
        "options": [
            847,
            0,
            846,
            848
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Gray wants to buy a Belt. If his waist size is 5cm, what available Belt may fit him?",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            16,
            17,
            10,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 59000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 163000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            853,
            770,
            275,
            361963.19
        ],
        "answer": 361963.19
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $10 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-tenth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 28.2 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            302,
            285,
            371,
            254.8
        ],
        "answer": 254.8
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $4 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-sixth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 49.0 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            391,
            300,
            358,
            292.0
        ],
        "answer": 292.0
    },
    {
        "question": "Aarush began counting from 0. She skip-counted by six's. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 282,
        "options": [
            282,
            0,
            284,
            283
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Rogers wants to buy a pair of pants. If his waist size is 20cm, what available pair of pants may fit him?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            42,
            28,
            21,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Carter wants to buy a Hand glove. If his Palm-size is 30cm, what available Hand glove may fit him?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            40,
            25,
            29,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 couch, 74 cycles, 90 empty boxes, 5 bed bugs, and 14 snail? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 172,
        "options": [
            172,
            95,
            173,
            82
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 6 pair of shoes, 88 couch, 24 tubelight, 13 dog, and 4 plants? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            15,
            99,
            74,
            72
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 32000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 534000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            958,
            840,
            63,
            59925.094
        ],
        "answer": 59925.094
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 11 ohms and 19 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 16 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            30,
            19,
            209,
            16,
            39
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 5 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            19,
            9,
            3,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $3 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional half mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 10.6 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            207,
            161,
            22.2,
            390
        ],
        "answer": 22.2
    },
    {
        "question": "Anya wants to buy a cap. If his head circumference is 14cm, what available cap may fit him?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            39,
            38,
            30,
            21
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If pigeon can eat 11 chocolates , how many chocolates can a giraffee eat?",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            11,
            15,
            26,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 88. When the sun is at 156 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 103,
        "options": [
            26,
            37,
            76,
            103
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            18,
            -26,
            8,
            26
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "If ants can eat 9 watermelon , how many watermelon can a snail eat?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            9,
            28,
            37,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Advik wants to buy a shirt. If his body size is 34cm, what available shirt may fit him?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            37,
            6,
            3,
            40
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Thursday and returns to the bank 7months later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Friday",
        "options": [
            "Thursday",
            "Saturday",
            "Monday",
            "Friday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 16 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            16,
            6,
            10,
            -16
        ],
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            3,
            0,
            1,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 22. When the sun is at 93 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            52,
            10,
            44,
            93
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 2 mat, 53 table, 8 flower vase, 1 bed bugs, and 10 dog? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 25,
        "options": [
            71,
            68,
            25,
            65
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Aaradhya wants to buy a pair of pants. If his waist size is 35cm, what available pair of pants may fit him?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            25,
            35,
            15,
            38
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international squash game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            2,
            1,
            0,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Shanaya wants to buy a hoodie. If his chest size is 9cm, what available hoodie may fit him?",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            17,
            12,
            29,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 78000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 326000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            668,
            239.264,
            806,
            612
        ],
        "answer": 239.264
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 20 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -30,
            11,
            30,
            19
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 33 ohms and 19 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 7 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            7,
            52,
            19,
            33
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a tuesday and returns to the bank 7851days later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Saturday",
        "options": [
            "Wednesday",
            "Saturday",
            "Friday",
            "Monday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 98 miles in 7 hours and 34 minutes?",
        "options": [
            1.9780658093343482,
            8.80990126055579,
            0.21585903083700442,
            6.171952748538684
        ],
        "answer": 0.21585903083700442
    },
    {
        "question": "Moore wants to buy a necklace. If his neck circumference is 28cm, what available necklace may fit him?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            28,
            43,
            11,
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jenkins wants to buy a shirt. If his body size is 21cm, what available shirt may fit him?",
        "answer": 26,
        "options": [
            26,
            11,
            25,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 4 broom, 73 cycles, 61 mat, 14 bed bugs, and 9 cat? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            23,
            75,
            77,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 52 miles in 3 hours and 26 minutes?",
        "options": [
            2.164606102732726,
            7.569591615261878,
            2.1567909484542596,
            0.4038834951456311
        ],
        "answer": 0.4038834951456311
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 12 broom, 32 flower vase, 25 mat, 13 human beings, and 13 people? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 72,
        "options": [
            0,
            262,
            309,
            72
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international golf game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            -1,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Tucker wants to buy a Belt. If his waist size is 14cm, what available Belt may fit him?",
        "answer": 32,
        "options": [
            27,
            32,
            5,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $6 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-tenth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 39.8 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            355.2,
            457,
            473,
            474
        ],
        "answer": 355.2
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international squash game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            2,
            -1,
            0,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            1,
            4,
            1,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Badminton game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            2,
            3,
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If cat can eat 6 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a elephant eat?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            6,
            16,
            22,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 20 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -30,
            11,
            30,
            19
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "If elephant can eat 5 cake , how many cake can a man eat?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            5,
            4,
            9,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -30,
            13,
            17,
            30
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Ice Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 4 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            1,
            4,
            5,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international volley ball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            5,
            4,
            9,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $6 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-fifth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 8.3 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            434,
            287,
            432,
            35.2
        ],
        "answer": 35.2
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 sofa, 82 tubelight, 76 mat, 7 plants, and 6 bed bugs? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 13,
        "options": [
            13,
            83,
            93,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 2 mat, 53 table, 8 flower vase, 1 bed bugs, and 10 dog? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 63,
        "options": [
            64,
            55,
            63,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -30,
            13,
            17,
            30
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 97 pints. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 4/9 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            74,
            72,
            12,
            43.11
        ],
        "answer": 43.11
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 3 mat, 74 broom, 79 flower vase, 11 algae spots, and 15 cockroaches? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            164,
            130,
            143,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 20 years old in the year 1564.In his greatest win, he looted 818663478 of 5951938350 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1673,
            1544,
            1722,
            1709
        ],
        "answer": 1544
    },
    {
        "question": "If pigeon can eat 8 watermelon , how many watermelon can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            8,
            20,
            28,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international basketball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 5 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            1,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 bed, 4 couch, 91 tubelight, 13 people, and 3 snail? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            18,
            57,
            126
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 4 feet by 3 feet?",
        "options": [
            9498,
            5584,
            1728,
            8290
        ],
        "answer": 1728
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $82 to the charity and a total of $14692 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was quadrupled?",
        "options": [
            179,
            525,
            735,
            48
        ],
        "answer": 179
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international volley ball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            2,
            5,
            9,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Friday and returns to the bank 3years later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Monday",
        "options": [
            "Wednesday",
            "Monday",
            "Sunday",
            "Thursday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A family is going on a vacation to Chicago in a bus. There were 9 men, 5 women, 5 children of less than 10 years, 6 old people of age above 60 years.How many of the people can drive??",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            112,
            25,
            0,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Scott wants to buy a Hand glove. If his Palm-size is 27cm, what available Hand glove may fit him?",
        "answer": 33,
        "options": [
            30,
            29,
            6,
            33
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 sofa, 16 bed, 93 pair of shoes, 9 algae spots, and 10 dog? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            131,
            23,
            77
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            4,
            28,
            24,
            -28
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 41000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 409000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            168,
            194,
            554,
            100.244
        ],
        "answer": 100.244
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 12 sofa, 28 bed, 16 empty boxes, 7 trees, and 13 crows? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            73,
            4,
            22
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 46 pints. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 1/8 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            26,
            5.75,
            98,
            56
        ],
        "answer": 5.75
    },
    {
        "question": "A family is going on a vacation to Chicago in a bus. There were 10 men, 8 women, 3 children of less than 10 years, 6 old people of age above 60 years.How many of the people can drive??",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            111,
            27,
            0,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 16 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            16,
            6,
            10,
            -16
        ],
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 22 ohms and 24 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 10 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            46,
            22,
            10,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 23 miles in 7 hours and 19 minutes?",
        "options": [
            9.430229261191522,
            0.05239179954441914,
            7.557951955623222,
            2.166348801875079
        ],
        "answer": 0.05239179954441914
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Ice Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 4 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            0,
            12,
            6,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 14 years old in the year 1810.In his greatest win, he looted 523242202 of 9660815474 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1796,
            1804,
            1893,
            1826
        ],
        "answer": 1796
    },
    {
        "question": "Snyder wants to put a chocolate in a jar.The jar is 9.958 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the chocolate?",
        "answer": 7.45,
        "options": [
            7.55,
            7.45,
            74.5,
            9.958
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international golf game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            1,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Aaradhya wants to buy a pair of socks. If his foot size is 35cm, what available pair of socks may fit him?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            21,
            42,
            14,
            29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -25,
            23,
            2,
            25
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 fan, 14 tubelight, 29 broom, 13 cat, and 14 pigeons? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 48,
        "options": [
            48,
            49,
            19,
            42
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 12 sofa, 28 bed, 16 empty boxes, 7 trees, and 13 crows? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 56,
        "options": [
            23,
            57,
            40,
            56
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 10 feet by 7 feet?",
        "options": [
            5195,
            8924,
            10080,
            7209
        ],
        "answer": 10080
    },
    {
        "question": "Parker wants to buy a pair of pants. If his waist size is 15cm, what available pair of pants may fit him?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            2,
            14,
            9,
            38
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $10 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-fifth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 35.6 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            169,
            406,
            225,
            148.4
        ],
        "answer": 148.4
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 12 broom, 32 flower vase, 25 mat, 13 human beings, and 13 people? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            6,
            81,
            85,
            92
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Bell began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fours. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 120,
        "options": [
            0,
            120,
            122,
            121
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A family is going on a vacation to Chicago in a bus. There were 9 men, 9 women, 8 children of less than 10 years, 4 old people of age above 60 years.How many of the people can drive??",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            117,
            30,
            0,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 2 tubelight, 69 flower vase, 77 broom, 8 human beings, and 7 fungi spots? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            5,
            22,
            33,
            31
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 1 feet by 10 feet?",
        "options": [
            5827,
            453,
            1440,
            8824
        ],
        "answer": 1440
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 mat, 10 table, 90 chair, 6 trees, and 4 fungi spots? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 54,
        "options": [
            332,
            54,
            258,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            4,
            28,
            24,
            -28
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Friday and returns to the bank 9934days later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Saturday",
        "options": [
            "Friday",
            "Friday",
            "Sunday",
            "Saturday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If man can eat 16 lemons , how many lemons can a giraffee eat?",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            16,
            18,
            34,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international rugby game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 11 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            0,
            3,
            28,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 empty boxes, 37 chair, 82 refrigerator, 8 cockroaches, and 5 dog? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            108,
            81,
            35
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Monday and returns to the bank 6375days later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Saturday",
        "options": [
            "Friday",
            "tuesday",
            "Saturday",
            "Sunday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            15,
            -26,
            26,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $68 to the charity and a total of $12549 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was tripled?",
        "options": [
            184,
            61,
            431,
            309
        ],
        "answer": 184
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 bed, 11 cycles, 61 empty boxes, 6 crows, and 11 pigeons? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 59,
        "options": [
            59,
            0,
            260,
            160
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 cycles, 61 broom, 13 empty boxes, 1 pigeons, and 6 snail? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 53,
        "options": [
            53,
            95,
            93,
            90
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international cricket game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 10 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            0,
            22,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If cat can eat 88 grapes , how many grapes can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 187,
        "options": [
            88,
            187,
            275,
            99
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $3 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-fifth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 33.0 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            169,
            484,
            131.0,
            445
        ],
        "answer": 131.0
    },
    {
        "question": "Kennedy began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fives. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 95,
        "options": [
            96,
            97,
            0,
            95
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $7 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-sixth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 5.7 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            139,
            212,
            35.2,
            171
        ],
        "answer": 35.2
    },
    {
        "question": "Stewart wants to buy a a ring. If his finger circumference is 28cm, what available a ring may fit him?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            38,
            42,
            28,
            37
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Evans wants to buy a cap. If his head circumference is 10cm, what available cap may fit him?",
        "answer": 25,
        "options": [
            11,
            5,
            25,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Reyes wants to put a Statue in a River.The River is 9.882 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Statue?",
        "answer": 6.22,
        "options": [
            9.882,
            6.319999999999999,
            6.22,
            62.199999999999996
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $8 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional half mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 29.7 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            92,
            65.4,
            113,
            208
        ],
        "answer": 65.4
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 tubelight, 57 fan, 67 broom, 5 snail, and 4 bed bugs? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            41,
            3,
            46,
            58
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a tuesday and returns to the bank 9months later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Sunday",
        "options": [
            "Thursday",
            "tuesday",
            "Sunday",
            "Saturday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 27 ohms and 17 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 3 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            3,
            44,
            17,
            27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Baker wants to buy a pair of socks. If his foot size is 5cm, what available pair of socks may fit him?",
        "answer": 34,
        "options": [
            26,
            26,
            18,
            34
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 31 ohms and 45 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 9 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 27,
        "options": [
            9,
            36,
            1395,
            45,
            76
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 mat, 46 refrigerator, 56 pair of shoes, 14 pigeons, and 10 crows? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 58,
        "options": [
            0,
            58,
            162,
            341
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 60 gallons. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 4/9 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            20,
            72,
            26.67,
            41
        ],
        "answer": 26.67
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 refrigerator, 47 empty boxes, 12 bed, 2 cat, and 5 bed bugs? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            8,
            7,
            14,
            55
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 6 years old in the year 1162.In his greatest win, he looted 35569691 of 175878297 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1156,
            1858,
            1223,
            1849
        ],
        "answer": 1156
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international volley ball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 6 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            0,
            10,
            -1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 couch, 43 table, 77 mat, 13 cockroaches, and 6 fungi spots? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 19,
        "options": [
            20,
            90,
            57,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 2 tubelight, 69 flower vase, 77 broom, 8 human beings, and 7 fungi spots? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            158,
            150,
            28,
            156
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Gomez wants to buy a pair of shorts. If his waist size is 10cm, what available pair of shorts may fit him?",
        "answer": 13,
        "options": [
            13,
            3,
            8,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If giraffee can eat 28 apples , how many apples can a snail eat?",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            28,
            11,
            39,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Palmer began counting from 0. She skip-counted by threes. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 270,
        "options": [
            271,
            0,
            270,
            272
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 20 years old in the year 1374.In his greatest win, he looted 420577844 of 3980479762 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1577,
            1431,
            1354,
            1598
        ],
        "answer": 1354
    },
    {
        "question": "Kennedy earns $7 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $4 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Kennedy was paid $3128, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            320,
            325,
            464,
            307
        ],
        "answer": 320
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a tuesday and returns to the bank 1487days later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Friday",
        "options": [
            "Sunday",
            "Thursday",
            "Friday",
            "Saturday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $10 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-eighth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 44.3 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            444,
            479,
            357,
            356.4
        ],
        "answer": 356.4
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 flower vase, 86 chair, 59 empty boxes, 13 human beings, and 3 trees? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 58,
        "options": [
            58,
            160,
            162,
            166
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ishaan wants to put a car in a car parking space.The car parking space is 7.895 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the car?",
        "answer": 3.7,
        "options": [
            3.7,
            3.8000000000000003,
            37.0,
            7.895
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 12 fan, 97 tubelight, 86 empty boxes, 6 cat, and 10 trees? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            16,
            109,
            92,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Badminton game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            2,
            1,
            3,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 41000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 410000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            86,
            0.1,
            406,
            992
        ],
        "answer": 0.1
    },
    {
        "question": "If ants can eat 12 apples , how many apples can a cat eat?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            12,
            24,
            36,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 3000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 534000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            303,
            679,
            0.006,
            378
        ],
        "answer": 0.006
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 24 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            17,
            23,
            6,
            -23
        ],
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of Eva increased from 597 per month to 689 per month while the salary of Reyansh increased from 611 to 843 and of Warren increased from 374 to 941 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Warren",
        "options": [
            "Eva",
            "Reyansh",
            "Warren",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ramos wants to buy a pair of shorts. If his waist size is 36cm, what available pair of shorts may fit him?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            37,
            11,
            10,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 53000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 865000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            652,
            61271.676,
            241,
            24
        ],
        "answer": 61271.676
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 19 years old in the year 1804.In his greatest win, he looted 193522271 of 1957937504 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins were actually present in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            1957937504,
            193522271,
            2151459775,
            -1764415233
        ],
        "answer": 1957937504
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            4,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Advaith wants to buy a pair of shoes. If his foot size is 32cm, what available pair of shoes may fit him?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            10,
            3,
            41,
            37
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international footbal game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            11,
            21,
            0,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 tubelight, 57 fan, 67 broom, 5 snail, and 4 bed bugs? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            10,
            72,
            9,
            62
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 19 years old in the year 1308.In his greatest win, he looted 603538598 of 1360988150 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1474,
            1289,
            1747,
            1731
        ],
        "answer": 1289
    },
    {
        "question": "Arnav wants to put a fruit in a basket.The basket is 3.75 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the fruit?",
        "answer": 1.49,
        "options": [
            1.59,
            3.75,
            1.49,
            14.9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 3 feet by 5 feet?",
        "options": [
            2160,
            3079,
            7796,
            5643
        ],
        "answer": 2160
    },
    {
        "question": "Kennedy wants to buy a pair of pants. If his waist size is 6cm, what available pair of pants may fit him?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            39,
            37,
            8,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 55 miles in 10 hours and 57 minutes?",
        "options": [
            6.792735182481107,
            4.719823225397647,
            0.1339421613394216,
            3.0918317314257138
        ],
        "answer": 0.1339421613394216
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 51000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 714000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            43,
            71428.571,
            799,
            717
        ],
        "answer": 71428.571
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 flower vase, 46 refrigerator, 87 couch, 2 snail, and 14 bed bugs? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            41,
            128,
            43,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hayes began counting from 0. She skip-counted by twos. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 176,
        "options": [
            176,
            0,
            178,
            177
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 9 years old in the year 1316.In his greatest win, he looted 307527889 of 7225972018 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins are remaining in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            7533499907,
            7225972018,
            307527889,
            6918444129
        ],
        "answer": 6918444129
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Sunday and returns to the bank 3140days later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Thursday",
        "options": [
            "Wednesday",
            "Sunday",
            "tuesday",
            "Thursday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 34 miles in 6 hours and 37 minutes?",
        "options": [
            2.4073575534016296,
            5.326384340225164,
            4.063337598105353,
            0.08564231738035265
        ],
        "answer": 0.08564231738035265
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Wednesday and returns to the bank 12years later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Monday",
        "options": [
            "Saturday",
            "Monday",
            "tuesday",
            "Sunday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 tubelight, 41 refrigerator, 93 mat, 8 cockroaches, and 8 human beings? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            101,
            16,
            51,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 79000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 930000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            84.946,
            569,
            290,
            980
        ],
        "answer": 84.946
    },
    {
        "question": "A family is going on a vacation to Chicago in a bus. There were 6 men, 9 women, 4 children of less than 10 years, 4 old people of age above 60 years.How many of the people can drive??",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            104,
            23,
            0,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Bryant wants to buy a shirt. If his body size is 40cm, what available shirt may fit him?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            45,
            41,
            45,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 4 feet by 3 feet?",
        "options": [
            6801,
            6317,
            391,
            1728
        ],
        "answer": 1728
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 66000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 588000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            6,
            112244.898,
            451,
            854
        ],
        "answer": 112244.898
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international basketball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 5 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            3,
            9,
            4,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Peterson wants to buy a Phone. If his Palm size is 8cm, what available Phone may fit him?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            20,
            23,
            12,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Spencer wants to buy a pair of shorts. If his waist size is 19cm, what available pair of shorts may fit him?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            8,
            16,
            16,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 55. When the sun is at 143 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 91,
        "options": [
            47,
            13,
            41,
            91
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Dunn wants to buy a necklace. If his neck circumference is 21cm, what available necklace may fit him?",
        "answer": 25,
        "options": [
            25,
            19,
            3,
            22
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ritvik wants to buy a pair of socks. If his foot size is 7cm, what available pair of socks may fit him?",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            10,
            29,
            23,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hayes wants to buy a shirt. If his body size is 21cm, what available shirt may fit him?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            41,
            43,
            28,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 empty boxes, 20 bed, 15 refrigerator, 8 dog, and 7 pigeons? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 48,
        "options": [
            48,
            237,
            0,
            341
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 2 tubelight, 69 flower vase, 77 broom, 8 human beings, and 7 fungi spots? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 107,
        "options": [
            344,
            0,
            107,
            260
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A family is going on a vacation to Chicago in a bus. There were 8 men, 9 women, 3 children of less than 10 years, 7 old people of age above 60 years.How many of the people can drive??",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            105,
            27,
            0,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 sofa, 16 bed, 93 pair of shoes, 9 algae spots, and 10 dog? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 114,
        "options": [
            115,
            21,
            102,
            114
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            18,
            -26,
            8,
            26
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 tubelight, 41 refrigerator, 93 mat, 8 cockroaches, and 8 human beings? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 87,
        "options": [
            374,
            0,
            331,
            87
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 15 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -26,
            19,
            7,
            26
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 6 years old in the year 1876.In his greatest win, he looted 179891474 of 3709546021 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1879,
            1872,
            1870,
            1899
        ],
        "answer": 1870
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 9 feet by 1 feet?",
        "options": [
            7937,
            5057,
            1296,
            2188
        ],
        "answer": 1296
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 couch, 43 table, 77 mat, 13 cockroaches, and 6 fungi spots? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 19,
        "options": [
            57,
            20,
            90,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 39 ohms and 31 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 4 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            39,
            70,
            31,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Ice Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 6 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            3,
            0,
            2,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a child can eat 65 grapes , how many grapes can a man eat?",
        "answer": 197,
        "options": [
            65,
            197,
            262,
            132
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Burns wants to buy a hoodie. If his chest size is 34cm, what available hoodie may fit him?",
        "answer": 35,
        "options": [
            30,
            35,
            13,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international basketball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 3 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            9,
            2,
            3,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 16 years old in the year 1475.In his greatest win, he looted 288747952 of 6728820684 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1808,
            1823,
            1459,
            1505
        ],
        "answer": 1459
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 40 gallons. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 2/8 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            60,
            62,
            10.0,
            15
        ],
        "answer": 10.0
    },
    {
        "question": "Ward wants to put a car in a road.The road is 3.27 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the car?",
        "answer": 1.3,
        "options": [
            1.3,
            3.27,
            1.4000000000000001,
            13.0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 mat, 10 table, 90 chair, 6 trees, and 4 fungi spots? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            24,
            96,
            5,
            66
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Table-Tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            0,
            3,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Walker began counting from 0. She skip-counted by sevens. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 483,
        "options": [
            0,
            485,
            484,
            483
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Davis wants to put a Card in a Envelope.The Envelope is 8.803 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Card?",
        "answer": 2.08,
        "options": [
            20.8,
            2.08,
            8.803,
            2.18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $6 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-tenth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 16.3 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            143.7,
            405,
            206,
            491
        ],
        "answer": 143.7
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 2 mat, 53 table, 8 flower vase, 1 bed bugs, and 10 dog? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            73,
            43,
            40,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Aaradhya earns $6 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $4 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Aaradhya was paid $4514, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            188,
            338,
            396,
            491
        ],
        "answer": 491
    },
    {
        "question": "Rivera earns $11 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $5 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Rivera was paid $3259, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            234,
            253,
            347,
            319
        ],
        "answer": 234
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 7 flower vase, 39 cycles, 36 tubelight, 10 cockroaches, and 10 human beings? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 82,
        "options": [
            82,
            46,
            46,
            83
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Boxing game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            0,
            2,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 25. When the sun is at 169 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 32,
        "options": [
            3,
            19,
            14,
            32
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 40 pints. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 5/7 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            10,
            75,
            26,
            28.57
        ],
        "answer": 28.57
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 7 feet by 1 feet?",
        "options": [
            5226,
            9944,
            1047,
            1008
        ],
        "answer": 1008
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 6 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            7,
            -17,
            10,
            17
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 90 miles in 10 hours and 34 minutes?",
        "options": [
            8.517350157728707,
            2.5147302035120376,
            2.55450438686172,
            4.180480809584532
        ],
        "answer": 8.517350157728707
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international rugby game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 10 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 13,
        "options": [
            3,
            18,
            13,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 19. When the sun is at 35 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 68,
        "options": [
            68,
            11,
            7,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Long wants to buy a necklace. If his neck circumference is 27cm, what available necklace may fit him?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            43,
            41,
            33,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Shaurya began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fives. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 330,
        "options": [
            331,
            330,
            0,
            332
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 39 ohms and 31 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 10 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            39,
            70,
            10,
            31
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 sofa, 82 tubelight, 76 mat, 7 plants, and 6 bed bugs? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 169,
        "options": [
            169,
            170,
            93,
            83
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "King wants to buy a hat. If his head circumference is 8cm, what available hat may fit him?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            7,
            41,
            4,
            26
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 7 fan, 3 cycles, 49 flower vase, 12 cat, and 4 human beings? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 59,
        "options": [
            59,
            10,
            61,
            60
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 61 miles in 8 hours and 20 minutes?",
        "options": [
            4.431332318905852,
            0.122,
            3.652173874274649,
            2.3579709058348137
        ],
        "answer": 0.122
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 flower vase, 86 chair, 59 empty boxes, 13 human beings, and 3 trees? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            16,
            172,
            99,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 78000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 185000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            14,
            714,
            0.422,
            192
        ],
        "answer": 0.422
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kph if you travel 35 miles in 10 hours and 11 minutes?",
        "options": [
            5.499181669394435,
            6.007055045096954,
            8.257662250331483,
            2.316933349283437
        ],
        "answer": 5.499181669394435
    },
    {
        "question": "If pigeon can eat 4 cake , how many cake can a dog eat?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            4,
            9,
            13,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $10 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-eighth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 15.3 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            330,
            124.4,
            157,
            341
        ],
        "answer": 124.4
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            15,
            -26,
            26,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $2 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional half mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 20.1 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            139,
            359,
            450,
            40.2
        ],
        "answer": 40.2
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 5 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -25,
            16,
            25,
            9
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $10 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-seventh mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 23.1 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            164.7,
            248,
            345,
            355
        ],
        "answer": 164.7
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 10 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            1,
            2,
            1,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 3 bed, 59 flower vase, 12 refrigerator, 4 trees, and 14 human beings? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            19,
            62,
            16,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 cycles, 61 broom, 13 empty boxes, 1 pigeons, and 6 snail? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            64,
            2,
            90,
            90
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Prisha wants to buy a Phone. If his Palm size is 29cm, what available Phone may fit him?",
        "answer": 33,
        "options": [
            8,
            33,
            11,
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international volley ball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 3 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            3,
            2,
            12,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If dog can eat 26 watermelon , how many watermelon can a snail eat?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            26,
            16,
            42,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $22 to the charity and a total of $10152 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was quadrupled?",
        "options": [
            815,
            797,
            461,
            881
        ],
        "answer": 461
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 7 cycles, 45 sofa, 68 chair, 11 plants, and 8 bed bugs? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 75,
        "options": [
            125,
            75,
            123,
            130
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            15,
            -26,
            26,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 2 mat, 53 table, 8 flower vase, 1 bed bugs, and 10 dog? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            11,
            12,
            9,
            55
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Russell wants to buy a Hand glove. If his Palm-size is 38cm, what available Hand glove may fit him?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            12,
            15,
            16,
            45
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 6 years old in the year 1443.In his greatest win, he looted 904043050 of 8220025366 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins are remaining in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            9124068416,
            8220025366,
            7315982316,
            904043050
        ],
        "answer": 7315982316
    },
    {
        "question": "Murphy wants to put a car in a road.The road is 4.756 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the car?",
        "answer": 2.87,
        "options": [
            2.97,
            2.87,
            4.756,
            28.700000000000003
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 10 years old in the year 1425.In his greatest win, he looted 652651653 of 6628306191 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1602,
            1415,
            1777,
            1885
        ],
        "answer": 1415
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 3 mat, 74 broom, 79 flower vase, 11 algae spots, and 15 cockroaches? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 156,
        "options": [
            157,
            90,
            156,
            77
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international baseball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 3 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            6,
            3,
            15,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Advaith wants to put a luggage in a car trunk.The car trunk is 5.521 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the luggage?",
        "answer": 3.81,
        "options": [
            5.521,
            38.1,
            3.91,
            3.81
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 12 broom, 32 flower vase, 25 mat, 13 human beings, and 13 people? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            65,
            81,
            17,
            45
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Navya began counting from 0. She skip-counted by eights. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 472,
        "options": [
            0,
            474,
            472,
            473
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international footbal game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 6 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            8,
            7,
            22,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 flower vase, 86 chair, 59 empty boxes, 13 human beings, and 3 trees? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 159,
        "options": [
            100,
            160,
            72,
            159
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Peters wants to put a car in a car parking space.The car parking space is 9.886 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the car?",
        "answer": 6.38,
        "options": [
            6.38,
            63.8,
            6.4799999999999995,
            9.886
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If pigeon can eat 23 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a dog eat?",
        "answer": 25,
        "options": [
            23,
            25,
            48,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hoffman wants to buy a hat. If his head circumference is 39cm, what available hat may fit him?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            37,
            43,
            28,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Reyansh began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fives. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 70,
        "options": [
            0,
            70,
            71,
            72
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 48 ohms and 19 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 16 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 19,
        "options": [
            67,
            912,
            16,
            35,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Peters began counting from 0. She skip-counted by sevens. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 511,
        "options": [
            511,
            513,
            0,
            512
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 5 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -25,
            16,
            25,
            9
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 17 years old in the year 1153.In his greatest win, he looted 821783639 of 3080400799 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1614,
            1136,
            1440,
            1840
        ],
        "answer": 1136
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Boxing game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            0,
            1,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 71000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 765000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            10,
            92.81,
            35,
            187
        ],
        "answer": 92.81
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 23 ohms and 50 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 9 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            9,
            0,
            5,
            1150,
            73
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international baseball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            2,
            9,
            8,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Campbell wants to buy a pair of socks. If his foot size is 20cm, what available pair of socks may fit him?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            16,
            44,
            43,
            40
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kph if you travel 58 miles in 4 hours and 60 minutes?",
        "options": [
            7.153244885600193,
            18.560000000000002,
            6.220704833628945,
            7.9439520721355485
        ],
        "answer": 18.560000000000002
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 9 years old in the year 1447.In his greatest win, he looted 714664535 of 4224985971 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1490,
            1502,
            1624,
            1438
        ],
        "answer": 1438
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $40 to the charity and a total of $6762 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was tripled?",
        "options": [
            865,
            847,
            437,
            169
        ],
        "answer": 169
    },
    {
        "question": "Miller wants to buy a pair of shoes. If his foot size is 29cm, what available pair of shoes may fit him?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            41,
            25,
            30,
            32
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Akshara wants to buy a Phone. If his Palm size is 36cm, what available Phone may fit him?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            22,
            28,
            44,
            22
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            3,
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Shanaya wants to buy a shirt. If his body size is 39cm, what available shirt may fit him?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            9,
            44,
            5,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 16 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            21,
            22,
            -22,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 22
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 87. When the sun is at 165 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 103,
        "options": [
            77,
            57,
            83,
            103
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 39 gallons. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 3/10 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            71,
            11,
            11.7,
            43
        ],
        "answer": 11.7
    },
    {
        "question": "Sanchez wants to buy a hat. If his head circumference is 12cm, what available hat may fit him?",
        "answer": 33,
        "options": [
            18,
            16,
            33,
            28
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Phillips wants to put a car in a car parking space.The car parking space is 6.959 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the car?",
        "answer": 4.1,
        "options": [
            4.199999999999999,
            6.959,
            41.0,
            4.1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $10 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-sixth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 39.0 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            379,
            238.0,
            359,
            344
        ],
        "answer": 238.0
    },
    {
        "question": "If ants can eat 12 lemons , how many lemons can a cow eat?",
        "answer": 25,
        "options": [
            12,
            25,
            37,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $9 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-seventh mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 38.4 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            292,
            451,
            410,
            270.8
        ],
        "answer": 270.8
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 refrigerator, 23 empty boxes, 83 couch, 7 cat, and 9 algae spots? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 116,
        "options": [
            117,
            33,
            90,
            116
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 mat, 10 table, 90 chair, 6 trees, and 4 fungi spots? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 105,
        "options": [
            106,
            96,
            15,
            105
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 68 miles in 5 hours and 19 minutes?",
        "options": [
            1.3280712989609578,
            4.201283251862437,
            0.34106583072100316,
            5.522691828315141
        ],
        "answer": 0.34106583072100316
    },
    {
        "question": "Ortiz wants to buy a shirt. If his body size is 5cm, what available shirt may fit him?",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            17,
            8,
            9,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 8 feet by 7 feet?",
        "options": [
            1876,
            8064,
            9248,
            7670
        ],
        "answer": 8064
    },
    {
        "question": "Johnson wants to put a Pizza Box in a Refrigerator.The Refrigerator is 5.46 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Pizza Box?",
        "answer": 2.73,
        "options": [
            2.83,
            5.46,
            27.3,
            2.73
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If man can eat 13 lemons , how many lemons can a ants eat?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            13,
            9,
            22,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Mitchell wants to buy a shirt. If his body size is 34cm, what available shirt may fit him?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            34,
            42,
            11,
            34
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 42 ohms and 18 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 3 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            60,
            18,
            42,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 12 ohms and 5 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 2 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            12,
            5,
            2,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 5 feet by 4 feet?",
        "options": [
            7215,
            2880,
            2302,
            9961
        ],
        "answer": 2880
    },
    {
        "question": "Aarav wants to buy a cap. If his head circumference is 29cm, what available cap may fit him?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            26,
            36,
            10,
            43
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 empty boxes, 9 couch, 71 sofa, 12 algae spots, and 2 plants? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 94,
        "options": [
            94,
            23,
            95,
            83
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 refrigerator, 23 empty boxes, 83 couch, 7 cat, and 9 algae spots? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 71,
        "options": [
            130,
            118,
            71,
            117
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -25,
            23,
            2,
            25
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            19,
            9,
            10,
            -19
        ],
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 16 years old in the year 1475.In his greatest win, he looted 288747952 of 6728820684 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1808,
            1823,
            1459,
            1505
        ],
        "answer": 1459
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 24. When the sun is at 172 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 93,
        "options": [
            93,
            3,
            6,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 7 years old in the year 1225.In his greatest win, he looted 554103652 of 1383503080 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins are remaining in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            1383503080,
            1937606732,
            829399428,
            554103652
        ],
        "answer": 829399428
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 99. When the sun is at 143 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 101,
        "options": [
            68,
            101,
            18,
            77
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Owens wants to buy a pair of pants. If his waist size is 20cm, what available pair of pants may fit him?",
        "answer": 31,
        "options": [
            31,
            3,
            13,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 33 ohms and 19 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 22 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            52,
            627,
            22,
            45,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Thursday and returns to the bank 11months later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Saturday",
        "options": [
            "Wednesday",
            "Sunday",
            "Saturday",
            "Sunday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a tuesday and returns to the bank 9years later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Thursday",
        "options": [
            "Monday",
            "Sunday",
            "Thursday",
            "Sunday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Dhruv wants to buy a necklace. If his neck circumference is 14cm, what available necklace may fit him?",
        "answer": 32,
        "options": [
            32,
            7,
            4,
            28
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 tubelight, 69 pair of shoes, 71 couch, 15 human beings, and 5 crows? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 151,
        "options": [
            152,
            80,
            86,
            151
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 sofa, 33 empty boxes, 13 bed, 2 bed bugs, and 15 fungi spots? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 54,
        "options": [
            54,
            55,
            15,
            41
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "King wants to buy a Hand glove. If his Palm-size is 33cm, what available Hand glove may fit him?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            33,
            43,
            18,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international squash game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            1,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 37 ohms and 11 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 3 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            48,
            11,
            37,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a child can eat 25 lemons , how many lemons can a ants eat?",
        "answer": 13,
        "options": [
            25,
            13,
            38,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 sofa, 16 bed, 93 pair of shoes, 9 algae spots, and 10 dog? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            132,
            133,
            2,
            131
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If dog can eat 22 lemons , how many lemons can a pigeon eat?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            22,
            16,
            38,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Cunningham wants to put a car in a car parking space.The car parking space is 5.118 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the car?",
        "answer": 2.88,
        "options": [
            5.118,
            28.799999999999997,
            2.88,
            2.98
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 bed, 4 couch, 91 tubelight, 13 people, and 3 snail? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            16,
            104,
            17,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 tubelight, 69 pair of shoes, 71 couch, 15 human beings, and 5 crows? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            159,
            41,
            171,
            152
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 46000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 869000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            580,
            52.934,
            88,
            609
        ],
        "answer": 52.934
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Badminton game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            -1,
            0,
            0,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 18 ohms and 31 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 3 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            3,
            31,
            18,
            49
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 12 ohms and 5 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 4 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            60,
            0,
            8,
            4,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 6 years old in the year 1162.In his greatest win, he looted 35569691 of 175878297 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1156,
            1858,
            1223,
            1849
        ],
        "answer": 1156
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            19,
            9,
            10,
            -19
        ],
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 48 ohms and 19 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 6 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            67,
            6,
            0,
            912,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 18 ohms and 31 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 6 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            31,
            49,
            6,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 11 ohms and 49 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 5 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            60,
            539,
            0,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Henry wants to buy a pair of shoes. If his foot size is 30cm, what available pair of shoes may fit him?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            42,
            24,
            34,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 broom, 10 sofa, 90 tubelight, 9 cat, and 12 algae spots? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 48,
        "options": [
            48,
            333,
            169,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 16 years old in the year 1571.In his greatest win, he looted 172618311 of 5657811463 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins are remaining in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            5657811463,
            5830429774,
            5485193152,
            172618311
        ],
        "answer": 5485193152
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 89000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 278000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            222,
            839,
            249,
            320.144
        ],
        "answer": 320.144
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international cricket game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 7 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            10,
            2,
            11,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international rugby game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 10 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            5,
            25,
            14,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 mat, 46 refrigerator, 56 pair of shoes, 14 pigeons, and 10 crows? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            24,
            70,
            25,
            51
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international rugby game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 9 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            3,
            14,
            16,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Johnson wants to buy a Belt. If his waist size is 8cm, what available Belt may fit him?",
        "answer": 34,
        "options": [
            26,
            4,
            34,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 91000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 839000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            42,
            52,
            705,
            108.462
        ],
        "answer": 108.462
    },
    {
        "question": "Torres wants to put a Pizza Box in a Refrigerator.The Refrigerator is 4.834 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Pizza Box?",
        "answer": 3.76,
        "options": [
            3.76,
            4.834,
            3.86,
            37.599999999999994
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If cow can eat 15 watermelon , how many watermelon can a man eat?",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            15,
            12,
            27,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Roberts earns $13 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $1 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Roberts was paid $4676, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            341,
            209,
            188,
            276
        ],
        "answer": 341
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 3 couch, 77 flower vase, 90 empty boxes, 2 bed bugs, and 15 cat? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 170,
        "options": [
            170,
            80,
            171,
            92
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 77 gallons. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 1/9 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            14,
            54,
            8.56,
            55
        ],
        "answer": 8.56
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 12 sofa, 28 bed, 16 empty boxes, 7 trees, and 13 crows? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            40,
            21,
            23,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Boyd wants to put a phone in a pocket.The pocket is 4.571 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the phone?",
        "answer": 2.41,
        "options": [
            4.571,
            2.41,
            24.1,
            2.5100000000000002
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 6 feet by 6 feet?",
        "options": [
            5184,
            142,
            768,
            690
        ],
        "answer": 5184
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international cricket game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 11 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            22,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 flower vase, 46 refrigerator, 87 couch, 2 snail, and 14 bed bugs? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 86,
        "options": [
            0,
            228,
            219,
            86
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Navya wants to put a house in a street.The street is 5.046 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the house?",
        "answer": 1.24,
        "options": [
            1.34,
            5.046,
            1.24,
            12.4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Saturday and returns to the bank 3months later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Saturday",
        "options": [
            "Saturday",
            "Wednesday",
            "tuesday",
            "Friday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Table-Tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            0,
            4,
            2,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Robinson wants to buy a pair of shoes. If his foot size is 5cm, what available pair of shoes may fit him?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            5,
            2,
            6,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international rugby game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 3 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 13,
        "options": [
            16,
            2,
            13,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Adams wants to put a car in a road.The road is 6.345 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the car?",
        "answer": 1.78,
        "options": [
            1.8800000000000001,
            6.345,
            1.78,
            17.8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 flower vase, 42 empty boxes, 68 bed, 12 pigeons, and 15 cockroaches? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            94,
            109,
            71
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If cat can eat 24 apples , how many apples can a pigeon eat?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            24,
            23,
            47,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Tucker wants to put a Car in a Garage.The Garage is 9.986 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Car?",
        "answer": 8.73,
        "options": [
            87.30000000000001,
            8.83,
            8.73,
            9.986
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 13 ohms and 19 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 24 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 30,
        "options": [
            24,
            32,
            247,
            19,
            54
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 15 years old in the year 1841.In his greatest win, he looted 717984761 of 7047515081 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1826,
            1863,
            1840,
            1877
        ],
        "answer": 1826
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 80 miles in 4 hours and 12 minutes?",
        "options": [
            9.039853552275058,
            0.31746031746031744,
            3.321757573596999,
            8.079376218710141
        ],
        "answer": 0.31746031746031744
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international rugby game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 13 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            5,
            4,
            2,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 couch, 15 flower vase, 55 refrigerator, 2 trees, and 13 bed bugs? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            49,
            1,
            48,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -17,
            4,
            17,
            13
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a tuesday and returns to the bank 5months later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Sunday",
        "options": [
            "Sunday",
            "Wednesday",
            "Wednesday",
            "Wednesday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Herrera began counting from 0. She skip-counted by eights. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 488,
        "options": [
            488,
            490,
            489,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 3 feet by 10 feet?",
        "options": [
            9414,
            334,
            8560,
            4320
        ],
        "answer": 4320
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international rugby game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            7,
            14,
            15,
            25
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 20 years old in the year 1374.In his greatest win, he looted 420577844 of 3980479762 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1577,
            1431,
            1354,
            1598
        ],
        "answer": 1354
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Boxing game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            1,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            18,
            -26,
            8,
            26
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 65 gallons. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 2/7 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            77,
            12,
            18.57,
            33
        ],
        "answer": 18.57
    },
    {
        "question": "Cooper wants to buy a Belt. If his waist size is 6cm, what available Belt may fit him?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            28,
            12,
            9,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Saturday and returns to the bank 9months later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Sunday",
        "options": [
            "tuesday",
            "Friday",
            "Wednesday",
            "Sunday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 17 years old in the year 1519.In his greatest win, he looted 900951520 of 4127340844 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1502,
            1703,
            1603,
            1861
        ],
        "answer": 1502
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 tubelight, 41 refrigerator, 93 mat, 8 cockroaches, and 8 human beings? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 144,
        "options": [
            145,
            144,
            51,
            101
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $2 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-sixth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 11.3 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            369,
            218,
            63.8,
            406
        ],
        "answer": 63.8
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 refrigerator, 47 empty boxes, 12 bed, 2 cat, and 5 bed bugs? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 67,
        "options": [
            68,
            55,
            14,
            67
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international footbal game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 7 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            18,
            3,
            4,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 16 years old in the year 1475.In his greatest win, he looted 288747952 of 6728820684 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1808,
            1823,
            1459,
            1505
        ],
        "answer": 1459
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 18 years old in the year 1142.In his greatest win, he looted 614451906 of 3381704035 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1396,
            1561,
            1804,
            1124
        ],
        "answer": 1124
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 sofa, 82 tubelight, 76 mat, 7 plants, and 6 bed bugs? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 156,
        "options": [
            156,
            296,
            0,
            312
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 22 ohms and 24 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 7 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            46,
            0,
            5,
            7,
            528
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 10 years old in the year 1515.In his greatest win, he looted 268184920 of 2191210805 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins were actually present in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            268184920,
            2191210805,
            2459395725,
            -1923025885
        ],
        "answer": 2191210805
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international cricket game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            9,
            10,
            14,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 12. When the sun is at 117 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            15,
            20,
            4,
            67
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 4 broom, 73 cycles, 61 mat, 14 bed bugs, and 9 cat? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            125,
            89,
            125
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -30,
            13,
            17,
            30
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "Dhruv began counting from 0. She skip-counted by six's. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 552,
        "options": [
            552,
            553,
            554,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Martin began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fours. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 180,
        "options": [
            180,
            182,
            0,
            181
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            20,
            -30,
            30,
            10
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "Parker wants to put a book in a bag.The bag is 3.071 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the book?",
        "answer": 1.85,
        "options": [
            1.85,
            1.9500000000000002,
            3.071,
            18.5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 18 years old in the year 1142.In his greatest win, he looted 614451906 of 3381704035 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1396,
            1561,
            1804,
            1124
        ],
        "answer": 1124
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Thursday and returns to the bank 8years later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Friday",
        "options": [
            "Sunday",
            "Saturday",
            "Friday",
            "Monday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 45 miles in 2 hours and 32 minutes?",
        "options": [
            1.7137504600063038,
            0.29605263157894735,
            5.539990998584659,
            1.8160878562105718
        ],
        "answer": 0.29605263157894735
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 6 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            7,
            -17,
            10,
            17
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Thursday and returns to the bank 4years later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Monday",
        "options": [
            "Thursday",
            "Monday",
            "Sunday",
            "Friday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 16 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            16,
            6,
            10,
            -16
        ],
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "question": "Hayes wants to buy a hoodie. If his chest size is 7cm, what available hoodie may fit him?",
        "answer": 31,
        "options": [
            28,
            31,
            13,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Arjun wants to buy a necklace. If his neck circumference is 25cm, what available necklace may fit him?",
        "answer": 36,
        "options": [
            18,
            20,
            32,
            36
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 51 miles in 8 hours and 40 minutes?",
        "options": [
            1.9032875721701643,
            4.252079745432647,
            9.360520808730271,
            0.09807692307692308
        ],
        "answer": 0.09807692307692308
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 56000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 543000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            103.131,
            403,
            702,
            53
        ],
        "answer": 103.131
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 couch, 66 flower vase, 15 cycles, 14 cat, and 15 dog? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 121,
        "options": [
            121,
            387,
            241,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 7 flower vase, 39 cycles, 36 tubelight, 10 cockroaches, and 10 human beings? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            97,
            43,
            89,
            86
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 empty boxes, 95 bed, 83 sofa, 4 pigeons, and 3 plants? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            147,
            6,
            121,
            130
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 7 flower vase, 39 cycles, 36 tubelight, 10 cockroaches, and 10 human beings? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            21,
            20,
            46,
            46
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If cow can eat 30 chocolates , how many chocolates can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            30,
            24,
            54,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 2 tubelight, 69 flower vase, 77 broom, 8 human beings, and 7 fungi spots? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 148,
        "options": [
            85,
            149,
            148,
            71
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 refrigerator, 23 empty boxes, 83 couch, 7 cat, and 9 algae spots? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 80,
        "options": [
            80,
            204,
            399,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $52 to the charity and a total of $12120 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was tripled?",
        "options": [
            233,
            496,
            274,
            367
        ],
        "answer": 233
    },
    {
        "question": "Fernandez wants to buy a a ring. If his finger circumference is 31cm, what available a ring may fit him?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            27,
            45,
            31,
            45
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international golf game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            0,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international golf game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            0,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 77000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 21000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            3.667,
            328,
            181,
            242
        ],
        "answer": 3.667
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kph if you travel 82 miles in 6 hours and 1 minutes?",
        "options": [
            21.80609418282549,
            5.321533164456646,
            6.660895831658417,
            3.185419195080937
        ],
        "answer": 21.80609418282549
    },
    {
        "question": "Webb wants to put a luggage in a car trunk.The car trunk is 9.885 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the luggage?",
        "answer": 2.36,
        "options": [
            2.36,
            2.46,
            9.885,
            23.599999999999998
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ishaan wants to buy a pair of shoes. If his foot size is 37cm, what available pair of shoes may fit him?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            7,
            40,
            17,
            35
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of Moore increased from 811 per month to 945 per month while the salary of Fernandez increased from 455 to 575 and of Aadhya increased from 361 to 613 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Aadhya",
        "options": [
            "Moore",
            "Fernandez",
            "Aadhya",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 12 years old in the year 1360.In his greatest win, he looted 946695092 of 8542280706 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins were actually present in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            946695092,
            9488975798,
            8542280706,
            -7595585614
        ],
        "answer": 8542280706
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 2 tubelight, 69 flower vase, 77 broom, 8 human beings, and 7 fungi spots? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            15,
            71,
            85,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If dog can eat 7 cake , how many cake can a man eat?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            7,
            9,
            16,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 16 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            16,
            6,
            10,
            -16
        ],
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "question": "Crawford wants to buy a a ring. If his finger circumference is 33cm, what available a ring may fit him?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            17,
            38,
            11,
            30
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 tubelight, 69 pair of shoes, 71 couch, 15 human beings, and 5 crows? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            21,
            20,
            80,
            86
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 36 miles in 2 hours and 30 minutes?",
        "options": [
            14.399999999999999,
            7.298654473434047,
            5.104493992387478,
            9.210761660379744
        ],
        "answer": 14.399999999999999
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $60 to the charity and a total of $4446 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was doubled?",
        "options": [
            961,
            74,
            283,
            468
        ],
        "answer": 74
    },
    {
        "question": "Darsh wants to buy a cap. If his head circumference is 36cm, what available cap may fit him?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            27,
            10,
            9,
            42
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 bed, 11 cycles, 61 empty boxes, 6 crows, and 11 pigeons? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 68,
        "options": [
            99,
            95,
            68,
            97
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If giraffee can eat 9 cake , how many cake can a dog eat?",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            9,
            8,
            17,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Wallace began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fives. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 375,
        "options": [
            377,
            0,
            375,
            376
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international cricket game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            10,
            6,
            11,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international baseball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            6,
            11,
            7,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 refrigerator, 23 empty boxes, 83 couch, 7 cat, and 9 algae spots? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            38,
            94,
            94
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Murphy wants to put a Drawer in a Table.The Table is 9.001 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Drawer?",
        "answer": 6.92,
        "options": [
            7.02,
            6.92,
            9.001,
            69.2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 6 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            7,
            -17,
            10,
            17
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 74 gallons. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 4/10 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            44,
            29.6,
            81,
            35
        ],
        "answer": 29.6
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international volley ball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            6,
            2,
            5,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international golf game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            1,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 tubelight, 69 pair of shoes, 71 couch, 15 human beings, and 5 crows? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            152,
            149,
            161
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ahana wants to buy a pair of shoes. If his foot size is 36cm, what available pair of shoes may fit him?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            25,
            44,
            21,
            35
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 43 gallons. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 3/9 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            70,
            83,
            35,
            14.33
        ],
        "answer": 14.33
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 20 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -30,
            11,
            30,
            19
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "If dog can eat 23 chocolates , how many chocolates can a giraffee eat?",
        "answer": 26,
        "options": [
            23,
            26,
            49,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 couch, 15 flower vase, 55 refrigerator, 2 trees, and 13 bed bugs? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 70,
        "options": [
            260,
            143,
            0,
            70
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ford wants to buy a cap. If his head circumference is 18cm, what available cap may fit him?",
        "answer": 21,
        "options": [
            18,
            12,
            7,
            21
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ananya wants to buy a hat. If his head circumference is 24cm, what available hat may fit him?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            5,
            42,
            5,
            38
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 14 years old in the year 1810.In his greatest win, he looted 523242202 of 9660815474 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1796,
            1804,
            1893,
            1826
        ],
        "answer": 1796
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 6 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            23,
            1,
            -23,
            22
        ],
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "Sanchez wants to put a Statue in a River.The River is 6.004 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Statue?",
        "answer": 3.35,
        "options": [
            3.45,
            3.35,
            33.5,
            6.004
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 11 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            8,
            1,
            -9,
            9
        ],
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 15 years old in the year 1831.In his greatest win, he looted 486871292 of 7728491861 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins were actually present in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            486871292,
            -7241620569,
            7728491861,
            8215363153
        ],
        "answer": 7728491861
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 53 miles in 2 hours and 23 minutes?",
        "options": [
            2.631674998334757,
            8.533472720682163,
            22.237762237762237,
            2.5339132622358354
        ],
        "answer": 22.237762237762237
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $82 to the charity and a total of $16896 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was quadrupled?",
        "options": [
            277,
            206,
            952,
            958
        ],
        "answer": 206
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 37000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 31000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            626,
            1193.548,
            831,
            477
        ],
        "answer": 1193.548
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 16 years old in the year 1801.In his greatest win, he looted 861791453 of 6887543630 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins are remaining in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            861791453,
            6887543630,
            7749335083,
            6025752177
        ],
        "answer": 6025752177
    },
    {
        "question": "If cow can eat 29 apples , how many apples can a dog eat?",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            29,
            17,
            46,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If giraffee can eat 42 grapes , how many grapes can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 100,
        "options": [
            42,
            100,
            142,
            58
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Torres wants to buy a hat. If his head circumference is 27cm, what available hat may fit him?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            19,
            23,
            13,
            44
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If ants can eat 13 apples , how many apples can a cat eat?",
        "answer": 30,
        "options": [
            13,
            30,
            43,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 11 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            8,
            1,
            -9,
            9
        ],
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            10,
            9,
            9,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Butler wants to buy a Phone. If his Palm size is 5cm, what available Phone may fit him?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            26,
            45,
            9,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            3,
            0,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 41. When the sun is at 145 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 49,
        "options": [
            49,
            9,
            32,
            27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A family is going on a vacation to Chicago in a bus. There were 8 men, 10 women, 7 children of less than 10 years, 10 old people of age above 60 years.How many of the people can drive??",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            120,
            35,
            0,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 12 years old in the year 1515.In his greatest win, he looted 197779199 of 7602609956 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1858,
            1503,
            1828,
            1603
        ],
        "answer": 1503
    },
    {
        "question": "If pigeon can eat 17 lemons , how many lemons can a man eat?",
        "answer": 21,
        "options": [
            17,
            21,
            38,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 tubelight, 57 fan, 67 broom, 5 snail, and 4 bed bugs? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            72,
            10,
            62,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Rivera earns $10 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $3 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Rivera was paid $1059, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            325,
            104,
            95,
            188
        ],
        "answer": 104
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 70000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 160000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            437.5,
            180,
            769,
            356
        ],
        "answer": 437.5
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 flower vase, 95 mat, 40 empty boxes, 10 dog, and 14 cockroaches? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 148,
        "options": [
            148,
            149,
            108,
            50
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Krishna wants to buy a pair of shorts. If his waist size is 34cm, what available pair of shorts may fit him?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            39,
            24,
            14,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 3 bed, 59 flower vase, 12 refrigerator, 4 trees, and 14 human beings? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 74,
        "options": [
            16,
            74,
            75,
            62
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Darsh wants to buy a pair of socks. If his foot size is 40cm, what available pair of socks may fit him?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            42,
            35,
            30,
            42
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 2 tubelight, 69 flower vase, 77 broom, 8 human beings, and 7 fungi spots? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            51,
            51,
            28
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $2 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-sixth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 50.0 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            497,
            296.0,
            496,
            488
        ],
        "answer": 296.0
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $3 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional half mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 41.1 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            83.2,
            289,
            175,
            353
        ],
        "answer": 83.2
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of Anaya increased from 816 per month to 918 per month while the salary of Nelson increased from 976 to 976 and of Kelley increased from 898 to 937 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Kelley",
        "options": [
            "Anaya",
            "Nelson",
            "Kelley",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 23 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            9,
            -9,
            4,
            5
        ],
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 6 flower vase, 42 tubelight, 6 refrigerator, 2 dog, and 12 plants? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            66,
            59,
            61,
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 20 ohms and 48 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 1 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            20,
            1,
            68,
            48
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Castro wants to buy a Belt. If his waist size is 6cm, what available Belt may fit him?",
        "answer": 31,
        "options": [
            31,
            26,
            22,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 18 miles in 10 hours and 18 minutes?",
        "options": [
            1.7752878538326282,
            2.8927147299819094,
            9.569500508492869,
            0.02912621359223301
        ],
        "answer": 0.02912621359223301
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $62 to the charity and a total of $19848 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was quadrupled?",
        "options": [
            320,
            600,
            183,
            703
        ],
        "answer": 320
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 flower vase, 14 chair, 32 cycles, 14 pigeons, and 14 bed bugs? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 57,
        "options": [
            46,
            25,
            58,
            57
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 82 miles in 3 hours and 20 minutes?",
        "options": [
            2.8563587088022286,
            2.7509817999531507,
            0.6560000000000001,
            6.501163819427164
        ],
        "answer": 0.6560000000000001
    },
    {
        "question": "Myra began counting from 0. She skip-counted by sevens. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 686,
        "options": [
            688,
            687,
            0,
            686
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international squash game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            -1,
            2,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Crawford began counting from 0. She skip-counted by tens. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 420,
        "options": [
            420,
            0,
            422,
            421
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hamilton wants to put a Card in a Envelope.The Envelope is 9.679 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Card?",
        "answer": 4.46,
        "options": [
            4.46,
            44.6,
            9.679,
            4.56
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 76000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 592000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            947,
            390,
            473,
            128.378
        ],
        "answer": 128.378
    },
    {
        "question": "Wagner wants to put a Card in a Envelope.The Envelope is 7.771 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Card?",
        "answer": 3.75,
        "options": [
            37.5,
            3.75,
            3.85,
            7.771
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "James began counting from 0. She skip-counted by threes. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 171,
        "options": [
            0,
            172,
            173,
            171
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Brooks began counting from 0. She skip-counted by eights. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 152,
        "options": [
            0,
            154,
            153,
            152
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Monday and returns to the bank 4months later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Saturday",
        "options": [
            "Sunday",
            "Wednesday",
            "Saturday",
            "Sunday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 46 ohms and 16 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 22 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 26,
        "options": [
            62,
            16,
            48,
            736,
            22
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a child can eat 21 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a elephant eat?",
        "answer": 27,
        "options": [
            21,
            27,
            48,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 97 miles in 7 hours and 24 minutes?",
        "options": [
            8.377628869650728,
            2.4722639809756757,
            0.3495495495495496,
            4.21540014794898
        ],
        "answer": 0.3495495495495496
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 31 ohms and 45 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 1 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            45,
            76,
            31
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 11 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            8,
            1,
            -9,
            9
        ],
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 5 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -25,
            16,
            25,
            9
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "Hayes began counting from 0. She skip-counted by twos. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            0,
            24,
            25,
            26
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            15,
            -26,
            26,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "Webb wants to buy a cap. If his head circumference is 28cm, what available cap may fit him?",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            29,
            27,
            15,
            28
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 2 mat, 53 table, 8 flower vase, 1 bed bugs, and 10 dog? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 63,
        "options": [
            64,
            9,
            63,
            55
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 cycles, 61 broom, 13 empty boxes, 1 pigeons, and 6 snail? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            8,
            14,
            7,
            75
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 23 ohms and 50 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 5 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            50,
            5,
            73,
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 73000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 631000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            419,
            115689.382,
            992,
            565
        ],
        "answer": 115689.382
    },
    {
        "question": "If snail can eat 10 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a cat eat?",
        "answer": 26,
        "options": [
            10,
            26,
            36,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kph if you travel 16 miles in 3 hours and 57 minutes?",
        "options": [
            2.5539176486971966,
            6.481012658227848,
            1.693120634069879,
            4.057383020965068
        ],
        "answer": 6.481012658227848
    },
    {
        "question": "Cole wants to put a Pizza Box in a Refrigerator.The Refrigerator is 7.371 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Pizza Box?",
        "answer": 1.58,
        "options": [
            1.58,
            1.6800000000000002,
            15.8,
            7.371
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 11 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            8,
            1,
            -9,
            9
        ],
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "If snail can eat 18 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a cow eat?",
        "answer": 26,
        "options": [
            18,
            26,
            44,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $4 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-tenth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 23.9 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            420,
            238,
            346,
            210.1
        ],
        "answer": 210.1
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 7 flower vase, 39 cycles, 36 tubelight, 10 cockroaches, and 10 human beings? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 82,
        "options": [
            46,
            83,
            82,
            46
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $28 to the charity and a total of $12144 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was tripled?",
        "options": [
            743,
            433,
            794,
            735
        ],
        "answer": 433
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 17 years old in the year 1153.In his greatest win, he looted 821783639 of 3080400799 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1614,
            1136,
            1440,
            1840
        ],
        "answer": 1136
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 4 couch, 3 broom, 73 bed, 1 plants, and 13 cat? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 80,
        "options": [
            80,
            74,
            81,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 mat, 26 cycles, 66 fan, 11 bed bugs, and 12 algae spots? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            39,
            106,
            108,
            122
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international golf game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            0,
            -1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 couch, 27 chair, 12 cycles, 10 plants, and 13 cockroaches? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 66,
        "options": [
            66,
            0,
            397,
            298
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 3 mat, 74 broom, 79 flower vase, 11 algae spots, and 15 cockroaches? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 151,
        "options": [
            151,
            290,
            304,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 bed, 11 cycles, 61 empty boxes, 6 crows, and 11 pigeons? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 85,
        "options": [
            86,
            85,
            24,
            67
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -25,
            23,
            2,
            25
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "If giraffee can eat 22 watermelon , how many watermelon can a ants eat?",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            22,
            18,
            40,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 24 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            13,
            -17,
            17,
            4
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "If dog can eat 6 chocolates , how many chocolates can a pigeon eat?",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            6,
            5,
            11,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 8 feet by 3 feet?",
        "options": [
            9670,
            3832,
            3456,
            9533
        ],
        "answer": 3456
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 7 fan, 3 cycles, 49 flower vase, 12 cat, and 4 human beings? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            61,
            10,
            16,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 3 mat, 74 broom, 79 flower vase, 11 algae spots, and 15 cockroaches? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 26,
        "options": [
            26,
            90,
            27,
            77
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 fan, 14 tubelight, 29 broom, 13 cat, and 14 pigeons? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 27,
        "options": [
            28,
            19,
            42,
            27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 sofa, 33 empty boxes, 13 bed, 2 bed bugs, and 15 fungi spots? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 54,
        "options": [
            41,
            55,
            15,
            54
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $6 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-sixth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 49.7 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            298.2,
            402,
            332,
            428
        ],
        "answer": 298.2
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 6 pair of shoes, 88 couch, 24 tubelight, 13 dog, and 4 plants? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 118,
        "options": [
            37,
            94,
            118,
            119
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $46 to the charity and a total of $4718 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was doubled?",
        "options": [
            485,
            729,
            423,
            102
        ],
        "answer": 102
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 20 years old in the year 1582.In his greatest win, he looted 339343984 of 2587397533 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1605,
            1624,
            1562,
            1641
        ],
        "answer": 1562
    },
    {
        "question": "Brooks wants to buy a pair of socks. If his foot size is 26cm, what available pair of socks may fit him?",
        "answer": 32,
        "options": [
            18,
            17,
            32,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If snail can eat 6 apples , how many apples can a dog eat?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            6,
            24,
            30,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 39 ohms and 34 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 6 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            6,
            73,
            34,
            39
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 43. When the sun is at 109 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            10,
            96,
            65,
            57
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 6 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            23,
            1,
            -23,
            22
        ],
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 18 years old in the year 1351.In his greatest win, he looted 63376057 of 2648341027 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1859,
            1848,
            1466,
            1333
        ],
        "answer": 1333
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 7 fan, 3 cycles, 49 flower vase, 12 cat, and 4 human beings? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 56,
        "options": [
            56,
            74,
            60,
            67
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -30,
            13,
            17,
            30
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $2 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-seventh mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 31.5 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            393,
            215.5,
            282,
            408
        ],
        "answer": 215.5
    },
    {
        "question": "If cow can eat 26 watermelon , how many watermelon can a snail eat?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            26,
            24,
            50,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 refrigerator, 23 empty boxes, 83 couch, 7 cat, and 9 algae spots? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            16,
            17,
            33,
            90
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If cow can eat 27 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            27,
            7,
            34,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 44. When the sun is at 88 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            6,
            69,
            72,
            96
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a child can eat 24 chocolates , how many chocolates can a elephant eat?",
        "answer": 27,
        "options": [
            24,
            27,
            51,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international golf game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            0,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 16 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            16,
            6,
            10,
            -16
        ],
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $74 to the charity and a total of $17836 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was quadrupled?",
        "options": [
            241,
            864,
            958,
            490
        ],
        "answer": 241
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 85000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 100000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            436,
            412,
            0.85,
            903
        ],
        "answer": 0.85
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 84000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 512000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            164.062,
            85,
            893,
            532
        ],
        "answer": 164.062
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Wednesday and returns to the bank 10months later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "tuesday",
        "options": [
            "Friday",
            "tuesday",
            "Monday",
            "Monday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Spencer wants to buy a Phone. If his Palm size is 14cm, what available Phone may fit him?",
        "answer": 33,
        "options": [
            2,
            14,
            12,
            33
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international squash game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            -1,
            0,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 refrigerator, 47 empty boxes, 12 bed, 2 cat, and 5 bed bugs? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            7,
            66,
            56
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 couch, 66 flower vase, 15 cycles, 14 cat, and 15 dog? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            35,
            59,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 7 flower vase, 39 cycles, 36 tubelight, 10 cockroaches, and 10 human beings? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 21,
        "options": [
            179,
            0,
            21,
            127
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 8 years old in the year 1900.In his greatest win, he looted 539175086 of 1175285492 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins are remaining in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            636110406,
            1175285492,
            539175086,
            1714460578
        ],
        "answer": 636110406
    },
    {
        "question": "Fox began counting from 0. She skip-counted by twos. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 92,
        "options": [
            0,
            92,
            94,
            93
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international cricket game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 9 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            19,
            2,
            9,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If giraffee can eat 73 grapes , how many grapes can a snail eat?",
        "answer": 86,
        "options": [
            73,
            86,
            159,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kabir wants to put a phone in a pocket.The pocket is 4.849 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the phone?",
        "answer": 1.42,
        "options": [
            1.42,
            4.849,
            14.2,
            1.52
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $8 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-tenth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 31.4 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            370,
            498,
            281.6,
            336
        ],
        "answer": 281.6
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 11 years old in the year 1329.In his greatest win, he looted 570410466 of 1547295181 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1370,
            1603,
            1318,
            1741
        ],
        "answer": 1318
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 33 miles in 10 hours and 2 minutes?",
        "options": [
            9.650463104483705,
            9.131196866909466,
            0.08770764119601329,
            6.570156154802866
        ],
        "answer": 0.08770764119601329
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 16 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            16,
            6,
            10,
            -16
        ],
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 6 ohms and 50 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 9 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            50,
            9,
            56,
            19,
            300
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 flower vase, 95 mat, 40 empty boxes, 10 dog, and 14 cockroaches? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 112,
        "options": [
            152,
            168,
            112,
            149
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 5 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -25,
            16,
            25,
            9
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 mat, 10 table, 90 chair, 6 trees, and 4 fungi spots? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            15,
            10,
            11,
            96
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $8 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-seventh mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 20.2 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            403,
            240,
            154,
            142.4
        ],
        "answer": 142.4
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Friday and returns to the bank 6years later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Thursday",
        "options": [
            "Friday",
            "tuesday",
            "Thursday",
            "Sunday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 4 couch, 18 tubelight, 51 broom, 14 snail, and 9 cat? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            18,
            44,
            82,
            79
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 69 miles in 4 hours and 28 minutes?",
        "options": [
            0.2574626865671642,
            7.003795237445972,
            2.066825148133556,
            6.257536575101212
        ],
        "answer": 0.2574626865671642
    },
    {
        "question": "Henderson began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fives. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 345,
        "options": [
            346,
            347,
            345,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 5 years old in the year 1221.In his greatest win, he looted 574269970 of 7205217893 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins were actually present in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            7205217893,
            7779487863,
            -6630947923,
            574269970
        ],
        "answer": 7205217893
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 63. When the sun is at 112 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            16,
            91,
            75,
            73
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 27. When the sun is at 11 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 108,
        "options": [
            26,
            6,
            22,
            108
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 flower vase, 42 empty boxes, 68 bed, 12 pigeons, and 15 cockroaches? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            126,
            24,
            126,
            54
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Aarav wants to buy a pair of shoes. If his foot size is 24cm, what available pair of shoes may fit him?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            25,
            37,
            45,
            30
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jordan began counting from 0. She skip-counted by six's. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 330,
        "options": [
            332,
            330,
            331,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 mat, 46 refrigerator, 56 pair of shoes, 14 pigeons, and 10 crows? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            2,
            113,
            120,
            125
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $50 to the charity and a total of $14248 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was quadrupled?",
        "options": [
            759,
            274,
            284,
            111
        ],
        "answer": 284
    },
    {
        "question": "If man can eat 17 lemons , how many lemons can a dog eat?",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            17,
            5,
            22,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 18 ohms and 46 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 3 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            2,
            828,
            0,
            3,
            64
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If elephant can eat 18 apples , how many apples can a cat eat?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            18,
            7,
            25,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 43 pints. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 2/10 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            8.6,
            82,
            28,
            62
        ],
        "answer": 8.6
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a tuesday and returns to the bank 9796days later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Friday",
        "options": [
            "tuesday",
            "Sunday",
            "Thursday",
            "Friday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Carter began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fours. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 120,
        "options": [
            120,
            122,
            0,
            121
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 12 ohms and 5 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 2 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            2,
            5,
            17,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 20 ohms and 48 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 6 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            20,
            6,
            48,
            68
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 26 ohms and 20 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 10 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            10,
            26,
            46,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international golf game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            1,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $86 to the charity and a total of $7600 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was doubled?",
        "options": [
            414,
            498,
            960,
            88
        ],
        "answer": 88
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 18 miles in 3 hours and 32 minutes?",
        "options": [
            5.094339622641509,
            4.127074724410271,
            3.9943551607390075,
            1.2979991472095347
        ],
        "answer": 5.094339622641509
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 27000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 503000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            53.678,
            537,
            240,
            300
        ],
        "answer": 53.678
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Thursday and returns to the bank 11months later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Friday",
        "options": [
            "Monday",
            "Monday",
            "Sunday",
            "Friday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 93 miles in 2 hours and 40 minutes?",
        "options": [
            6.192073538046631,
            5.837480282976578,
            0.93,
            3.8852041778026805
        ],
        "answer": 0.93
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 20 years old in the year 1582.In his greatest win, he looted 339343984 of 2587397533 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1605,
            1624,
            1562,
            1641
        ],
        "answer": 1562
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 7 flower vase, 39 cycles, 36 tubelight, 10 cockroaches, and 10 human beings? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            46,
            21,
            46,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 couch, 43 table, 77 mat, 13 cockroaches, and 6 fungi spots? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            18,
            97,
            80,
            101
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 6 pair of shoes, 88 couch, 24 tubelight, 13 dog, and 4 plants? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 118,
        "options": [
            118,
            120,
            120,
            134
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Morales earns $6 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $2 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Morales was paid $3907, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            151,
            73,
            247,
            513
        ],
        "answer": 513
    },
    {
        "question": "Ananya earns $19 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $4 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Ananya was paid $4304, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            162,
            204,
            65,
            404
        ],
        "answer": 204
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 12 years old in the year 1693.In his greatest win, he looted 788950713 of 9490956965 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1685,
            1850,
            1681,
            1791
        ],
        "answer": 1681
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 11 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            12,
            4,
            5,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 46 ohms and 16 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 4 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            46,
            62,
            16,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Ice Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 6 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            5,
            9,
            0,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Tran wants to put a luggage in a car trunk.The car trunk is 3.2 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the luggage?",
        "answer": 1.16,
        "options": [
            1.26,
            1.16,
            3.2,
            11.6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Herrera wants to buy a hat. If his head circumference is 38cm, what available hat may fit him?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            25,
            41,
            9,
            41
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            2,
            1,
            3,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international basketball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            4,
            8,
            0,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international baseball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            0,
            8,
            12,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kph if you travel 29 miles in 8 hours and 11 minutes?",
        "options": [
            8.94492627646074,
            5.670061099796335,
            9.841982151050264,
            2.076017634359692
        ],
        "answer": 5.670061099796335
    },
    {
        "question": "Henderson began counting from 0. She skip-counted by threes. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 216,
        "options": [
            216,
            0,
            217,
            218
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Wednesday and returns to the bank 11months later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Wednesday",
        "options": [
            "Thursday",
            "Wednesday",
            "Sunday",
            "Saturday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 bed, 11 cycles, 61 empty boxes, 6 crows, and 11 pigeons? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            73,
            43,
            35
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international volley ball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 5 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            1,
            2,
            10,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $46 to the charity and a total of $11343 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was tripled?",
        "options": [
            132,
            246,
            692,
            848
        ],
        "answer": 246
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            18,
            -26,
            8,
            26
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            18,
            -26,
            8,
            26
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international basketball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            10,
            2,
            5,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If dog can eat 5 cake , how many cake can a cow eat?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            5,
            6,
            11,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 14 years old in the year 1329.In his greatest win, he looted 269959268 of 2310180349 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins are remaining in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            2310180349,
            2580139617,
            2040221081,
            269959268
        ],
        "answer": 2040221081
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international basketball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            10,
            3,
            3,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Badminton game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            4,
            0,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "White wants to buy a cap. If his head circumference is 27cm, what available cap may fit him?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            6,
            28,
            17,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 73 miles in 10 hours and 29 minutes?",
        "options": [
            6.474217297603495,
            8.332242916156275,
            1.2078686993371655,
            0.11605723370429252
        ],
        "answer": 0.11605723370429252
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $10 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-fifth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 13.0 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            201,
            125,
            97,
            58.0
        ],
        "answer": 58.0
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 17 years old in the year 1508.In his greatest win, he looted 239809754 of 2316739501 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins were actually present in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            2556549255,
            -2076929747,
            239809754,
            2316739501
        ],
        "answer": 2316739501
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 20 years old in the year 1582.In his greatest win, he looted 339343984 of 2587397533 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1605,
            1624,
            1562,
            1641
        ],
        "answer": 1562
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 11 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            8,
            1,
            -9,
            9
        ],
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 23 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            15,
            -15,
            4,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Sunday and returns to the bank 12years later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Friday",
        "options": [
            "Sunday",
            "Friday",
            "Thursday",
            "Sunday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international cricket game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            9,
            8,
            15,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 6 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            23,
            1,
            -23,
            22
        ],
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "Kelley began counting from 0. She skip-counted by tens. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 790,
        "options": [
            790,
            791,
            0,
            792
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 15 ohms and 23 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 6 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            15,
            23,
            38,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 11 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            8,
            1,
            -9,
            9
        ],
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 12 years old in the year 1693.In his greatest win, he looted 788950713 of 9490956965 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1685,
            1850,
            1681,
            1791
        ],
        "answer": 1681
    },
    {
        "question": "Kelly began counting from 0. She skip-counted by tens. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 960,
        "options": [
            961,
            0,
            962,
            960
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 52000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 248000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            209.677,
            123,
            392,
            887
        ],
        "answer": 209.677
    },
    {
        "question": "Vivaan wants to buy a hat. If his head circumference is 37cm, what available hat may fit him?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            45,
            40,
            9,
            42
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 mat, 26 cycles, 66 fan, 11 bed bugs, and 12 algae spots? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            77,
            24,
            23,
            36
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 4 feet by 9 feet?",
        "options": [
            4974,
            4772,
            1096,
            5184
        ],
        "answer": 5184
    },
    {
        "question": "If cat can eat 20 apples , how many apples can a man eat?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            20,
            24,
            44,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Navya began counting from 0. She skip-counted by threes. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 213,
        "options": [
            214,
            213,
            215,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Friday and returns to the bank 7years later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Friday",
        "options": [
            "Wednesday",
            "Friday",
            "Monday",
            "tuesday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Aaradhya wants to put a luggage in a car trunk.The car trunk is 9.518 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the luggage?",
        "answer": 5.62,
        "options": [
            5.72,
            5.62,
            56.2,
            9.518
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Anvi began counting from 0. She skip-counted by threes. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 162,
        "options": [
            0,
            162,
            163,
            164
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 12 broom, 32 flower vase, 25 mat, 13 human beings, and 13 people? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 69,
        "options": [
            38,
            70,
            69,
            44
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Badminton game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            4,
            1,
            0,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If man can eat 6 apples , how many apples can a elephant eat?",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            6,
            8,
            14,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Burns wants to buy a pair of shorts. If his waist size is 25cm, what available pair of shorts may fit him?",
        "answer": 32,
        "options": [
            6,
            32,
            24,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 sofa, 16 bed, 93 pair of shoes, 9 algae spots, and 10 dog? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 83,
        "options": [
            307,
            236,
            0,
            83
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 tubelight, 57 fan, 67 broom, 5 snail, and 4 bed bugs? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 129,
        "options": [
            130,
            72,
            62,
            129
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 sofa, 33 empty boxes, 13 bed, 2 bed bugs, and 15 fungi spots? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            67,
            10,
            61,
            43
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $4 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-seventh mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 36.7 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            432,
            475,
            253.9,
            370
        ],
        "answer": 253.9
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 15 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -26,
            19,
            7,
            26
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $6 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-third mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 36.9 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            394,
            437,
            265,
            113.7
        ],
        "answer": 113.7
    },
    {
        "question": "If pigeon can eat 19 lemons , how many lemons can a snail eat?",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            19,
            18,
            37,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ortiz wants to put a picture in a frame.The frame is 3.625 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the picture?",
        "answer": 1.37,
        "options": [
            3.625,
            1.37,
            1.4700000000000002,
            13.700000000000001
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 61000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 731000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            83.447,
            59,
            436,
            82
        ],
        "answer": 83.447
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 7 cycles, 45 sofa, 68 chair, 11 plants, and 8 bed bugs? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            77,
            123,
            135,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Ice Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 4 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            12,
            2,
            1,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If elephant can eat 27 lemons , how many lemons can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            27,
            24,
            51,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 23 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -27,
            23,
            4,
            27
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international cricket game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 11 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            7,
            17,
            0,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Crawford wants to buy a pair of shoes. If his foot size is 12cm, what available pair of shoes may fit him?",
        "answer": 36,
        "options": [
            14,
            36,
            31,
            31
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $8 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-third mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 38.6 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            120.8,
            450,
            399,
            382
        ],
        "answer": 120.8
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international cricket game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 3 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            18,
            7,
            8,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international basketball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 5 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            2,
            10,
            0,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 5 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            5,
            19,
            7,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Snyder wants to buy a pair of shorts. If his waist size is 21cm, what available pair of shorts may fit him?",
        "answer": 26,
        "options": [
            24,
            16,
            19,
            26
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 20 years old in the year 1374.In his greatest win, he looted 420577844 of 3980479762 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1577,
            1431,
            1354,
            1598
        ],
        "answer": 1354
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 16 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            21,
            22,
            -22,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 22
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Saturday and returns to the bank 3338days later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Friday",
        "options": [
            "Saturday",
            "Wednesday",
            "tuesday",
            "Friday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $8 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-tenth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 19.2 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            319,
            171.8,
            331,
            443
        ],
        "answer": 171.8
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 23. When the sun is at 24 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 72,
        "options": [
            72,
            16,
            16,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -17,
            4,
            17,
            13
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "If dog can eat 52 grapes , how many grapes can a cow eat?",
        "answer": 101,
        "options": [
            52,
            101,
            153,
            49
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $7 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-third mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 27.2 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            87,
            85.6,
            265,
            398
        ],
        "answer": 85.6
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $2 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-fifth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 14.2 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            58,
            476,
            282,
            54.8
        ],
        "answer": 54.8
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 6 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            3,
            -24,
            24,
            21
        ],
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 1 feet by 6 feet?",
        "options": [
            864,
            7361,
            9936,
            7218
        ],
        "answer": 864
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 7 cycles, 45 sofa, 68 chair, 11 plants, and 8 bed bugs? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 19,
        "options": [
            20,
            19,
            79,
            52
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 5 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -25,
            16,
            25,
            9
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 bed, 4 couch, 91 tubelight, 13 people, and 3 snail? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 110,
        "options": [
            19,
            104,
            110,
            111
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -30,
            13,
            17,
            30
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $10 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional quarter mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 41.8 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            194,
            173.2,
            460,
            348
        ],
        "answer": 173.2
    },
    {
        "question": "Gibson began counting from 0. She skip-counted by eights. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 152,
        "options": [
            153,
            152,
            0,
            154
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 empty boxes, 95 bed, 83 sofa, 4 pigeons, and 3 plants? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 192,
        "options": [
            193,
            109,
            87,
            192
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Badminton game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            -1,
            0,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If giraffee can eat 76 grapes , how many grapes can a cat eat?",
        "answer": 74,
        "options": [
            76,
            74,
            150,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international golf game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            -1,
            2,
            0,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ahana earns $17 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $5 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Ahana was paid $4881, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            319,
            67,
            311,
            244
        ],
        "answer": 244
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 empty boxes, 37 chair, 82 refrigerator, 8 cockroaches, and 5 dog? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 130,
        "options": [
            48,
            130,
            131,
            90
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 12 fan, 97 tubelight, 86 empty boxes, 6 cat, and 10 trees? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            202,
            163,
            198
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Richardson wants to put a luggage in a car trunk.The car trunk is 7.779 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the luggage?",
        "answer": 2.61,
        "options": [
            2.71,
            7.779,
            26.099999999999998,
            2.61
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 3 bed, 59 flower vase, 12 refrigerator, 4 trees, and 14 human beings? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            39,
            7,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 sofa, 82 tubelight, 76 mat, 7 plants, and 6 bed bugs? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            117,
            2,
            116,
            68
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If giraffee can eat 25 chocolates , how many chocolates can a elephant eat?",
        "answer": 26,
        "options": [
            25,
            26,
            51,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 18 years old in the year 1351.In his greatest win, he looted 63376057 of 2648341027 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1859,
            1848,
            1466,
            1333
        ],
        "answer": 1333
    },
    {
        "question": "Vivaan wants to put a luggage in a car trunk.The car trunk is 4.698 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the luggage?",
        "answer": 2.27,
        "options": [
            22.7,
            2.37,
            4.698,
            2.27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kph if you travel 72 miles in 1 hours and 36 minutes?",
        "options": [
            8.520302935627603,
            6.058710092631464,
            72.0,
            2.304036599891531
        ],
        "answer": 72.0
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international basketball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 5 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            -1,
            0,
            0,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 couch, 15 flower vase, 55 refrigerator, 2 trees, and 13 bed bugs? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 84,
        "options": [
            85,
            57,
            84,
            29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Sunday and returns to the bank 2years later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "tuesday",
        "options": [
            "Thursday",
            "Thursday",
            "tuesday",
            "Saturday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 7 fan, 3 cycles, 49 flower vase, 12 cat, and 4 human beings? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            141,
            0,
            2,
            141
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -17,
            4,
            17,
            13
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 couch, 74 cycles, 90 empty boxes, 5 bed bugs, and 14 snail? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            78,
            54,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 flower vase, 95 mat, 40 empty boxes, 10 dog, and 14 cockroaches? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            50,
            25,
            108,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $88 to the charity and a total of $19400 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was quadrupled?",
        "options": [
            487,
            430,
            383,
            220
        ],
        "answer": 220
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 19 years old in the year 1157.In his greatest win, he looted 516168024 of 2069171387 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins are remaining in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            516168024,
            1553003363,
            2069171387,
            2585339411
        ],
        "answer": 1553003363
    },
    {
        "question": "If cat can eat 15 lemons , how many lemons can a man eat?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            15,
            24,
            39,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Gomez wants to buy a hoodie. If his chest size is 31cm, what available hoodie may fit him?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            35,
            39,
            11,
            28
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Angel wants to put a fruit in a basket.The basket is 4.263 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the fruit?",
        "answer": 2.91,
        "options": [
            4.263,
            3.0100000000000002,
            2.91,
            29.1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 24 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            13,
            -17,
            17,
            4
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 6 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            23,
            1,
            -23,
            22
        ],
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "Stone began counting from 0. She skip-counted by nine's. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 351,
        "options": [
            352,
            351,
            353,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a child can eat 30 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a snail eat?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            30,
            20,
            50,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Mendoza earns $12 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $5 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Mendoza was paid $2267, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            459,
            102,
            452,
            162
        ],
        "answer": 162
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 tubelight, 57 fan, 67 broom, 5 snail, and 4 bed bugs? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 52,
        "options": [
            0,
            52,
            178,
            334
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 37000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 26000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            397,
            298,
            446,
            1423.077
        ],
        "answer": 1423.077
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $7 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-third mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 36.9 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            114.7,
            216,
            343,
            398
        ],
        "answer": 114.7
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international golf game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            1,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $6 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional quarter mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 15.7 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            332,
            373,
            64.8,
            291
        ],
        "answer": 64.8
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 80. When the sun is at 152 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 82,
        "options": [
            44,
            39,
            79,
            82
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Vivaan wants to buy a Phone. If his Palm size is 30cm, what available Phone may fit him?",
        "answer": 33,
        "options": [
            17,
            17,
            16,
            33
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 bed, 11 cycles, 61 empty boxes, 6 crows, and 11 pigeons? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            24,
            18,
            17,
            67
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 6 flower vase, 42 tubelight, 6 refrigerator, 2 dog, and 12 plants? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            62,
            11,
            19,
            57
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 98000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 882000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            900,
            111.111,
            376,
            166
        ],
        "answer": 111.111
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 couch, 74 cycles, 90 empty boxes, 5 bed bugs, and 14 snail? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 19,
        "options": [
            69,
            19,
            50,
            177
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 44 ohms and 6 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 6 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            264,
            10,
            50,
            6,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kph if you travel 59 miles in 8 hours and 34 minutes?",
        "options": [
            4.591126057509208,
            11.019455252918288,
            1.7259728460965613,
            2.687366980628644
        ],
        "answer": 11.019455252918288
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 23 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            15,
            -15,
            4,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 24 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            13,
            -17,
            17,
            4
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "Aadhya began counting from 0. She skip-counted by sevens. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 238,
        "options": [
            239,
            238,
            240,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 6 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            3,
            -24,
            24,
            21
        ],
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international volley ball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            6,
            7,
            1,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Henry wants to buy a Phone. If his Palm size is 10cm, what available Phone may fit him?",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            14,
            4,
            4,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 4 couch, 3 broom, 73 bed, 1 plants, and 13 cat? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 80,
        "options": [
            74,
            7,
            81,
            80
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 fan, 31 tubelight, 34 pair of shoes, 3 cockroaches, and 1 bed bugs? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 80,
        "options": [
            46,
            37,
            80,
            81
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 5 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -25,
            16,
            25,
            9
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "Myers wants to buy a Phone. If his Palm size is 23cm, what available Phone may fit him?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            27,
            7,
            20,
            42
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 refrigerator, 23 empty boxes, 83 couch, 7 cat, and 9 algae spots? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            90,
            17,
            16,
            33
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international footbal game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 3 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            10,
            12,
            9,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 4 couch, 3 broom, 73 bed, 1 plants, and 13 cat? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            17,
            359,
            158,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 12 broom, 32 flower vase, 25 mat, 13 human beings, and 13 people? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 26,
        "options": [
            27,
            26,
            44,
            38
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -30,
            13,
            17,
            30
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 3 mat, 74 broom, 79 flower vase, 11 algae spots, and 15 cockroaches? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            22,
            15,
            89
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kph if you travel 50 miles in 1 hours and 40 minutes?",
        "options": [
            9.978148643206124,
            6.800883983700184,
            48.0,
            8.639815308036898
        ],
        "answer": 48.0
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Badminton game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            4,
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 15 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -26,
            19,
            7,
            26
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Boxing game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            0,
            1,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 22 ohms and 24 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 2 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            24,
            2,
            22,
            46
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kelly wants to put a Table in a Room.The Room is 5.136 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Table?",
        "answer": 2.74,
        "options": [
            2.8400000000000003,
            27.400000000000002,
            5.136,
            2.74
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international golf game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            0,
            -1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 5 feet by 3 feet?",
        "options": [
            1284,
            9694,
            2024,
            2160
        ],
        "answer": 2160
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international volley ball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 5 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            11,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Peterson wants to put a Statue in a River.The River is 5.931 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Statue?",
        "answer": 4.06,
        "options": [
            40.599999999999994,
            4.06,
            4.159999999999999,
            5.931
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 4 broom, 73 cycles, 61 mat, 14 bed bugs, and 9 cat? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 138,
        "options": [
            139,
            138,
            77,
            75
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 empty boxes, 95 bed, 83 sofa, 4 pigeons, and 3 plants? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 192,
        "options": [
            87,
            192,
            109,
            193
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 15 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -26,
            19,
            7,
            26
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 cycles, 61 broom, 13 empty boxes, 1 pigeons, and 6 snail? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            8,
            75,
            14,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Weaver wants to buy a shirt. If his body size is 26cm, what available shirt may fit him?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            32,
            44,
            21,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $4 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-seventh mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 7.4 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            315,
            48.8,
            479,
            87
        ],
        "answer": 48.8
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 86 pints. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 5/9 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            47.78,
            40,
            94,
            26
        ],
        "answer": 47.78
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 6 years old in the year 1894.In his greatest win, he looted 994238319 of 2685474586 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins were actually present in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            3679712905,
            -1691236267,
            2685474586,
            994238319
        ],
        "answer": 2685474586
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Boxing game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            0,
            -1,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 flower vase, 42 empty boxes, 68 bed, 12 pigeons, and 15 cockroaches? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 118,
        "options": [
            119,
            80,
            118,
            50
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international basketball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            2,
            4,
            3,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 63 pints. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 1/7 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            98,
            67,
            9.0,
            13
        ],
        "answer": 9.0
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international cricket game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 10 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            10,
            12,
            9,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hoffman began counting from 0. She skip-counted by tens. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 70,
        "options": [
            0,
            71,
            70,
            72
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 57 miles in 6 hours and 36 minutes?",
        "options": [
            5.283676964968946,
            0.23030303030303031,
            4.035581940654626,
            1.5873522709504306
        ],
        "answer": 0.23030303030303031
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international volley ball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 4 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            1,
            0,
            10,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ferguson earns $10 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $1 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Ferguson was paid $4936, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            363,
            70,
            457,
            188
        ],
        "answer": 457
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $8 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-fifth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 37.5 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            154.0,
            483,
            295,
            266
        ],
        "answer": 154.0
    },
    {
        "question": "If cow can eat 19 apples , how many apples can a snail eat?",
        "answer": 13,
        "options": [
            19,
            13,
            32,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 empty boxes, 9 couch, 71 sofa, 12 algae spots, and 2 plants? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 94,
        "options": [
            83,
            94,
            95,
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            4,
            28,
            24,
            -28
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 58. When the sun is at 177 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 63,
        "options": [
            54,
            4,
            63,
            41
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 56000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 186000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            337,
            948,
            537,
            0.301
        ],
        "answer": 0.301
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            19,
            9,
            10,
            -19
        ],
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 59 pints. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 4/6 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            18,
            100,
            39.33,
            98
        ],
        "answer": 39.33
    },
    {
        "question": "If ants can eat 15 chocolates , how many chocolates can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 26,
        "options": [
            15,
            26,
            41,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 5 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -25,
            16,
            25,
            9
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "Rogers wants to buy a hoodie. If his chest size is 17cm, what available hoodie may fit him?",
        "answer": 33,
        "options": [
            29,
            33,
            8,
            25
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Aarohi began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fours. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 224,
        "options": [
            224,
            0,
            225,
            226
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If pigeon can eat 23 watermelon , how many watermelon can a cat eat?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            23,
            28,
            51,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 10 years old in the year 1425.In his greatest win, he looted 652651653 of 6628306191 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1602,
            1415,
            1777,
            1885
        ],
        "answer": 1415
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 24 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            17,
            23,
            6,
            -23
        ],
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "Romero wants to put a car in a car parking space.The car parking space is 5.351 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the car?",
        "answer": 3.32,
        "options": [
            5.351,
            3.42,
            3.32,
            33.199999999999996
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 11. When the sun is at 83 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            40,
            58,
            10,
            108
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            3,
            1,
            2,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Table-Tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            4,
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 8 feet by 2 feet?",
        "options": [
            2304,
            6755,
            7410,
            9659
        ],
        "answer": 2304
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 73 miles in 1 hours and 1 minutes?",
        "options": [
            71.80327868852459,
            9.54916966085498,
            3.196030075160736,
            9.488308491667826
        ],
        "answer": 71.80327868852459
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 6 years old in the year 1368.In his greatest win, he looted 696169940 of 2363305690 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins are remaining in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            696169940,
            1667135750,
            2363305690,
            3059475630
        ],
        "answer": 1667135750
    },
    {
        "question": "Ahana wants to put a Card in a Envelope.The Envelope is 9.98 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Card?",
        "answer": 2.64,
        "options": [
            2.64,
            9.98,
            2.74,
            26.400000000000002
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            -1,
            4,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Evans earns $7 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $2 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Evans was paid $1512, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            190,
            112,
            298,
            495
        ],
        "answer": 190
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 4 couch, 18 tubelight, 51 broom, 14 snail, and 9 cat? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 73,
        "options": [
            22,
            74,
            73,
            65
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 2 flower vase, 85 table, 85 pair of shoes, 3 cat, and 9 crows? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 172,
        "options": [
            173,
            88,
            172,
            87
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 15 years old in the year 1542.In his greatest win, he looted 25132639 of 299690815 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins were actually present in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            25132639,
            324823454,
            299690815,
            -274558176
        ],
        "answer": 299690815
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 3000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 241000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            614,
            599,
            594,
            12.448
        ],
        "answer": 12.448
    },
    {
        "question": "Myers wants to buy a Hand glove. If his Palm-size is 11cm, what available Hand glove may fit him?",
        "answer": 32,
        "options": [
            16,
            32,
            12,
            30
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 17 years old in the year 1807.In his greatest win, he looted 217303743 of 7928914330 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins were actually present in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            8146218073,
            -7711610587,
            217303743,
            7928914330
        ],
        "answer": 7928914330
    },
    {
        "question": "Aarush wants to buy a necklace. If his neck circumference is 39cm, what available necklace may fit him?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            3,
            43,
            43,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 14 years old in the year 1748.In his greatest win, he looted 912362361 of 9405625353 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins are remaining in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            8493262992,
            10317987714,
            912362361,
            9405625353
        ],
        "answer": 8493262992
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 20 ohms and 48 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 6 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            6,
            68,
            960,
            3,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international golf game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            0,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Vihaan wants to put a Drawer in a Table.The Table is 3.816 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Drawer?",
        "answer": 1.01,
        "options": [
            3.816,
            1.11,
            10.1,
            1.01
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 couch, 74 cycles, 90 empty boxes, 5 bed bugs, and 14 snail? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 158,
        "options": [
            379,
            246,
            158,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Ice Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 4 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            1,
            11,
            1,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 23 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            9,
            -9,
            4,
            5
        ],
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "If giraffee can eat 7 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a elephant eat?",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            7,
            15,
            22,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 44 miles in 9 hours and 56 minutes?",
        "options": [
            3.8593384595838764,
            8.468552092359008,
            4.429530201342282,
            8.02799958877846
        ],
        "answer": 4.429530201342282
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 flower vase, 86 chair, 59 empty boxes, 13 human beings, and 3 trees? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            17,
            100,
            72,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 10 years old in the year 1796.In his greatest win, he looted 126588341 of 2072840991 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1810,
            1848,
            1786,
            1819
        ],
        "answer": 1786
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 83 miles in 7 hours and 58 minutes?",
        "options": [
            7.659646150123368,
            2.002435699746676,
            0.2778242677824268,
            9.975530011525267
        ],
        "answer": 0.2778242677824268
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 4 couch, 3 broom, 73 bed, 1 plants, and 13 cat? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            74,
            7,
            15,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Williams earns $15 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $2 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Williams was paid $3812, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            361,
            191,
            236,
            29
        ],
        "answer": 236
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 49000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 441000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            903,
            630,
            404,
            111.111
        ],
        "answer": 111.111
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international footbal game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 6 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            7,
            8,
            20,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 54000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 143000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            377.622,
            412,
            940,
            428
        ],
        "answer": 377.622
    },
    {
        "question": "If man can eat 5 cake , how many cake can a ants eat?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            5,
            4,
            9,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 14 years old in the year 1810.In his greatest win, he looted 523242202 of 9660815474 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1796,
            1804,
            1893,
            1826
        ],
        "answer": 1796
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $92 to the charity and a total of $5946 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was doubled?",
        "options": [
            270,
            64,
            184,
            59
        ],
        "answer": 64
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 12 broom, 32 flower vase, 25 mat, 13 human beings, and 13 people? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 26,
        "options": [
            44,
            27,
            26,
            38
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A family is going on a vacation to Chicago in a bus. There were 8 men, 6 women, 9 children of less than 10 years, 10 old people of age above 60 years.How many of the people can drive??",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            106,
            33,
            0,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            20,
            -30,
            30,
            10
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "Ford wants to buy a pair of shorts. If his waist size is 16cm, what available pair of shorts may fit him?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            37,
            40,
            13,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Bailey wants to buy a shirt. If his body size is 39cm, what available shirt may fit him?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            43,
            14,
            17,
            34
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Aarush wants to buy a pair of shorts. If his waist size is 9cm, what available pair of shorts may fit him?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            2,
            2,
            20,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Saturday and returns to the bank 5606days later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Friday",
        "options": [
            "Thursday",
            "Sunday",
            "tuesday",
            "Friday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international rugby game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 7 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            2,
            16,
            12,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Howard wants to buy a Belt. If his waist size is 16cm, what available Belt may fit him?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            39,
            42,
            32,
            27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Barnes began counting from 0. She skip-counted by tens. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 240,
        "options": [
            0,
            242,
            241,
            240
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Freeman wants to put a chocolate in a jar.The jar is 5.491 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the chocolate?",
        "answer": 4.24,
        "options": [
            4.24,
            4.34,
            5.491,
            42.400000000000006
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If dog can eat 8 cake , how many cake can a giraffee eat?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            8,
            9,
            17,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ortiz wants to put a Drawer in a Table.The Table is 5.925 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Drawer?",
        "answer": 4.47,
        "options": [
            5.925,
            44.699999999999996,
            4.569999999999999,
            4.47
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Friday and returns to the bank 8years later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Saturday",
        "options": [
            "Saturday",
            "Thursday",
            "Friday",
            "Thursday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            18,
            -26,
            8,
            26
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "Anya wants to buy a cap. If his head circumference is 9cm, what available cap may fit him?",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            2,
            29,
            9,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Fisher wants to buy a cap. If his head circumference is 15cm, what available cap may fit him?",
        "answer": 21,
        "options": [
            21,
            3,
            8,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 23 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -27,
            23,
            4,
            27
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Thursday and returns to the bank 9958days later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Monday",
        "options": [
            "Thursday",
            "Thursday",
            "Monday",
            "Saturday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Nguyen wants to buy a pair of shorts. If his waist size is 25cm, what available pair of shorts may fit him?",
        "answer": 35,
        "options": [
            35,
            14,
            22,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Prisha wants to buy a cap. If his head circumference is 28cm, what available cap may fit him?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            41,
            29,
            45,
            44
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 couch, 27 chair, 12 cycles, 10 plants, and 13 cockroaches? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            23,
            32,
            24,
            22
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 19. When the sun is at 16 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            12,
            2,
            38,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sai wants to buy a hoodie. If his chest size is 35cm, what available hoodie may fit him?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            7,
            40,
            23,
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 10 years old in the year 1370.In his greatest win, he looted 435333603 of 2129131507 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins are remaining in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            2564465110,
            2129131507,
            1693797904,
            435333603
        ],
        "answer": 1693797904
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international rugby game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 9 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            27,
            3,
            10,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 11 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            8,
            1,
            -9,
            9
        ],
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 7 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            20,
            9,
            1,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 12 fan, 97 tubelight, 86 empty boxes, 6 cat, and 10 trees? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            4,
            119,
            96,
            109
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Fisher wants to buy a pair of pants. If his waist size is 15cm, what available pair of pants may fit him?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            40,
            8,
            24,
            35
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If cat can eat 8 chocolates , how many chocolates can a pigeon eat?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            8,
            7,
            15,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $58 to the charity and a total of $5962 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was doubled?",
        "options": [
            314,
            111,
            102,
            151
        ],
        "answer": 102
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 11 ohms and 19 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 6 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            6,
            19,
            11,
            30
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international baseball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 3 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            5,
            10,
            6,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 9 years old in the year 1447.In his greatest win, he looted 714664535 of 4224985971 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1490,
            1502,
            1624,
            1438
        ],
        "answer": 1438
    },
    {
        "question": "Hill wants to buy a pair of socks. If his foot size is 34cm, what available pair of socks may fit him?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            35,
            40,
            9,
            26
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $5 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-seventh mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 11.8 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            497,
            108,
            80.6,
            250
        ],
        "answer": 80.6
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 31 ohms and 45 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 4 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            1395,
            4,
            0,
            76,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Shaurya earns $9 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $3 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Shaurya was paid $3679, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            198,
            400,
            331,
            438
        ],
        "answer": 331
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kph if you travel 87 miles in 3 hours and 59 minutes?",
        "options": [
            34.945606694560674,
            2.7974309844672556,
            3.3639093410381657,
            1.3950049941759035
        ],
        "answer": 34.945606694560674
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Thursday and returns to the bank 9years later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Saturday",
        "options": [
            "Saturday",
            "Sunday",
            "Thursday",
            "Friday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Johnson wants to put a Statue in a River.The River is 4.159 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Statue?",
        "answer": 2.81,
        "options": [
            28.1,
            2.81,
            4.159,
            2.91
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A family is going on a vacation to Chicago in a bus. There were 5 men, 6 women, 4 children of less than 10 years, 7 old people of age above 60 years.How many of the people can drive??",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            105,
            22,
            0,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 20 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -30,
            11,
            30,
            19
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 23 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -27,
            23,
            4,
            27
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international basketball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            1,
            3,
            8,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 11 years old in the year 1535.In his greatest win, he looted 118578690 of 2877246404 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins are remaining in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            2758667714,
            2995825094,
            118578690,
            2877246404
        ],
        "answer": 2758667714
    },
    {
        "question": "If pigeon can eat 28 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a snail eat?",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            28,
            12,
            40,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 broom, 10 sofa, 90 tubelight, 9 cat, and 12 algae spots? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 21,
        "options": [
            21,
            99,
            25,
            22
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 16 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            21,
            22,
            -22,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 22
    },
    {
        "question": "Nichols began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fours. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 72,
        "options": [
            0,
            72,
            74,
            73
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            1,
            2,
            1,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 26 ohms and 20 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 3 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            20,
            26,
            46,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Spencer wants to buy a Hand glove. If his Palm-size is 17cm, what available Hand glove may fit him?",
        "answer": 31,
        "options": [
            8,
            10,
            12,
            31
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 6 pair of shoes, 88 couch, 24 tubelight, 13 dog, and 4 plants? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            17,
            18,
            94,
            37
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Romero wants to put a book in a bag.The bag is 9.852 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the book?",
        "answer": 4.04,
        "options": [
            4.04,
            40.4,
            4.14,
            9.852
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 15 years old in the year 1155.In his greatest win, he looted 331991280 of 360960493 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1319,
            1341,
            1140,
            1688
        ],
        "answer": 1140
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 84 gallons. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 2/8 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            91,
            21.0,
            97,
            44
        ],
        "answer": 21.0
    },
    {
        "question": "If giraffee can eat 29 lemons , how many lemons can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            29,
            23,
            52,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 24 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            13,
            -17,
            17,
            4
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international volley ball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 3 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            3,
            8,
            3,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 tubelight, 57 fan, 67 broom, 5 snail, and 4 bed bugs? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            23,
            93,
            121
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international rugby game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 10 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            27,
            0,
            9,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 6 pair of shoes, 88 couch, 24 tubelight, 13 dog, and 4 plants? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            94,
            18,
            17,
            37
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 6 ohms and 50 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 4 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            56,
            50,
            6,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $5 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-third mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 18.6 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            77,
            372,
            323,
            57.8
        ],
        "answer": 57.8
    },
    {
        "question": "Allen wants to buy a Phone. If his Palm size is 17cm, what available Phone may fit him?",
        "answer": 21,
        "options": [
            21,
            16,
            4,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Mitchell wants to buy a Phone. If his Palm size is 18cm, what available Phone may fit him?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            12,
            26,
            11,
            37
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Myra began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fives. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 115,
        "options": [
            0,
            117,
            115,
            116
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 23 miles in 8 hours and 15 minutes?",
        "options": [
            0.046464646464646465,
            7.042272622070734,
            6.250184467854233,
            9.130097022486213
        ],
        "answer": 0.046464646464646465
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 24 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            17,
            23,
            6,
            -23
        ],
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 mat, 46 refrigerator, 56 pair of shoes, 14 pigeons, and 10 crows? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 107,
        "options": [
            107,
            108,
            51,
            70
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 2 flower vase, 85 table, 85 pair of shoes, 3 cat, and 9 crows? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            87,
            13,
            12,
            88
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Cruz earns $14 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $1 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Cruz was paid $4743, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            128,
            193,
            428,
            322
        ],
        "answer": 322
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Wednesday and returns to the bank 5547days later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Saturday",
        "options": [
            "Sunday",
            "Saturday",
            "Sunday",
            "Thursday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 54000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 285000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            922,
            189.474,
            495,
            603
        ],
        "answer": 189.474
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            11,
            -29,
            29,
            18
        ],
        "answer": 29
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 11 ohms and 49 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 3 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            11,
            3,
            49,
            60
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 32. When the sun is at 178 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 32,
        "options": [
            14,
            32,
            30,
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Simpson wants to buy a Belt. If his waist size is 9cm, what available Belt may fit him?",
        "answer": 31,
        "options": [
            25,
            4,
            31,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 20 years old in the year 1564.In his greatest win, he looted 818663478 of 5951938350 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1673,
            1544,
            1722,
            1709
        ],
        "answer": 1544
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international footbal game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 11 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            2,
            3,
            0,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 12 broom, 32 flower vase, 25 mat, 13 human beings, and 13 people? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            28,
            22,
            69
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Peterson wants to put a Drawer in a Table.The Table is 5.597 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Drawer?",
        "answer": 3.24,
        "options": [
            3.3400000000000003,
            3.24,
            32.400000000000006,
            5.597
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "King wants to buy a pair of pants. If his waist size is 30cm, what available pair of pants may fit him?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            41,
            14,
            17,
            29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 12 sofa, 28 bed, 16 empty boxes, 7 trees, and 13 crows? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 65,
        "options": [
            65,
            308,
            0,
            270
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Sunday and returns to the bank 12months later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Monday",
        "options": [
            "Saturday",
            "Monday",
            "tuesday",
            "Wednesday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 39 ohms and 31 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 9 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            70,
            0,
            9,
            1209,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Woods wants to put a car in a road.The road is 4.643 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the car?",
        "answer": 2.37,
        "options": [
            2.37,
            23.700000000000003,
            2.47,
            4.643
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Olson began counting from 0. She skip-counted by eights. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            42,
            40,
            0,
            41
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $4 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional quarter mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 43.9 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            175.6,
            333,
            415,
            178
        ],
        "answer": 175.6
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 sofa, 82 tubelight, 76 mat, 7 plants, and 6 bed bugs? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 13,
        "options": [
            13,
            14,
            83,
            93
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If giraffee can eat 27 chocolates , how many chocolates can a cow eat?",
        "answer": 13,
        "options": [
            27,
            13,
            40,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international rugby game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 3 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            12,
            25,
            11,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 18 years old in the year 1351.In his greatest win, he looted 63376057 of 2648341027 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1859,
            1848,
            1466,
            1333
        ],
        "answer": 1333
    },
    {
        "question": "If snail can eat 21 watermelon , how many watermelon can a giraffee eat?",
        "answer": 30,
        "options": [
            21,
            30,
            51,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 16 years old in the year 1831.In his greatest win, he looted 861323390 of 7817265017 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins are remaining in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            861323390,
            6955941627,
            7817265017,
            8678588407
        ],
        "answer": 6955941627
    },
    {
        "question": "Edwards wants to put a book in a bag.The bag is 7.61 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the book?",
        "answer": 2.19,
        "options": [
            2.29,
            2.19,
            21.9,
            7.61
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 43. When the sun is at 120 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 25,
        "options": [
            97,
            50,
            77,
            25
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 6 pair of shoes, 88 couch, 24 tubelight, 13 dog, and 4 plants? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 118,
        "options": [
            94,
            37,
            118,
            119
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Table-Tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            3,
            0,
            1,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $4 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-eighth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 11.5 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            211,
            426,
            88.0,
            316
        ],
        "answer": 88.0
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 7 years old in the year 1831.In his greatest win, he looted 583044588 of 9854007764 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins are remaining in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            9270963176,
            10437052352,
            583044588,
            9854007764
        ],
        "answer": 9270963176
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 23 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            15,
            -15,
            4,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 23 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -27,
            23,
            4,
            27
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 6 years old in the year 1162.In his greatest win, he looted 35569691 of 175878297 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1156,
            1858,
            1223,
            1849
        ],
        "answer": 1156
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 37 ohms and 11 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 9 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            31,
            407,
            9,
            11,
            48
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 4 couch, 18 tubelight, 51 broom, 14 snail, and 9 cat? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            23,
            24,
            65,
            22
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of Dunn increased from 381 per month to 954 per month while the salary of Kabir increased from 455 to 698 and of Ward increased from 909 to 921 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Ward",
        "options": [
            "Dunn",
            "Kabir",
            "Ward",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Badminton game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            -1,
            0,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 18 ohms and 46 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 7 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            7,
            18,
            64,
            46
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 87 miles in 3 hours and 34 minutes?",
        "options": [
            9.932075210553272,
            5.4376853537818866,
            24.39252336448598,
            3.740792957086949
        ],
        "answer": 24.39252336448598
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Boxing game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            0,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 56 miles in 1 hours and 43 minutes?",
        "options": [
            0.8699029126213593,
            9.829770946622665,
            3.318330468053441,
            7.39545001988402
        ],
        "answer": 0.8699029126213593
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 58 miles in 1 hours and 8 minutes?",
        "options": [
            7.097704246852424,
            1.057087058194679,
            1.3647058823529414,
            6.080422907676742
        ],
        "answer": 1.3647058823529414
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 cycles, 61 broom, 13 empty boxes, 1 pigeons, and 6 snail? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 88,
        "options": [
            75,
            89,
            14,
            88
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 46 ohms and 16 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 3 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            0,
            62,
            736,
            4,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 8 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -25,
            23,
            2,
            25
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "Gray wants to buy a shirt. If his body size is 10cm, what available shirt may fit him?",
        "answer": 13,
        "options": [
            13,
            9,
            13,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 33 ohms and 19 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 4 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            33,
            52,
            19,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 6 flower vase, 42 tubelight, 6 refrigerator, 2 dog, and 12 plants? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 54,
        "options": [
            8,
            54,
            48,
            55
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international baseball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 4 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            13,
            7,
            8,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $32 to the charity and a total of $11769 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was tripled?",
        "options": [
            727,
            826,
            159,
            367
        ],
        "answer": 367
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 41 miles in 6 hours and 57 minutes?",
        "options": [
            2.555611908145304,
            2.223751578415006,
            5.042407342445187,
            0.09832134292565947
        ],
        "answer": 0.09832134292565947
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international baseball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 4 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            5,
            12,
            6,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If cat can eat 18 apples , how many apples can a man eat?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            18,
            20,
            38,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 31 ohms and 45 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 9 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            76,
            31,
            45,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 4 broom, 73 cycles, 61 mat, 14 bed bugs, and 9 cat? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            75,
            77,
            24,
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 15 years old in the year 1155.In his greatest win, he looted 331991280 of 360960493 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1319,
            1341,
            1140,
            1688
        ],
        "answer": 1140
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            18,
            -26,
            8,
            26
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "Mcdonald began counting from 0. She skip-counted by sevens. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 623,
        "options": [
            623,
            625,
            0,
            624
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 fan, 31 tubelight, 34 pair of shoes, 3 cockroaches, and 1 bed bugs? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            46,
            5,
            37,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Table-Tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            4,
            1,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Rose wants to put a Table in a Room.The Room is 7.976 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Table?",
        "answer": 2.97,
        "options": [
            7.976,
            29.700000000000003,
            2.97,
            3.0700000000000003
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international baseball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 3 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            6,
            9,
            8,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a child can eat 24 watermelon , how many watermelon can a giraffee eat?",
        "answer": 26,
        "options": [
            24,
            26,
            50,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -30,
            13,
            17,
            30
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "Phillips began counting from 0. She skip-counted by tens. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 290,
        "options": [
            292,
            0,
            291,
            290
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 42 ohms and 18 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 5 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            42,
            5,
            18,
            60
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 29 miles in 3 hours and 47 minutes?",
        "options": [
            8.55522549743625,
            5.496257818718971,
            0.1277533039647577,
            2.386340230378158
        ],
        "answer": 0.1277533039647577
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 6 years old in the year 1876.In his greatest win, he looted 179891474 of 3709546021 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1879,
            1872,
            1870,
            1899
        ],
        "answer": 1870
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            1,
            1,
            3,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -17,
            4,
            17,
            13
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 11 years old in the year 1329.In his greatest win, he looted 570410466 of 1547295181 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1370,
            1603,
            1318,
            1741
        ],
        "answer": 1318
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            20,
            -30,
            30,
            10
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $9 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional quarter mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 47.2 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            193.8,
            433,
            217,
            396
        ],
        "answer": 193.8
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 46 miles in 5 hours and 44 minutes?",
        "options": [
            8.521919320561809,
            8.922499020275875,
            4.096922117003388,
            0.13372093023255813
        ],
        "answer": 0.13372093023255813
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            4,
            28,
            24,
            -28
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 41 miles in 2 hours and 16 minutes?",
        "options": [
            3.053252814136716,
            0.48235294117647065,
            6.893102533526144,
            7.106586003183519
        ],
        "answer": 0.48235294117647065
    },
    {
        "question": "Taylor began counting from 0. She skip-counted by nine's. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 486,
        "options": [
            487,
            488,
            0,
            486
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 9. When the sun is at 118 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            19,
            66,
            5,
            51
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Shaurya wants to buy a pair of shoes. If his foot size is 10cm, what available pair of shoes may fit him?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            28,
            17,
            8,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 6 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            7,
            -17,
            10,
            17
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 42. When the sun is at 78 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            100,
            103,
            106,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Lee wants to buy a Hand glove. If his Palm-size is 24cm, what available Hand glove may fit him?",
        "answer": 36,
        "options": [
            36,
            20,
            29,
            28
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 29000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 317000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            91.483,
            170,
            891,
            717
        ],
        "answer": 91.483
    },
    {
        "question": "Long wants to buy a pair of pants. If his waist size is 8cm, what available pair of pants may fit him?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            28,
            12,
            8,
            28
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 1 feet by 9 feet?",
        "options": [
            2175,
            137,
            8686,
            1296
        ],
        "answer": 1296
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international baseball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 7 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            10,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international baseball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 4 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            5,
            3,
            6,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If man can eat 98 grapes , how many grapes can a giraffee eat?",
        "answer": 153,
        "options": [
            98,
            153,
            251,
            55
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 41. When the sun is at 30 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 100,
        "options": [
            18,
            3,
            100,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If ants can eat 85 grapes , how many grapes can a cat eat?",
        "answer": 173,
        "options": [
            85,
            173,
            258,
            88
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 7 flower vase, 39 cycles, 36 tubelight, 10 cockroaches, and 10 human beings? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            98,
            28,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Holmes wants to buy a a ring. If his finger circumference is 27cm, what available a ring may fit him?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            40,
            31,
            30,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 1 feet by 8 feet?",
        "options": [
            2107,
            2295,
            7106,
            1152
        ],
        "answer": 1152
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 couch, 66 flower vase, 15 cycles, 14 cat, and 15 dog? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            112,
            75,
            94,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 20 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -30,
            11,
            30,
            19
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "Torres wants to buy a pair of pants. If his waist size is 15cm, what available pair of pants may fit him?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            41,
            29,
            8,
            37
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ryan wants to buy a cap. If his head circumference is 26cm, what available cap may fit him?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            3,
            44,
            43,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sai wants to put a Table in a Room.The Room is 5.143 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Table?",
        "answer": 4.08,
        "options": [
            4.08,
            5.143,
            40.8,
            4.18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 40 ohms and 39 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 10 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            11,
            79,
            0,
            1560,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If snail can eat 18 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a elephant eat?",
        "answer": 27,
        "options": [
            18,
            27,
            45,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -17,
            4,
            17,
            13
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $20 to the charity and a total of $13386 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was tripled?",
        "options": [
            669,
            363,
            511,
            694
        ],
        "answer": 669
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 14 years old in the year 1507.In his greatest win, he looted 590161739 of 4423182681 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1824,
            1766,
            1493,
            1658
        ],
        "answer": 1493
    },
    {
        "question": "A family is going on a vacation to Chicago in a bus. There were 3 men, 9 women, 3 children of less than 10 years, 2 old people of age above 60 years.How many of the people can drive??",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            108,
            17,
            0,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international golf game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            0,
            -1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international basketball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            8,
            1,
            3,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 bed, 4 couch, 91 tubelight, 13 people, and 3 snail? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 48,
        "options": [
            126,
            114,
            48,
            117
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If elephant can eat 24 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a ants eat?",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            24,
            17,
            41,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 24 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            17,
            23,
            6,
            -23
        ],
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 empty boxes, 37 chair, 82 refrigerator, 8 cockroaches, and 5 dog? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            74,
            71,
            1,
            26
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 39 ohms and 34 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 19 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            73,
            19,
            43,
            34,
            1326
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 6 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            23,
            1,
            -23,
            22
        ],
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international rugby game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 3 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            11,
            30,
            12,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international rugby game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            15,
            20,
            5,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If man can eat 29 apples , how many apples can a snail eat?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            29,
            23,
            52,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a tuesday and returns to the bank 2years later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Thursday",
        "options": [
            "Saturday",
            "Sunday",
            "Sunday",
            "Thursday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 16 years old in the year 1880.In his greatest win, he looted 483626438 of 9144657538 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1873,
            1889,
            1881,
            1864
        ],
        "answer": 1864
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international golf game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            1,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 tubelight, 69 pair of shoes, 71 couch, 15 human beings, and 5 crows? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            86,
            21,
            80,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $8 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional half mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 42.5 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            225,
            91.0,
            99,
            293
        ],
        "answer": 91.0
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 23 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            9,
            -9,
            4,
            5
        ],
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "Tucker wants to buy a pair of socks. If his foot size is 38cm, what available pair of socks may fit him?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            32,
            40,
            13,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 3 feet by 3 feet?",
        "options": [
            3753,
            1296,
            2795,
            8656
        ],
        "answer": 1296
    },
    {
        "question": "Nichols wants to put a house in a street.The street is 8.724 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the house?",
        "answer": 4.9,
        "options": [
            49.0,
            4.9,
            5.0,
            8.724
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            21,
            -21,
            19,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 21
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international baseball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 3 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            0,
            6,
            10,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of Cole increased from 470 per month to 792 per month while the salary of Medina increased from 917 to 962 and of Jenkins increased from 457 to 988 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Jenkins",
        "options": [
            "Cole",
            "Medina",
            "Jenkins",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 32 ohms and 29 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 16 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            928,
            61,
            16,
            39,
            29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If giraffee can eat 29 apples , how many apples can a pigeon eat?",
        "answer": 25,
        "options": [
            29,
            25,
            54,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 flower vase, 14 chair, 32 cycles, 14 pigeons, and 14 bed bugs? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            29,
            28,
            25,
            46
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 15 years old in the year 1728.In his greatest win, he looted 940338025 of 2970471518 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins were actually present in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            2970471518,
            3910809543,
            940338025,
            -2030133493
        ],
        "answer": 2970471518
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 mat, 10 table, 90 chair, 6 trees, and 4 fungi spots? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            22,
            22,
            88
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international golf game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            -1,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international cricket game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 10 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            19,
            5,
            4,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 39 ohms and 34 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 7 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            39,
            7,
            34,
            73
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            4,
            1,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If cat can eat 21 watermelon , how many watermelon can a giraffee eat?",
        "answer": 26,
        "options": [
            21,
            26,
            47,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of Kabir increased from 555 per month to 976 per month while the salary of Murphy increased from 822 to 984 and of Hoffman increased from 537 to 594 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Hoffman",
        "options": [
            "Kabir",
            "Murphy",
            "Hoffman",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international golf game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            2,
            -1,
            0,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 61000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 25000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            983,
            534,
            2440.0,
            170
        ],
        "answer": 2440.0
    },
    {
        "question": "Harris wants to buy a Phone. If his Palm size is 14cm, what available Phone may fit him?",
        "answer": 36,
        "options": [
            21,
            33,
            36,
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Allen wants to buy a hoodie. If his chest size is 31cm, what available hoodie may fit him?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            27,
            18,
            45,
            41
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $96 to the charity and a total of $14824 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was quadrupled?",
        "options": [
            154,
            350,
            799,
            292
        ],
        "answer": 154
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 14 years old in the year 1507.In his greatest win, he looted 590161739 of 4423182681 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1824,
            1766,
            1493,
            1658
        ],
        "answer": 1493
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Boxing game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            -1,
            0,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 23 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -27,
            23,
            4,
            27
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 couch, 43 table, 77 mat, 13 cockroaches, and 6 fungi spots? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 134,
        "options": [
            90,
            57,
            135,
            134
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Wednesday and returns to the bank 9months later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Wednesday",
        "options": [
            "Friday",
            "Monday",
            "Saturday",
            "Wednesday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 bed, 11 cycles, 61 empty boxes, 6 crows, and 11 pigeons? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 85,
        "options": [
            67,
            85,
            24,
            86
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 6 years old in the year 1876.In his greatest win, he looted 179891474 of 3709546021 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1879,
            1872,
            1870,
            1899
        ],
        "answer": 1870
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $84 to the charity and a total of $6908 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was doubled?",
        "options": [
            822,
            82,
            834,
            327
        ],
        "answer": 82
    },
    {
        "question": "Owens wants to put a chocolate in a jar.The jar is 8.671 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the chocolate?",
        "answer": 2.31,
        "options": [
            2.31,
            2.41,
            23.1,
            8.671
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international volley ball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 4 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            12,
            2,
            1,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 tubelight, 41 refrigerator, 93 mat, 8 cockroaches, and 8 human beings? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            69,
            7,
            153
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 6 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            3,
            -24,
            24,
            21
        ],
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 17 years old in the year 1153.In his greatest win, he looted 821783639 of 3080400799 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1614,
            1136,
            1440,
            1840
        ],
        "answer": 1136
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $7 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional half mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 17.4 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            233,
            448,
            39.8,
            373
        ],
        "answer": 39.8
    },
    {
        "question": "Flores began counting from 0. She skip-counted by tens. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 370,
        "options": [
            372,
            0,
            370,
            371
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 flower vase, 14 chair, 32 cycles, 14 pigeons, and 14 bed bugs? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            13,
            19,
            38
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Anaya began counting from 0. She skip-counted by six's. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 240,
        "options": [
            241,
            242,
            0,
            240
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            20,
            -30,
            30,
            10
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 15 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -26,
            19,
            7,
            26
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 empty boxes, 20 bed, 15 refrigerator, 8 dog, and 7 pigeons? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            9,
            56,
            36,
            44
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 18 years old in the year 1142.In his greatest win, he looted 614451906 of 3381704035 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1396,
            1561,
            1804,
            1124
        ],
        "answer": 1124
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 44 ohms and 6 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 10 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            44,
            50,
            6,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $9 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-third mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 22.9 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            373,
            74.7,
            376,
            392
        ],
        "answer": 74.7
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Badminton game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            -1,
            3,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 16 miles in 10 hours and 10 minutes?",
        "options": [
            2.080057985447081,
            8.337385069731198,
            0.0419672131147541,
            2.065430998751324
        ],
        "answer": 0.0419672131147541
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 23 miles in 3 hours and 43 minutes?",
        "options": [
            6.674868810051568,
            2.1475445104540682,
            6.988361352674968,
            0.1650224215246637
        ],
        "answer": 0.1650224215246637
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 11 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            11,
            10,
            14,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 refrigerator, 47 empty boxes, 12 bed, 2 cat, and 5 bed bugs? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            31,
            29,
            1,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Wells wants to buy a shirt. If his body size is 34cm, what available shirt may fit him?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            41,
            11,
            23,
            37
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international rugby game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 3 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 13,
        "options": [
            13,
            3,
            12,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 6 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            7,
            -17,
            10,
            17
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 24 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            13,
            -17,
            17,
            4
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 60 miles in 5 hours and 54 minutes?",
        "options": [
            0.1694915254237288,
            7.552904702006365,
            3.4521048390488587,
            5.301574607423976
        ],
        "answer": 0.1694915254237288
    },
    {
        "question": "Crawford wants to put a book in a bag.The bag is 5.729 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the book?",
        "answer": 1.35,
        "options": [
            5.729,
            1.35,
            13.5,
            1.4500000000000002
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 57 miles in 4 hours and 22 minutes?",
        "options": [
            2.9381096308154,
            0.3480916030534351,
            7.793594732718159,
            9.693876532199045
        ],
        "answer": 0.3480916030534351
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 empty boxes, 95 bed, 83 sofa, 4 pigeons, and 3 plants? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 171,
        "options": [
            171,
            288,
            0,
            240
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 empty boxes, 20 bed, 15 refrigerator, 8 dog, and 7 pigeons? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            15,
            23,
            16,
            34
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Cook earns $19 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $1 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Cook was paid $2363, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            23,
            123,
            164,
            161
        ],
        "answer": 123
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 mat, 46 refrigerator, 56 pair of shoes, 14 pigeons, and 10 crows? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 21,
        "options": [
            82,
            43,
            21,
            46
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Aayan wants to buy a hat. If his head circumference is 10cm, what available hat may fit him?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            29,
            38,
            22,
            29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 11 years old in the year 1716.In his greatest win, he looted 836326661 of 8675669182 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1765,
            1760,
            1705,
            1764
        ],
        "answer": 1705
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            4,
            28,
            24,
            -28
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "Patel wants to buy a shirt. If his body size is 25cm, what available shirt may fit him?",
        "answer": 35,
        "options": [
            27,
            35,
            35,
            35
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 2 mat, 53 table, 8 flower vase, 1 bed bugs, and 10 dog? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 54,
        "options": [
            276,
            0,
            54,
            383
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 26000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 536000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            48507.463,
            957,
            955,
            624
        ],
        "answer": 48507.463
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            21,
            -21,
            19,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 21
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 empty boxes, 20 bed, 15 refrigerator, 8 dog, and 7 pigeons? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 49,
        "options": [
            50,
            23,
            34,
            49
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 6 flower vase, 42 tubelight, 6 refrigerator, 2 dog, and 12 plants? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            48,
            15,
            8,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Peters wants to buy a pair of shorts. If his waist size is 26cm, what available pair of shorts may fit him?",
        "answer": 31,
        "options": [
            23,
            21,
            31,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $5 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional half mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 15.3 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            250,
            33.6,
            152,
            73
        ],
        "answer": 33.6
    },
    {
        "question": "If cow can eat 29 lemons , how many lemons can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 21,
        "options": [
            29,
            21,
            50,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Ice Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            3,
            12,
            4,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Black began counting from 0. She skip-counted by six's. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 516,
        "options": [
            517,
            516,
            0,
            518
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Myers wants to buy a Belt. If his waist size is 28cm, what available Belt may fit him?",
        "answer": 35,
        "options": [
            23,
            35,
            10,
            26
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Wood wants to buy a shirt. If his body size is 22cm, what available shirt may fit him?",
        "answer": 27,
        "options": [
            23,
            27,
            4,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 23 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            15,
            -15,
            4,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 3 couch, 77 flower vase, 90 empty boxes, 2 bed bugs, and 15 cat? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 148,
        "options": [
            148,
            0,
            387,
            235
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Rivera wants to put a book in a bag.The bag is 5.291 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the book?",
        "answer": 3.01,
        "options": [
            3.11,
            3.01,
            5.291,
            30.099999999999998
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a child can eat 28 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a dog eat?",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            28,
            15,
            43,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international volley ball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 6 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            10,
            0,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $7 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional half mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 42.6 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            397,
            213,
            90.2,
            490
        ],
        "answer": 90.2
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 6 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            9,
            4,
            10,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international squash game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            -1,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 empty boxes, 9 couch, 71 sofa, 12 algae spots, and 2 plants? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 13,
        "options": [
            68,
            24,
            13,
            76
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 12000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 342000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            746,
            689,
            540,
            0.035
        ],
        "answer": 0.035
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 empty boxes, 9 couch, 71 sofa, 12 algae spots, and 2 plants? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 94,
        "options": [
            107,
            103,
            95,
            94
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 23 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -27,
            23,
            4,
            27
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 15000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 145000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            353,
            103448.276,
            220,
            29
        ],
        "answer": 103448.276
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international volley ball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 3 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            3,
            10,
            0,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 5 feet by 10 feet?",
        "options": [
            2428,
            7601,
            7200,
            6163
        ],
        "answer": 7200
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 empty boxes, 95 bed, 83 sofa, 4 pigeons, and 3 plants? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            77,
            187,
            100
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "White wants to buy a a ring. If his finger circumference is 30cm, what available a ring may fit him?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            24,
            33,
            42,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 20. When the sun is at 163 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 85,
        "options": [
            18,
            16,
            8,
            85
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $10 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-tenth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 8.6 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            417,
            409,
            193,
            78.4
        ],
        "answer": 78.4
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 flower vase, 14 chair, 32 cycles, 14 pigeons, and 14 bed bugs? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            62,
            67,
            14,
            82
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 fan, 31 tubelight, 34 pair of shoes, 3 cockroaches, and 1 bed bugs? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 59,
        "options": [
            130,
            0,
            341,
            59
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 7 cycles, 45 sofa, 68 chair, 11 plants, and 8 bed bugs? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 120,
        "options": [
            79,
            52,
            121,
            120
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If pigeon can eat 6 chocolates , how many chocolates can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 26,
        "options": [
            6,
            26,
            32,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            4,
            28,
            24,
            -28
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            15,
            -26,
            26,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "If snail can eat 7 cake , how many cake can a pigeon eat?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            7,
            9,
            16,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 17 years old in the year 1320.In his greatest win, he looted 169198821 of 1356931224 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1303,
            1545,
            1875,
            1813
        ],
        "answer": 1303
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -17,
            4,
            17,
            13
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international footbal game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            6,
            10,
            21,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -17,
            4,
            17,
            13
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international volley ball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            4,
            0,
            3,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Friday and returns to the bank 5months later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Sunday",
        "options": [
            "Sunday",
            "Friday",
            "Saturday",
            "Saturday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Sunday and returns to the bank 8months later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Thursday",
        "options": [
            "Thursday",
            "tuesday",
            "Sunday",
            "tuesday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 fan, 31 tubelight, 34 pair of shoes, 3 cockroaches, and 1 bed bugs? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 80,
        "options": [
            37,
            81,
            46,
            80
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Diaz wants to buy a hoodie. If his chest size is 13cm, what available hoodie may fit him?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            24,
            14,
            13,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of Ritvik increased from 583 per month to 908 per month while the salary of Myra increased from 710 to 856 and of Wagner increased from 773 to 824 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Wagner",
        "options": [
            "Ritvik",
            "Myra",
            "Wagner",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Lewis wants to put a book in a bag.The bag is 4.952 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the book?",
        "answer": 1.84,
        "options": [
            1.9400000000000002,
            4.952,
            1.84,
            18.400000000000002
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 broom, 10 sofa, 90 tubelight, 9 cat, and 12 algae spots? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 115,
        "options": [
            116,
            115,
            25,
            99
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Sunday and returns to the bank 9296days later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Sunday",
        "options": [
            "Wednesday",
            "tuesday",
            "Sunday",
            "Friday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 48 ohms and 19 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 3 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            19,
            67,
            3,
            48
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            19,
            9,
            10,
            -19
        ],
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 4 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            6,
            7,
            6,
            21
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 88 miles in 10 hours and 10 minutes?",
        "options": [
            9.647246863480458,
            9.373858969066873,
            8.590448071118207,
            0.23081967213114757
        ],
        "answer": 0.23081967213114757
    },
    {
        "question": "If man can eat 88 grapes , how many grapes can a dog eat?",
        "answer": 58,
        "options": [
            88,
            58,
            146,
            30
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international footbal game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 3 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            11,
            10,
            5,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of Mohammed increased from 637 per month to 958 per month while the salary of Coleman increased from 549 to 701 and of Roberts increased from 620 to 860 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Roberts",
        "options": [
            "Mohammed",
            "Coleman",
            "Roberts",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Gonzalez wants to buy a hat. If his head circumference is 11cm, what available hat may fit him?",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            12,
            8,
            4,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international rugby game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 5 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            14,
            21,
            15,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 empty boxes, 9 couch, 71 sofa, 12 algae spots, and 2 plants? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            14,
            15,
            83,
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Reyansh began counting from 0. She skip-counted by twos. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 166,
        "options": [
            168,
            166,
            167,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 35000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 956000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            56,
            528,
            575,
            36.611
        ],
        "answer": 36.611
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 4 couch, 18 tubelight, 51 broom, 14 snail, and 9 cat? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            91,
            95,
            88
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 refrigerator, 47 empty boxes, 12 bed, 2 cat, and 5 bed bugs? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 67,
        "options": [
            14,
            68,
            67,
            55
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Saanvi began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fives. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 435,
        "options": [
            436,
            437,
            435,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 broom, 5 empty boxes, 53 table, 13 bed bugs, and 1 trees? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 59,
        "options": [
            66,
            60,
            6,
            59
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 49 pints. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 4/10 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            19.6,
            38,
            66,
            97
        ],
        "answer": 19.6
    },
    {
        "question": "Medina wants to buy a Phone. If his Palm size is 38cm, what available Phone may fit him?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            14,
            45,
            33,
            30
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 17 years old in the year 1153.In his greatest win, he looted 821783639 of 3080400799 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1614,
            1136,
            1440,
            1840
        ],
        "answer": 1136
    },
    {
        "question": "If pigeon can eat 7 watermelon , how many watermelon can a dog eat?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            7,
            22,
            29,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of Shanaya increased from 408 per month to 605 per month while the salary of Boyd increased from 875 to 900 and of Sullivan increased from 330 to 416 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Sullivan",
        "options": [
            "Shanaya",
            "Boyd",
            "Sullivan",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Boxing game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            0,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 67 miles in 8 hours and 37 minutes?",
        "options": [
            7.788596342211324,
            7.601445117958386,
            9.500337728168013,
            0.12959381044487428
        ],
        "answer": 0.12959381044487428
    },
    {
        "question": "A family is going on a vacation to Chicago in a bus. There were 7 men, 9 women, 9 children of less than 10 years, 5 old people of age above 60 years.How many of the people can drive??",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            120,
            30,
            0,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 10 years old in the year 1425.In his greatest win, he looted 652651653 of 6628306191 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1602,
            1415,
            1777,
            1885
        ],
        "answer": 1415
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $4 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-sixth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 21.9 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            486,
            452,
            288,
            129.4
        ],
        "answer": 129.4
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 flower vase, 14 chair, 32 cycles, 14 pigeons, and 14 bed bugs? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 13,
        "options": [
            63,
            84,
            13,
            63
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Friday and returns to the bank 10months later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Wednesday",
        "options": [
            "tuesday",
            "Sunday",
            "Monday",
            "Wednesday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 23 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            15,
            -15,
            4,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 36 gallons. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 5/9 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            20.0,
            91,
            98,
            97
        ],
        "answer": 20.0
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 16 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            16,
            6,
            10,
            -16
        ],
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            20,
            -30,
            30,
            10
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "If man can eat 18 watermelon , how many watermelon can a cat eat?",
        "answer": 13,
        "options": [
            18,
            13,
            31,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Table-Tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            4,
            0,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international squash game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            0,
            0,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 72 miles in 9 hours and 22 minutes?",
        "options": [
            7.686832740213523,
            4.697060469411261,
            7.779063298570056,
            9.79320955678973
        ],
        "answer": 7.686832740213523
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 7 years old in the year 1324.In his greatest win, he looted 169327656 of 4195264474 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1317,
            1783,
            1794,
            1661
        ],
        "answer": 1317
    },
    {
        "question": "If pigeon can eat 52 grapes , how many grapes can a ants eat?",
        "answer": 92,
        "options": [
            52,
            92,
            144,
            40
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 23 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            9,
            -9,
            4,
            5
        ],
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "If pigeon can eat 16 apples , how many apples can a giraffee eat?",
        "answer": 21,
        "options": [
            16,
            21,
            37,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Wells wants to put a Pizza Box in a Refrigerator.The Refrigerator is 9.273 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Pizza Box?",
        "answer": 2.99,
        "options": [
            29.900000000000002,
            3.0900000000000003,
            9.273,
            2.99
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 68 miles in 8 hours and 17 minutes?",
        "options": [
            0.2189134808853119,
            4.720320984259706,
            7.931931954722066,
            2.430228266644613
        ],
        "answer": 0.2189134808853119
    },
    {
        "question": "Ananya wants to put a Pizza Box in a Refrigerator.The Refrigerator is 6.275 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Pizza Box?",
        "answer": 3.51,
        "options": [
            35.099999999999994,
            6.275,
            3.51,
            3.61
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            11,
            -29,
            29,
            18
        ],
        "answer": 29
    },
    {
        "question": "If dog can eat 91 grapes , how many grapes can a giraffee eat?",
        "answer": 153,
        "options": [
            91,
            153,
            244,
            62
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international squash game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            -1,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 tubelight, 41 refrigerator, 93 mat, 8 cockroaches, and 8 human beings? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 144,
        "options": [
            51,
            144,
            145,
            101
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Walker wants to put a fruit in a basket.The basket is 8.5 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the fruit?",
        "answer": 6.35,
        "options": [
            6.449999999999999,
            6.35,
            63.5,
            8.5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 flower vase, 14 chair, 32 cycles, 14 pigeons, and 14 bed bugs? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            25,
            28,
            46,
            29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            20,
            14,
            6,
            -20
        ],
        "answer": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            1,
            3,
            0,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $4 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-eighth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 48.8 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            448,
            386,
            386.4,
            457
        ],
        "answer": 386.4
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $72 to the charity and a total of $11672 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was quadrupled?",
        "options": [
            162,
            565,
            201,
            878
        ],
        "answer": 162
    },
    {
        "question": "Anaya began counting from 0. She skip-counted by six's. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 414,
        "options": [
            414,
            415,
            0,
            416
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 5 years old in the year 1879.In his greatest win, he looted 278576379 of 9551297534 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins are remaining in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            278576379,
            9829873913,
            9272721155,
            9551297534
        ],
        "answer": 9272721155
    },
    {
        "question": "Castro wants to buy a pair of shoes. If his foot size is 32cm, what available pair of shoes may fit him?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            39,
            27,
            8,
            26
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 3 mat, 74 broom, 79 flower vase, 11 algae spots, and 15 cockroaches? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 156,
        "options": [
            77,
            156,
            157,
            90
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 broom, 5 empty boxes, 53 table, 13 bed bugs, and 1 trees? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 59,
        "options": [
            59,
            66,
            6,
            60
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international squash game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            -1,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 13 years old in the year 1505.In his greatest win, he looted 783444133 of 4160939907 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins are remaining in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            783444133,
            4944384040,
            4160939907,
            3377495774
        ],
        "answer": 3377495774
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 4 couch, 3 broom, 73 bed, 1 plants, and 13 cat? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            14,
            15,
            7,
            74
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 26 ohms and 20 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 8 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            8,
            520,
            46,
            0,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 couch, 43 table, 77 mat, 13 cockroaches, and 6 fungi spots? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 56,
        "options": [
            246,
            0,
            232,
            56
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Patterson wants to buy a Phone. If his Palm size is 32cm, what available Phone may fit him?",
        "answer": 33,
        "options": [
            33,
            23,
            3,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Bailey began counting from 0. She skip-counted by threes. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            12,
            14,
            0,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $28 to the charity and a total of $8576 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was quadrupled?",
        "options": [
            306,
            393,
            422,
            130
        ],
        "answer": 306
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international rugby game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 14 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 13,
        "options": [
            1,
            13,
            12,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 40 ohms and 39 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 24 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            39,
            79,
            24,
            53,
            1560
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 16 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            16,
            6,
            10,
            -16
        ],
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 2 tubelight, 69 flower vase, 77 broom, 8 human beings, and 7 fungi spots? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 148,
        "options": [
            85,
            149,
            148,
            71
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kelley wants to buy a cap. If his head circumference is 30cm, what available cap may fit him?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            8,
            41,
            34,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 4 feet by 3 feet?",
        "options": [
            2610,
            9056,
            7855,
            1728
        ],
        "answer": 1728
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -30,
            13,
            17,
            30
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 17 years old in the year 1519.In his greatest win, he looted 900951520 of 4127340844 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1502,
            1703,
            1603,
            1861
        ],
        "answer": 1502
    },
    {
        "question": "Simmons wants to buy a necklace. If his neck circumference is 24cm, what available necklace may fit him?",
        "answer": 26,
        "options": [
            26,
            14,
            12,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -30,
            13,
            17,
            30
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international squash game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            -1,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Anika wants to buy a Belt. If his waist size is 40cm, what available Belt may fit him?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            44,
            22,
            25,
            27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 6 pair of shoes, 88 couch, 24 tubelight, 13 dog, and 4 plants? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            124,
            108,
            121
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 6 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            23,
            1,
            -23,
            22
        ],
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 24 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            17,
            23,
            6,
            -23
        ],
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 15 years old in the year 1155.In his greatest win, he looted 331991280 of 360960493 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1319,
            1341,
            1140,
            1688
        ],
        "answer": 1140
    },
    {
        "question": "Advik began counting from 0. She skip-counted by nine's. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 396,
        "options": [
            396,
            0,
            397,
            398
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If ants can eat 97 grapes , how many grapes can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 124,
        "options": [
            97,
            124,
            221,
            27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Martinez began counting from 0. She skip-counted by twos. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 118,
        "options": [
            0,
            120,
            119,
            118
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kim wants to buy a pair of shoes. If his foot size is 17cm, what available pair of shoes may fit him?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            29,
            39,
            10,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $22 to the charity and a total of $13161 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was tripled?",
        "options": [
            485,
            741,
            598,
            382
        ],
        "answer": 598
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            20,
            14,
            6,
            -20
        ],
        "answer": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "If a child can eat 85 grapes , how many grapes can a dog eat?",
        "answer": 59,
        "options": [
            85,
            59,
            144,
            26
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 4 flower vase, 85 empty boxes, 30 mat, 9 crows, and 9 snail? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            18,
            39,
            19,
            89
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If elephant can eat 9 cake , how many cake can a pigeon eat?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            9,
            2,
            11,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ishaan wants to buy a shirt. If his body size is 26cm, what available shirt may fit him?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            40,
            27,
            25,
            42
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 99000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 262000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            739,
            863,
            377862.595,
            695
        ],
        "answer": 377862.595
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 4 flower vase, 85 empty boxes, 30 mat, 9 crows, and 9 snail? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 99,
        "options": [
            99,
            356,
            0,
            183
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -17,
            4,
            17,
            13
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            15,
            -26,
            26,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "Ryan wants to buy a pair of socks. If his foot size is 37cm, what available pair of socks may fit him?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            41,
            43,
            5,
            43
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Ice Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 5 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            5,
            4,
            0,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Tucker wants to put a car in a car parking space.The car parking space is 7.514 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the car?",
        "answer": 1.07,
        "options": [
            10.700000000000001,
            1.1700000000000002,
            7.514,
            1.07
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 couch, 15 flower vase, 55 refrigerator, 2 trees, and 13 bed bugs? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            41,
            30,
            43
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -17,
            4,
            17,
            13
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            18,
            -26,
            8,
            26
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "Green wants to buy a cap. If his head circumference is 16cm, what available cap may fit him?",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            17,
            13,
            5,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ward wants to put a Car in a Garage.The Garage is 9.235 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Car?",
        "answer": 7.51,
        "options": [
            75.1,
            7.51,
            7.609999999999999,
            9.235
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $6 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional quarter mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 7.6 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            200,
            240,
            378,
            32.4
        ],
        "answer": 32.4
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 17 years old in the year 1320.In his greatest win, he looted 169198821 of 1356931224 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1303,
            1545,
            1875,
            1813
        ],
        "answer": 1303
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 mat, 46 refrigerator, 56 pair of shoes, 14 pigeons, and 10 crows? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            24,
            25,
            70,
            51
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 46000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 935000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            754,
            273,
            0.049,
            727
        ],
        "answer": 0.049
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international basketball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 4 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            4,
            10,
            3,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            20,
            -30,
            30,
            10
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "Campbell wants to put a phone in a pocket.The pocket is 9.106 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the phone?",
        "answer": 2.28,
        "options": [
            22.799999999999997,
            9.106,
            2.28,
            2.38
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            18,
            -26,
            8,
            26
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 13 ohms and 19 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 9 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            32,
            0,
            9,
            247
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 fan, 14 tubelight, 29 broom, 13 cat, and 14 pigeons? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 27,
        "options": [
            28,
            19,
            27,
            42
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a child can eat 11 watermelon , how many watermelon can a man eat?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            11,
            20,
            31,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 82. When the sun is at 76 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 21,
        "options": [
            21,
            100,
            82,
            106
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Green wants to put a house in a street.The street is 3.06 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the house?",
        "answer": 1.63,
        "options": [
            1.73,
            16.299999999999997,
            3.06,
            1.63
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 11 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            8,
            1,
            -9,
            9
        ],
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 11 years old in the year 1807.In his greatest win, he looted 154847298 of 3500278904 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins were actually present in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            3500278904,
            3655126202,
            154847298,
            -3345431606
        ],
        "answer": 3500278904
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 3 feet by 6 feet?",
        "options": [
            2592,
            4031,
            3756,
            3621
        ],
        "answer": 2592
    },
    {
        "question": "Akshara wants to buy a pair of shoes. If his foot size is 17cm, what available pair of shoes may fit him?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            31,
            4,
            42,
            26
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 4 feet by 6 feet?",
        "options": [
            3536,
            1323,
            5338,
            3456
        ],
        "answer": 3456
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 4 couch, 18 tubelight, 51 broom, 14 snail, and 9 cat? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 73,
        "options": [
            22,
            74,
            73,
            65
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 15 years old in the year 1841.In his greatest win, he looted 717984761 of 7047515081 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1826,
            1863,
            1840,
            1877
        ],
        "answer": 1826
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 53 gallons. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 4/10 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            85,
            44,
            34,
            21.2
        ],
        "answer": 21.2
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 62 miles in 10 hours and 52 minutes?",
        "options": [
            0.1521472392638037,
            9.145903582759008,
            4.508975107895704,
            8.573234426456345
        ],
        "answer": 0.1521472392638037
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 23 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            9,
            -9,
            4,
            5
        ],
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "If man can eat 18 lemons , how many lemons can a cow eat?",
        "answer": 30,
        "options": [
            18,
            30,
            48,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international basketball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 5 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            9,
            0,
            5,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 17 years old in the year 1519.In his greatest win, he looted 900951520 of 4127340844 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1502,
            1703,
            1603,
            1861
        ],
        "answer": 1502
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 12 sofa, 28 bed, 16 empty boxes, 7 trees, and 13 crows? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 56,
        "options": [
            23,
            56,
            57,
            40
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 20 years old in the year 1807.In his greatest win, he looted 413887177 of 4277717307 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins are remaining in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            3863830130,
            4691604484,
            413887177,
            4277717307
        ],
        "answer": 3863830130
    },
    {
        "question": "Anika wants to buy a Hand glove. If his Palm-size is 39cm, what available Hand glove may fit him?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            33,
            27,
            44,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 48 ohms and 19 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 2 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            67,
            48,
            2,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international baseball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 8 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            14,
            0,
            5,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 10 years old in the year 1796.In his greatest win, he looted 126588341 of 2072840991 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1810,
            1848,
            1786,
            1819
        ],
        "answer": 1786
    },
    {
        "question": "Krishna wants to buy a pair of socks. If his foot size is 8cm, what available pair of socks may fit him?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            28,
            11,
            10,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international baseball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 5 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            15,
            6,
            2,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 3 couch, 77 flower vase, 90 empty boxes, 2 bed bugs, and 15 cat? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 138,
        "options": [
            174,
            138,
            172,
            171
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 17 years old in the year 1320.In his greatest win, he looted 169198821 of 1356931224 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1303,
            1545,
            1875,
            1813
        ],
        "answer": 1303
    },
    {
        "question": "If cow can eat 25 apples , how many apples can a dog eat?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            25,
            24,
            49,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Ice Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 6 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            0,
            4,
            11,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 42000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 677000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            974,
            295,
            0.062,
            585
        ],
        "answer": 0.062
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 tubelight, 69 pair of shoes, 71 couch, 15 human beings, and 5 crows? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 151,
        "options": [
            151,
            152,
            80,
            86
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Aadhya wants to buy a pair of shorts. If his waist size is 24cm, what available pair of shorts may fit him?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            22,
            44,
            45,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 100 miles in 10 hours and 31 minutes?",
        "options": [
            1.2436096800110668,
            9.508716323296355,
            8.434321769379247,
            8.547540602126572
        ],
        "answer": 9.508716323296355
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 4 flower vase, 85 empty boxes, 30 mat, 9 crows, and 9 snail? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            72,
            103,
            22
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Marshall wants to buy a hoodie. If his chest size is 17cm, what available hoodie may fit him?",
        "answer": 30,
        "options": [
            17,
            24,
            17,
            30
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $46 to the charity and a total of $8547 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was tripled?",
        "options": [
            550,
            438,
            396,
            185
        ],
        "answer": 185
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 91 miles in 2 hours and 11 minutes?",
        "options": [
            2.6375866562137418,
            0.6946564885496184,
            1.4831065957699887,
            3.649833101586596
        ],
        "answer": 0.6946564885496184
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Ice Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            5,
            4,
            11,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international rugby game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 15 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            3,
            4,
            16,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 16 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            16,
            6,
            10,
            -16
        ],
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Boxing game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            0,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 6 ohms and 50 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 6 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            56,
            6,
            50,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hoffman wants to buy a pair of shoes. If his foot size is 15cm, what available pair of shoes may fit him?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            41,
            34,
            41,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 24 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            17,
            23,
            6,
            -23
        ],
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "Richardson wants to buy a necklace. If his neck circumference is 8cm, what available necklace may fit him?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            24,
            40,
            20,
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 86 miles in 6 hours and 39 minutes?",
        "options": [
            1.5301075201255108,
            9.536844373720681,
            0.34486215538847115,
            7.2401405184874
        ],
        "answer": 0.34486215538847115
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 11 ohms and 49 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 8 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            11,
            8,
            49,
            60
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Table-Tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            0,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 mat, 46 refrigerator, 56 pair of shoes, 14 pigeons, and 10 crows? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 107,
        "options": [
            107,
            70,
            51,
            108
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 4 feet by 1 feet?",
        "options": [
            576,
            5192,
            9789,
            6550
        ],
        "answer": 576
    },
    {
        "question": "Kelley wants to put a Pizza Box in a Refrigerator.The Refrigerator is 3.293 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Pizza Box?",
        "answer": 2.12,
        "options": [
            2.22,
            21.200000000000003,
            3.293,
            2.12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Boxing game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            0,
            -1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kph if you travel 23 miles in 2 hours and 15 minutes?",
        "options": [
            7.70424979146267,
            5.541361783637348,
            16.355555555555558,
            9.099517695475884
        ],
        "answer": 16.355555555555558
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Wednesday and returns to the bank 3months later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Thursday",
        "options": [
            "Thursday",
            "Wednesday",
            "Sunday",
            "Friday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 15 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -26,
            19,
            7,
            26
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 7 years old in the year 1324.In his greatest win, he looted 169327656 of 4195264474 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1317,
            1783,
            1794,
            1661
        ],
        "answer": 1317
    },
    {
        "question": "Adams wants to put a Car in a Garage.The Garage is 7.155 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Car?",
        "answer": 5.44,
        "options": [
            5.54,
            54.400000000000006,
            5.44,
            7.155
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 fan, 14 tubelight, 29 broom, 13 cat, and 14 pigeons? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 33,
        "options": [
            33,
            60,
            62,
            65
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If cat can eat 17 lemons , how many lemons can a snail eat?",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            17,
            14,
            31,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ananya earns $8 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $1 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Ananya was paid $2799, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            170,
            325,
            313,
            322
        ],
        "answer": 322
    },
    {
        "question": "Rose wants to buy a a ring. If his finger circumference is 13cm, what available a ring may fit him?",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            13,
            7,
            15,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Cox began counting from 0. She skip-counted by eights. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 168,
        "options": [
            168,
            170,
            169,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 46 miles in 6 hours and 32 minutes?",
        "options": [
            7.040816326530613,
            1.2065209800806818,
            7.71708199453621,
            9.389690989561945
        ],
        "answer": 7.040816326530613
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 94000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 584000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            904,
            160.959,
            120,
            423
        ],
        "answer": 160.959
    },
    {
        "question": "Hawkins wants to buy a Phone. If his Palm size is 38cm, what available Phone may fit him?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            36,
            3,
            44,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Myers wants to put a phone in a pocket.The pocket is 3.189 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the phone?",
        "answer": 2.11,
        "options": [
            2.11,
            2.21,
            21.099999999999998,
            3.189
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $74 to the charity and a total of $5546 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was doubled?",
        "options": [
            74,
            171,
            520,
            908
        ],
        "answer": 74
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international squash game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            -1,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 88 miles in 2 hours and 38 minutes?",
        "options": [
            9.879693410518533,
            1.6563211674425458,
            0.5569620253164557,
            7.651915154781696
        ],
        "answer": 0.5569620253164557
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $8 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-tenth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 5.8 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            51.2,
            474,
            405,
            78
        ],
        "answer": 51.2
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 empty boxes, 20 bed, 15 refrigerator, 8 dog, and 7 pigeons? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 49,
        "options": [
            49,
            34,
            23,
            50
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $7 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-sixth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 33.8 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            362,
            285,
            203.8,
            213
        ],
        "answer": 203.8
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 24 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            13,
            -17,
            17,
            4
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 sofa, 82 tubelight, 76 mat, 7 plants, and 6 bed bugs? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 169,
        "options": [
            170,
            93,
            83,
            169
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $66 to the charity and a total of $16628 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was quadrupled?",
        "options": [
            692,
            434,
            622,
            251
        ],
        "answer": 251
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Ice Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 5 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            4,
            1,
            12,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 7 feet by 5 feet?",
        "options": [
            8318,
            9187,
            5040,
            9089
        ],
        "answer": 5040
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Thursday and returns to the bank 6674days later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Sunday",
        "options": [
            "Sunday",
            "Wednesday",
            "Monday",
            "tuesday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 26 miles in 9 hours and 6 minutes?",
        "options": [
            9.411478765993367,
            6.429102879855219,
            9.65488574969242,
            0.047619047619047616
        ],
        "answer": 0.047619047619047616
    },
    {
        "question": "West began counting from 0. She skip-counted by eights. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 640,
        "options": [
            0,
            641,
            640,
            642
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If snail can eat 12 chocolates , how many chocolates can a elephant eat?",
        "answer": 30,
        "options": [
            12,
            30,
            42,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            3,
            0,
            1,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 6 flower vase, 42 tubelight, 6 refrigerator, 2 dog, and 12 plants? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            341,
            362,
            11,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 mat, 26 cycles, 66 fan, 11 bed bugs, and 12 algae spots? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 102,
        "options": [
            36,
            102,
            77,
            103
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 75. When the sun is at 123 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            104,
            82,
            87,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 66 pints. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 4/7 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            64,
            89,
            72,
            37.71
        ],
        "answer": 37.71
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 6 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            7,
            -17,
            10,
            17
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Table-Tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            -1,
            0,
            4,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Badminton game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            -1,
            0,
            3,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $3 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional quarter mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 24.6 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            97.4,
            244,
            419,
            183
        ],
        "answer": 97.4
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Badminton game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            4,
            2,
            0,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kph if you travel 82 miles in 10 hours and 32 minutes?",
        "options": [
            1.5584832329767888,
            9.236498777214072,
            4.867550352770638,
            12.455696202531646
        ],
        "answer": 12.455696202531646
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 7 cycles, 45 sofa, 68 chair, 11 plants, and 8 bed bugs? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 120,
        "options": [
            120,
            79,
            52,
            121
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international golf game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            2,
            -1,
            0,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 24 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            13,
            -17,
            17,
            4
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            20,
            14,
            6,
            -20
        ],
        "answer": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 mat, 26 cycles, 66 fan, 11 bed bugs, and 12 algae spots? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 102,
        "options": [
            102,
            103,
            36,
            77
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Riya wants to buy a Belt. If his waist size is 5cm, what available Belt may fit him?",
        "answer": 13,
        "options": [
            13,
            10,
            4,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international basketball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 3 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            8,
            0,
            2,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $3 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-eighth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 30.1 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            235.8,
            340,
            318,
            467
        ],
        "answer": 235.8
    },
    {
        "question": "Tran wants to buy a pair of shoes. If his foot size is 18cm, what available pair of shoes may fit him?",
        "answer": 34,
        "options": [
            26,
            13,
            5,
            34
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hughes wants to buy a pair of socks. If his foot size is 21cm, what available pair of socks may fit him?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            6,
            33,
            35,
            45
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 11 years old in the year 1716.In his greatest win, he looted 836326661 of 8675669182 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1765,
            1760,
            1705,
            1764
        ],
        "answer": 1705
    },
    {
        "question": "If a child can eat 25 apples , how many apples can a elephant eat?",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            25,
            29,
            54,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            18,
            -26,
            8,
            26
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "If elephant can eat 8 cake , how many cake can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            8,
            4,
            12,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 25000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 518000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            13,
            420,
            48262.548,
            961
        ],
        "answer": 48262.548
    },
    {
        "question": "If a child can eat 24 apples , how many apples can a man eat?",
        "answer": 25,
        "options": [
            24,
            25,
            49,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If dog can eat 5 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            5,
            11,
            16,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 9 years old in the year 1316.In his greatest win, he looted 512422231 of 8523245106 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins are remaining in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            8523245106,
            512422231,
            8010822875,
            9035667337
        ],
        "answer": 8010822875
    },
    {
        "question": "Griffin wants to put a Table in a Room.The Room is 9.783 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Table?",
        "answer": 4.11,
        "options": [
            9.783,
            4.21,
            41.1,
            4.11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Aayan wants to buy a Hand glove. If his Palm-size is 10cm, what available Hand glove may fit him?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            37,
            12,
            5,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kabir wants to buy a a ring. If his finger circumference is 37cm, what available a ring may fit him?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            19,
            24,
            28,
            45
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Aadhya earns $5 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $4 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Aadhya was paid $1374, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            262,
            197,
            433,
            74
        ],
        "answer": 197
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 14 years old in the year 1810.In his greatest win, he looted 523242202 of 9660815474 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1796,
            1804,
            1893,
            1826
        ],
        "answer": 1796
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 13000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 220000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            712,
            59.091,
            657,
            106
        ],
        "answer": 59.091
    },
    {
        "question": "Vihaan wants to buy a pair of socks. If his foot size is 10cm, what available pair of socks may fit him?",
        "answer": 31,
        "options": [
            21,
            10,
            29,
            31
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 11 years old in the year 1329.In his greatest win, he looted 570410466 of 1547295181 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1370,
            1603,
            1318,
            1741
        ],
        "answer": 1318
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            19,
            9,
            10,
            -19
        ],
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 fan, 14 tubelight, 29 broom, 13 cat, and 14 pigeons? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 48,
        "options": [
            48,
            19,
            42,
            49
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Fernandez wants to put a house in a street.The street is 3.082 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the house?",
        "answer": 1.32,
        "options": [
            1.32,
            3.082,
            1.4200000000000002,
            13.200000000000001
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 1 broom, 5 empty boxes, 53 table, 13 bed bugs, and 1 trees? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            68,
            52,
            29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Campbell began counting from 0. She skip-counted by eights. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 704,
        "options": [
            704,
            705,
            706,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 16 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            21,
            22,
            -22,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 22
    },
    {
        "question": "If elephant can eat 14 grapes , how many grapes can a pigeon eat?",
        "answer": 64,
        "options": [
            14,
            64,
            78,
            50
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ford wants to buy a shirt. If his body size is 40cm, what available shirt may fit him?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            41,
            19,
            38,
            41
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a tuesday and returns to the bank 10months later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "tuesday",
        "options": [
            "Sunday",
            "Thursday",
            "tuesday",
            "Sunday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 65. When the sun is at 117 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 46,
        "options": [
            46,
            104,
            83,
            72
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 19 years old in the year 1308.In his greatest win, he looted 603538598 of 1360988150 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1474,
            1289,
            1747,
            1731
        ],
        "answer": 1289
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 broom, 10 sofa, 90 tubelight, 9 cat, and 12 algae spots? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            39,
            102,
            75
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 15 years old in the year 1841.In his greatest win, he looted 717984761 of 7047515081 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1826,
            1863,
            1840,
            1877
        ],
        "answer": 1826
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 10 years old in the year 1191.In his greatest win, he looted 921719987 of 3300307368 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins are remaining in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            921719987,
            2378587381,
            4222027355,
            3300307368
        ],
        "answer": 2378587381
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 2 flower vase, 85 table, 85 pair of shoes, 3 cat, and 9 crows? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            112,
            52,
            173
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hayes wants to buy a pair of pants. If his waist size is 31cm, what available pair of pants may fit him?",
        "answer": 34,
        "options": [
            34,
            31,
            8,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 couch, 74 cycles, 90 empty boxes, 5 bed bugs, and 14 snail? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 19,
        "options": [
            20,
            82,
            19,
            95
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 6 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            3,
            -24,
            24,
            21
        ],
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 3 couch, 77 flower vase, 90 empty boxes, 2 bed bugs, and 15 cat? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            92,
            18,
            17,
            80
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If snail can eat 80 grapes , how many grapes can a pigeon eat?",
        "answer": 132,
        "options": [
            80,
            132,
            212,
            52
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Chavez wants to buy a a ring. If his finger circumference is 18cm, what available a ring may fit him?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            5,
            15,
            16,
            28
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 12 fan, 97 tubelight, 86 empty boxes, 6 cat, and 10 trees? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 56,
        "options": [
            267,
            56,
            215,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of Ford increased from 597 per month to 646 per month while the salary of Perry increased from 476 to 534 and of Pranav increased from 460 to 491 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Pranav",
        "options": [
            "Ford",
            "Perry",
            "Pranav",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 47 miles in 8 hours and 54 minutes?",
        "options": [
            7.155681885892098,
            5.681749430054886,
            5.280898876404494,
            6.777114822136825
        ],
        "answer": 5.280898876404494
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 couch, 15 flower vase, 55 refrigerator, 2 trees, and 13 bed bugs? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            29,
            57,
            15,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international cricket game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 5 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            4,
            10,
            13,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a child can eat 24 chocolates , how many chocolates can a pigeon eat?",
        "answer": 19,
        "options": [
            24,
            19,
            43,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 sofa, 33 empty boxes, 13 bed, 2 bed bugs, and 15 fungi spots? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            41,
            17,
            15,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 2 tubelight, 69 flower vase, 77 broom, 8 human beings, and 7 fungi spots? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            71,
            85,
            16,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 10 mat, 26 cycles, 66 fan, 11 bed bugs, and 12 algae spots? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            23,
            36,
            77,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 18000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 598000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            521,
            750,
            0.03,
            778
        ],
        "answer": 0.03
    },
    {
        "question": "Ford wants to buy a necklace. If his neck circumference is 25cm, what available necklace may fit him?",
        "answer": 30,
        "options": [
            22,
            30,
            4,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Fox wants to buy a Hand glove. If his Palm-size is 8cm, what available Hand glove may fit him?",
        "answer": 35,
        "options": [
            12,
            23,
            14,
            35
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Mohammed wants to buy a pair of shorts. If his waist size is 31cm, what available pair of shorts may fit him?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            3,
            38,
            22,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If dog can eat 14 chocolates , how many chocolates can a cat eat?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            14,
            9,
            23,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Williams wants to buy a pair of pants. If his waist size is 11cm, what available pair of pants may fit him?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            44,
            30,
            33,
            28
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 couch, 66 flower vase, 15 cycles, 14 cat, and 15 dog? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            124,
            8,
            106,
            97
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 19 years old in the year 1794.In his greatest win, he looted 282246359 of 7759530043 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins were actually present in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            8041776402,
            7759530043,
            282246359,
            -7477283684
        ],
        "answer": 7759530043
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Monday and returns to the bank 4years later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Friday",
        "options": [
            "Friday",
            "Monday",
            "tuesday",
            "Sunday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            21,
            -21,
            19,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 21
    },
    {
        "question": "Olson wants to put a Table in a Room.The Room is 9.094 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Table?",
        "answer": 3.55,
        "options": [
            3.55,
            9.094,
            35.5,
            3.65
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Ice Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 6 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            12,
            0,
            6,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Moreno wants to buy a hat. If his head circumference is 21cm, what available hat may fit him?",
        "answer": 31,
        "options": [
            18,
            31,
            30,
            31
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 60. When the sun is at 42 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 107,
        "options": [
            45,
            50,
            44,
            107
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Cole wants to buy a hat. If his head circumference is 22cm, what available hat may fit him?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            24,
            20,
            9,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Tran wants to put a phone in a pocket.The pocket is 6.352 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the phone?",
        "answer": 2.35,
        "options": [
            2.45,
            6.352,
            23.5,
            2.35
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            4,
            10,
            22,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Krishna began counting from 0. She skip-counted by sevens. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 455,
        "options": [
            455,
            457,
            0,
            456
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A family is going on a vacation to Chicago in a bus. There were 9 men, 7 women, 3 children of less than 10 years, 9 old people of age above 60 years.How many of the people can drive??",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            116,
            28,
            0,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Carter wants to put a Statue in a River.The River is 8.691 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Statue?",
        "answer": 3.08,
        "options": [
            3.18,
            3.08,
            30.8,
            8.691
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 4 couch, 18 tubelight, 51 broom, 14 snail, and 9 cat? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 58,
        "options": [
            89,
            75,
            58,
            76
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 10 years old in the year 1425.In his greatest win, he looted 652651653 of 6628306191 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1602,
            1415,
            1777,
            1885
        ],
        "answer": 1415
    },
    {
        "question": "If cat can eat 18 chocolates , how many chocolates can a ants eat?",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            18,
            8,
            26,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $5 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-third mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 17.4 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            488,
            54.2,
            292,
            215
        ],
        "answer": 54.2
    },
    {
        "question": "Bryant wants to put a Card in a Envelope.The Envelope is 7.551 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Card?",
        "answer": 6.05,
        "options": [
            6.1499999999999995,
            60.5,
            6.05,
            7.551
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 11 years old in the year 1716.In his greatest win, he looted 836326661 of 8675669182 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1765,
            1760,
            1705,
            1764
        ],
        "answer": 1705
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international squash game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            2,
            0,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $28 to the charity and a total of $4154 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was doubled?",
        "options": [
            674,
            148,
            784,
            150
        ],
        "answer": 148
    },
    {
        "question": "A family is going on a vacation to Chicago in a bus. There were 4 men, 5 women, 9 children of less than 10 years, 2 old people of age above 60 years.How many of the people can drive??",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            105,
            20,
            0,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 20 years old in the year 1379.In his greatest win, he looted 943808329 of 4266480855 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins were actually present in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            -3322672526,
            943808329,
            4266480855,
            5210289184
        ],
        "answer": 4266480855
    },
    {
        "question": "Aarav wants to buy a hat. If his head circumference is 17cm, what available hat may fit him?",
        "answer": 21,
        "options": [
            2,
            9,
            19,
            21
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If dog can eat 15 lemons , how many lemons can a giraffee eat?",
        "answer": 27,
        "options": [
            15,
            27,
            42,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 refrigerator, 47 empty boxes, 12 bed, 2 cat, and 5 bed bugs? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            296,
            9,
            0,
            259
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 28000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 283000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            461,
            438,
            98.94,
            309
        ],
        "answer": 98.94
    },
    {
        "question": "Mitchell wants to put a Drawer in a Table.The Table is 3.332 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Drawer?",
        "answer": 2.31,
        "options": [
            23.1,
            3.332,
            2.41,
            2.31
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Nguyen wants to put a Table in a Room.The Room is 9.895 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Table?",
        "answer": 3.96,
        "options": [
            39.6,
            4.06,
            9.895,
            3.96
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $9 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional quarter mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 10.1 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            436,
            45.4,
            436,
            326
        ],
        "answer": 45.4
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            11,
            -29,
            29,
            18
        ],
        "answer": 29
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 flower vase, 46 refrigerator, 87 couch, 2 snail, and 14 bed bugs? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 67,
        "options": [
            157,
            155,
            151,
            67
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international footbal game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 8 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            0,
            9,
            22,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 10 years old in the year 1796.In his greatest win, he looted 126588341 of 2072840991 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1810,
            1848,
            1786,
            1819
        ],
        "answer": 1786
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international squash game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            0,
            2,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 32 ohms and 29 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 7 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            61,
            7,
            32,
            29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 11 ohms and 19 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 9 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            0,
            209,
            9,
            30,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $86 to the charity and a total of $5508 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was doubled?",
        "options": [
            366,
            64,
            248,
            54
        ],
        "answer": 64
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Table-Tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            3,
            2,
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Morales wants to buy a hoodie. If his chest size is 12cm, what available hoodie may fit him?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            19,
            20,
            28,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            20,
            14,
            6,
            -20
        ],
        "answer": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "If cat can eat 27 apples , how many apples can a pigeon eat?",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            27,
            14,
            41,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 12 fan, 97 tubelight, 86 empty boxes, 6 cat, and 10 trees? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            17,
            109,
            92,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Ice Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 3 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            8,
            2,
            3,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Thursday and returns to the bank 8818days later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "tuesday",
        "options": [
            "Saturday",
            "Monday",
            "tuesday",
            "Saturday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 66000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 413000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            858,
            197,
            159.806,
            705
        ],
        "answer": 159.806
    },
    {
        "question": "Martinez wants to buy a a ring. If his finger circumference is 22cm, what available a ring may fit him?",
        "answer": 32,
        "options": [
            32,
            32,
            27,
            30
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Table-Tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            0,
            3,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a child can eat 1 cake , how many cake can a man eat?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            1,
            2,
            3,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 1 feet by 9 feet?",
        "options": [
            5385,
            2545,
            2578,
            1296
        ],
        "answer": 1296
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 flower vase, 86 chair, 59 empty boxes, 13 human beings, and 3 trees? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            17,
            72,
            100,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            3,
            0,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "White wants to put a Car in a Garage.The Garage is 5.296 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Car?",
        "answer": 1.86,
        "options": [
            1.9600000000000002,
            5.296,
            1.86,
            18.6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If cow can eat 24 apples , how many apples can a man eat?",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            24,
            5,
            29,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $36 to the charity and a total of $13580 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was quadrupled?",
        "options": [
            330,
            377,
            562,
            660
        ],
        "answer": 377
    },
    {
        "question": "King wants to buy a necklace. If his neck circumference is 29cm, what available necklace may fit him?",
        "answer": 33,
        "options": [
            33,
            10,
            31,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international cricket game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 8 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            12,
            6,
            5,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If elephant can eat 8 cake , how many cake can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            8,
            4,
            12,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 20 years old in the year 1564.In his greatest win, he looted 818663478 of 5951938350 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1673,
            1544,
            1722,
            1709
        ],
        "answer": 1544
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 12 years old in the year 1515.In his greatest win, he looted 197779199 of 7602609956 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1858,
            1503,
            1828,
            1603
        ],
        "answer": 1503
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international volley ball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 4 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            0,
            5,
            10,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 flower vase, 42 empty boxes, 68 bed, 12 pigeons, and 15 cockroaches? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 86,
        "options": [
            253,
            291,
            86,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $6 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-tenth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 15.5 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            136.5,
            275,
            142,
            442
        ],
        "answer": 136.5
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 53 pints. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 3/6 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            94,
            29,
            26.5,
            14
        ],
        "answer": 26.5
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 4 feet by 8 feet?",
        "options": [
            6564,
            3608,
            4608,
            2074
        ],
        "answer": 4608
    },
    {
        "question": "Sai began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fours. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 344,
        "options": [
            345,
            0,
            346,
            344
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Moreno began counting from 0. She skip-counted by threes. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 165,
        "options": [
            0,
            166,
            167,
            165
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 23 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            9,
            -9,
            4,
            5
        ],
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "Roberts wants to put a Statue in a River.The River is 9.133 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Statue?",
        "answer": 4.74,
        "options": [
            47.400000000000006,
            4.84,
            4.74,
            9.133
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Taylor wants to put a book in a bag.The bag is 6.262 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the book?",
        "answer": 1.53,
        "options": [
            15.3,
            6.262,
            1.53,
            1.6300000000000001
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 7 cycles, 45 sofa, 68 chair, 11 plants, and 8 bed bugs? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 50,
        "options": [
            208,
            228,
            0,
            50
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 4 couch, 3 broom, 73 bed, 1 plants, and 13 cat? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            39,
            24,
            58,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If snail can eat 19 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a giraffee eat?",
        "answer": 27,
        "options": [
            19,
            27,
            46,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 51 miles in 10 hours and 56 minutes?",
        "options": [
            3.878490776824666,
            4.664634146341464,
            7.006938854743349,
            6.564935309362003
        ],
        "answer": 4.664634146341464
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 5 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -25,
            16,
            25,
            9
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 72. When the sun is at 127 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 32,
        "options": [
            32,
            106,
            81,
            81
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $72 to the charity and a total of $17676 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was quadrupled?",
        "options": [
            842,
            26,
            245,
            243
        ],
        "answer": 245
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 23 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -27,
            23,
            4,
            27
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 12 years old in the year 1693.In his greatest win, he looted 788950713 of 9490956965 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1685,
            1850,
            1681,
            1791
        ],
        "answer": 1681
    },
    {
        "question": "Hunt wants to buy a pair of pants. If his waist size is 26cm, what available pair of pants may fit him?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            9,
            19,
            45,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Sunday and returns to the bank 11years later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Thursday",
        "options": [
            "Sunday",
            "Saturday",
            "Friday",
            "Thursday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $10 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-sixth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 13.6 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            148,
            135,
            85.6,
            109
        ],
        "answer": 85.6
    },
    {
        "question": "Patterson wants to buy a shirt. If his body size is 13cm, what available shirt may fit him?",
        "answer": 34,
        "options": [
            34,
            10,
            20,
            31
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Grant wants to buy a a ring. If his finger circumference is 28cm, what available a ring may fit him?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            14,
            39,
            23,
            43
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Romero wants to buy a Belt. If his waist size is 16cm, what available Belt may fit him?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            28,
            16,
            11,
            22
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 10 feet by 9 feet?",
        "options": [
            5207,
            7398,
            6399,
            12960
        ],
        "answer": 12960
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 23 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            15,
            -15,
            4,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            11,
            -29,
            29,
            18
        ],
        "answer": 29
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 5 years old in the year 1321.In his greatest win, he looted 989716676 of 1025991996 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins were actually present in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            2015708672,
            -36275320,
            989716676,
            1025991996
        ],
        "answer": 1025991996
    },
    {
        "question": "Elliott wants to put a Drawer in a Table.The Table is 4.905 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Drawer?",
        "answer": 2.2,
        "options": [
            22.0,
            2.2,
            4.905,
            2.3000000000000003
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 6 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            23,
            1,
            -23,
            22
        ],
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of Coleman increased from 565 per month to 577 per month while the salary of Weaver increased from 546 to 665 and of Reyes increased from 623 to 627 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Reyes",
        "options": [
            "Coleman",
            "Weaver",
            "Reyes",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 6 flower vase, 42 tubelight, 6 refrigerator, 2 dog, and 12 plants? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            55,
            68,
            22
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a tuesday and returns to the bank 4903days later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Friday",
        "options": [
            "Wednesday",
            "Friday",
            "Thursday",
            "Wednesday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 sofa, 82 tubelight, 76 mat, 7 plants, and 6 bed bugs? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            145,
            182,
            81
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ishaan wants to put a car in a car parking space.The car parking space is 9.018 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the car?",
        "answer": 2.13,
        "options": [
            2.13,
            9.018,
            2.23,
            21.299999999999997
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If man can eat 12 chocolates , how many chocolates can a dog eat?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            12,
            10,
            22,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If giraffee can eat 25 apples , how many apples can a pigeon eat?",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            25,
            18,
            43,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Dunn wants to put a picture in a frame.The frame is 3.162 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the picture?",
        "answer": 1.51,
        "options": [
            1.51,
            3.162,
            15.1,
            1.61
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Ice Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            5,
            2,
            4,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 24 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            13,
            -17,
            17,
            4
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "Vivaan wants to put a Card in a Envelope.The Envelope is 9.721 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Card?",
        "answer": 7.73,
        "options": [
            9.721,
            7.73,
            7.83,
            77.30000000000001
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Aadhya wants to buy a Belt. If his waist size is 18cm, what available Belt may fit him?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            22,
            4,
            9,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Mason wants to buy a hat. If his head circumference is 6cm, what available hat may fit him?",
        "answer": 34,
        "options": [
            14,
            22,
            34,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ramos began counting from 0. She skip-counted by twos. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 170,
        "options": [
            170,
            171,
            172,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 15 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -26,
            19,
            7,
            26
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "If ants can eat 5 cake , how many cake can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            5,
            6,
            11,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            19,
            9,
            10,
            -19
        ],
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international rugby game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 14 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            20,
            10,
            11,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 93 miles in 8 hours and 28 minutes?",
        "options": [
            2.5866068499614916,
            10.984251968503937,
            9.427006031147602,
            4.058010525847899
        ],
        "answer": 10.984251968503937
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 23 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            15,
            -15,
            4,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $4 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional half mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 44.6 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            91.2,
            486,
            122,
            264
        ],
        "answer": 91.2
    },
    {
        "question": "Arnold earns $10 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $1 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Arnold was paid $4460, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            488,
            190,
            414,
            141
        ],
        "answer": 414
    },
    {
        "question": "Ford wants to put a chocolate in a jar.The jar is 7.429 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the chocolate?",
        "answer": 2.5,
        "options": [
            25.0,
            2.6,
            2.5,
            7.429
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 20 years old in the year 1564.In his greatest win, he looted 818663478 of 5951938350 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1673,
            1544,
            1722,
            1709
        ],
        "answer": 1544
    },
    {
        "question": "If cow can eat 184 grapes , how many grapes can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 63,
        "options": [
            184,
            63,
            247,
            121
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Gordon wants to buy a Phone. If his Palm size is 10cm, what available Phone may fit him?",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            12,
            5,
            11,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a child can eat 14 apples , how many apples can a elephant eat?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            14,
            16,
            30,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Aarav wants to buy a pair of pants. If his waist size is 13cm, what available pair of pants may fit him?",
        "answer": 32,
        "options": [
            21,
            32,
            8,
            25
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If cow can eat 73 grapes , how many grapes can a cat eat?",
        "answer": 60,
        "options": [
            73,
            60,
            133,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            21,
            -21,
            19,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 21
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of Kyra increased from 322 per month to 932 per month while the salary of Murphy increased from 440 to 855 and of Bell increased from 734 to 796 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Bell",
        "options": [
            "Kyra",
            "Murphy",
            "Bell",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 15 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -26,
            19,
            7,
            26
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 23 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            9,
            -9,
            4,
            5
        ],
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 mat, 46 refrigerator, 56 pair of shoes, 14 pigeons, and 10 crows? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            52,
            35,
            33
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international basketball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            0,
            5,
            4,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            1,
            3,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Boyd wants to put a phone in a pocket.The pocket is 6.945 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the phone?",
        "answer": 2.28,
        "options": [
            22.799999999999997,
            2.28,
            2.38,
            6.945
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 couch, 27 chair, 12 cycles, 10 plants, and 13 cockroaches? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            32,
            45,
            22,
            44
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 10 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            15,
            6,
            5,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 23 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -27,
            23,
            4,
            27
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 couch, 27 chair, 12 cycles, 10 plants, and 13 cockroaches? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            59,
            13,
            64
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Atharva wants to buy a a ring. If his finger circumference is 15cm, what available a ring may fit him?",
        "answer": 32,
        "options": [
            12,
            2,
            25,
            32
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sullivan wants to put a Car in a Garage.The Garage is 8.446 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Car?",
        "answer": 1.62,
        "options": [
            16.200000000000003,
            8.446,
            1.7200000000000002,
            1.62
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Aayan wants to buy a hoodie. If his chest size is 33cm, what available hoodie may fit him?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            40,
            4,
            22,
            36
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 2 mat, 53 table, 8 flower vase, 1 bed bugs, and 10 dog? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            11,
            12,
            55,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If giraffee can eat 29 apples , how many apples can a ants eat?",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            29,
            11,
            40,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            4,
            28,
            24,
            -28
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 23 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            9,
            -9,
            4,
            5
        ],
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 20 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -30,
            11,
            30,
            19
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "Daniels wants to put a Drawer in a Table.The Table is 9.931 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Drawer?",
        "answer": 5.26,
        "options": [
            5.359999999999999,
            5.26,
            9.931,
            52.599999999999994
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international cricket game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            9,
            8,
            10,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international basketball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 5 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            2,
            1,
            8,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international baseball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 7 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            2,
            4,
            5,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 34000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 199000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            550,
            0.171,
            955,
            133
        ],
        "answer": 0.171
    },
    {
        "question": "Rodriguez wants to put a fruit in a basket.The basket is 8.361 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the fruit?",
        "answer": 5.61,
        "options": [
            5.61,
            8.361,
            56.1,
            5.71
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 6 years old in the year 1162.In his greatest win, he looted 35569691 of 175878297 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1156,
            1858,
            1223,
            1849
        ],
        "answer": 1156
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $8 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-seventh mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 17.5 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            123.5,
            132,
            371,
            128
        ],
        "answer": 123.5
    },
    {
        "question": "Vivaan wants to buy a hoodie. If his chest size is 40cm, what available hoodie may fit him?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            43,
            43,
            30,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 89 miles in 5 hours and 10 minutes?",
        "options": [
            9.09857686530451,
            0.4593548387096774,
            9.660344092305897,
            5.788409403265946
        ],
        "answer": 0.4593548387096774
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            20,
            -30,
            30,
            10
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 flower vase, 46 refrigerator, 87 couch, 2 snail, and 14 bed bugs? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            16,
            89,
            17,
            54
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international footbal game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 2 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            14,
            9,
            9,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 5 years old in the year 1703.In his greatest win, he looted 422809184 of 4467812818 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many of them are transferred to Jordan city??",
        "options": [
            4467812818,
            4890622002,
            4045003634,
            422809184
        ],
        "answer": 422809184
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 flower vase, 46 refrigerator, 87 couch, 2 snail, and 14 bed bugs? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 141,
        "options": [
            141,
            54,
            89,
            142
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international volley ball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 4 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            4,
            3,
            8,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Darsh began counting from 0. She skip-counted by nine's. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 477,
        "options": [
            479,
            478,
            0,
            477
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Coleman wants to put a chocolate in a jar.The jar is 5.497 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the chocolate?",
        "answer": 3.74,
        "options": [
            37.400000000000006,
            3.8400000000000003,
            5.497,
            3.74
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Crawford wants to buy a a ring. If his finger circumference is 13cm, what available a ring may fit him?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            11,
            31,
            39,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If snail can eat 26 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a ants eat?",
        "answer": 21,
        "options": [
            26,
            21,
            47,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If snail can eat 7 watermelon , how many watermelon can a cat eat?",
        "answer": 21,
        "options": [
            7,
            21,
            28,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 74. When the sun is at 71 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            16,
            107,
            95,
            92
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If dog can eat 12 apples , how many apples can a giraffee eat?",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            12,
            17,
            29,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If giraffee can eat 9 cake , how many cake can a snail eat?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            9,
            6,
            15,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Martinez wants to put a car in a road.The road is 8.627 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the car?",
        "answer": 5.59,
        "options": [
            5.6899999999999995,
            5.59,
            8.627,
            55.9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Thursday and returns to the bank 6333days later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "tuesday",
        "options": [
            "tuesday",
            "Monday",
            "Friday",
            "Monday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 20 years old in the year 1374.In his greatest win, he looted 420577844 of 3980479762 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1577,
            1431,
            1354,
            1598
        ],
        "answer": 1354
    },
    {
        "question": "Iraa wants to put a picture in a frame.The frame is 3.15 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the picture?",
        "answer": 1.65,
        "options": [
            3.15,
            1.75,
            16.5,
            1.65
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 sofa, 33 empty boxes, 13 bed, 2 bed bugs, and 15 fungi spots? How many of them are are tangible?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            123,
            182,
            23,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 22 ohms and 24 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 18 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            24,
            18,
            42,
            46,
            528
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of Mills increased from 579 per month to 872 per month while the salary of Jordan increased from 769 to 861 and of Sanders increased from 721 to 739 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Sanders",
        "options": [
            "Mills",
            "Jordan",
            "Sanders",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Brooks wants to put a car in a road.The road is 5.437 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the car?",
        "answer": 4.04,
        "options": [
            4.04,
            4.14,
            5.437,
            40.4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 12 years old in the year 1515.In his greatest win, he looted 197779199 of 7602609956 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1858,
            1503,
            1828,
            1603
        ],
        "answer": 1503
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 13 ohms and 19 ohms respectively connected in series. If the current at R1 is 9 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            9,
            19,
            13,
            32
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kyra wants to buy a pair of shoes. If his foot size is 6cm, what available pair of shoes may fit him?",
        "answer": 26,
        "options": [
            6,
            23,
            26,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international volley ball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 5 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            1,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Phillips wants to put a house in a street.The street is 6.668 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the house?",
        "answer": 1.43,
        "options": [
            1.43,
            14.299999999999999,
            1.53,
            6.668
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 couch, 43 table, 77 mat, 13 cockroaches, and 6 fungi spots? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            140,
            140,
            143,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international baseball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 7 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            16,
            0,
            2,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $7 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-tenth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 20.6 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            455,
            305,
            318,
            183.4
        ],
        "answer": 183.4
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 52000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 715000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            434,
            359,
            72727.273,
            907
        ],
        "answer": 72727.273
    },
    {
        "question": "Rose earns $5 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $1 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Rose was paid $4490, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            172,
            178,
            233,
            765
        ],
        "answer": 765
    },
    {
        "question": "Vivaan wants to put a car in a road.The road is 5.025 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the car?",
        "answer": 2.45,
        "options": [
            2.45,
            5.025,
            2.5500000000000003,
            24.5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 93. When the sun is at 58 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            98,
            20,
            101,
            110
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Romero wants to put a picture in a frame.The frame is 7.923 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the picture?",
        "answer": 3.84,
        "options": [
            7.923,
            3.84,
            3.94,
            38.4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Thomas wants to put a Card in a Envelope.The Envelope is 3.635 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Card?",
        "answer": 1.15,
        "options": [
            3.635,
            1.25,
            11.5,
            1.15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 2 flower vase, 85 table, 85 pair of shoes, 3 cat, and 9 crows? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            113,
            125,
            15,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 4 flower vase, 85 empty boxes, 30 mat, 9 crows, and 9 snail? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 119,
        "options": [
            89,
            120,
            119,
            39
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 90 miles in 7 hours and 50 minutes?",
        "options": [
            9.007649474854015,
            0.19148936170212766,
            6.566045300628595,
            9.383221892103176
        ],
        "answer": 0.19148936170212766
    },
    {
        "question": "Stewart wants to buy a pair of shorts. If his waist size is 17cm, what available pair of shorts may fit him?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            41,
            10,
            4,
            34
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Boxing game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            -1,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Miller earns $14 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $1 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Miller was paid $4194, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            183,
            354,
            286,
            118
        ],
        "answer": 286
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $2 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-third mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 45.6 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            135.8,
            170,
            274,
            308
        ],
        "answer": 135.8
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international squash game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            0,
            -1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 broom, 10 sofa, 90 tubelight, 9 cat, and 12 algae spots? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 115,
        "options": [
            99,
            25,
            115,
            116
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $7 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-sixth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 9.3 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            345,
            98,
            56.8,
            403
        ],
        "answer": 56.8
    },
    {
        "question": "Green wants to buy a pair of shoes. If his foot size is 32cm, what available pair of shoes may fit him?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            11,
            39,
            39,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 19 years old in the year 1308.In his greatest win, he looted 603538598 of 1360988150 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1474,
            1289,
            1747,
            1731
        ],
        "answer": 1289
    },
    {
        "question": "Romero wants to buy a pair of pants. If his waist size is 19cm, what available pair of pants may fit him?",
        "answer": 36,
        "options": [
            36,
            17,
            2,
            28
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 22. When the sun is at 99 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            23,
            3,
            28,
            96
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 23 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            15,
            -15,
            4,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 2000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 740000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            445,
            2702.703,
            65,
            661
        ],
        "answer": 2702.703
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Monday and returns to the bank 6years later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Sunday",
        "options": [
            "Sunday",
            "Thursday",
            "Monday",
            "Wednesday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Table-Tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            2,
            4,
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 39 ohms and 31 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 16 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 27,
        "options": [
            1209,
            70,
            43,
            31,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 12 sofa, 28 bed, 16 empty boxes, 7 trees, and 13 crows? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            30,
            60,
            16,
            32
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a child can eat 11 lemons , how many lemons can a giraffee eat?",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            11,
            12,
            23,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 6 ohms and 50 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 9 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            300,
            4,
            9,
            56,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mpm if you travel 22 miles in 6 hours and 34 minutes?",
        "options": [
            0.05583756345177665,
            6.103094443392106,
            5.224613775567492,
            9.728155210910739
        ],
        "answer": 0.05583756345177665
    },
    {
        "question": "Ferguson wants to buy a pair of pants. If his waist size is 30cm, what available pair of pants may fit him?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            39,
            30,
            31,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 broom, 10 sofa, 90 tubelight, 9 cat, and 12 algae spots? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 21,
        "options": [
            99,
            25,
            22,
            21
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 23 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            9,
            -9,
            4,
            5
        ],
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "Krishna began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fives. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 350,
        "options": [
            350,
            351,
            352,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A tank has a capacity of 55 gallons. How many gallons of water would it take to fill the tank to 1/9 of its capacity?",
        "options": [
            6.11,
            21,
            48,
            15
        ],
        "answer": 6.11
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -17,
            4,
            17,
            13
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 3 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            7,
            8,
            14,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 fan, 14 tubelight, 29 broom, 13 cat, and 14 pigeons? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            44,
            14,
            66
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 8 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            8,
            20,
            9,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Harris wants to put a chocolate in a jar.The jar is 7.541 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the chocolate?",
        "answer": 1.44,
        "options": [
            1.44,
            14.399999999999999,
            1.54,
            7.541
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $9 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-seventh mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 7.7 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            55.9,
            85,
            257,
            209
        ],
        "answer": 55.9
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 11 years old in the year 1243.In his greatest win, he looted 614708840 of 3166684963 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.How many coins were actually present in vatican city??",
        "options": [
            -2551976123,
            3166684963,
            3781393803,
            614708840
        ],
        "answer": 3166684963
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 23 ohms and 50 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 20 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            50,
            1150,
            49,
            73,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 4 flower vase, 85 empty boxes, 30 mat, 9 crows, and 9 snail? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            110,
            106,
            3,
            40
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Dunn wants to buy a Phone. If his Palm size is 7cm, what available Phone may fit him?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            20,
            11,
            20,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 4 feet by 3 feet?",
        "options": [
            2383,
            1733,
            4022,
            1728
        ],
        "answer": 1728
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 61000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 847000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            149,
            795,
            72018.89,
            942
        ],
        "answer": 72018.89
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 bed, 4 couch, 91 tubelight, 13 people, and 3 snail? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 110,
        "options": [
            110,
            19,
            104,
            111
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $66 to the charity and a total of $6876 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was tripled?",
        "options": [
            856,
            862,
            104,
            184
        ],
        "answer": 104
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 couch, 15 flower vase, 55 refrigerator, 2 trees, and 13 bed bugs? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            57,
            15,
            16,
            29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Boxing game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            1,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 6 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            7,
            -17,
            10,
            17
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 78000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 228000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            342.105,
            652,
            481,
            551
        ],
        "answer": 342.105
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 13 ohms and 19 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 9 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            32,
            9,
            19,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jones wants to put a book in a bag.The bag is 4.831 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the book?",
        "answer": 3.0,
        "options": [
            30.0,
            4.831,
            3.1,
            3.0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If snail can eat 52 grapes , how many grapes can a dog eat?",
        "answer": 131,
        "options": [
            52,
            131,
            183,
            79
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Wednesday and returns to the bank 2153days later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Sunday",
        "options": [
            "Monday",
            "Sunday",
            "Monday",
            "Thursday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international squash game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            0,
            2,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 72 miles in 5 hours and 23 minutes?",
        "options": [
            7.052081692223232,
            9.114820203953332,
            1.2477673833426217,
            0.356656346749226
        ],
        "answer": 0.356656346749226
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 39 ohms and 34 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the current at R1 is 6 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            6,
            73,
            0,
            1326,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Wood wants to buy a necklace. If his neck circumference is 23cm, what available necklace may fit him?",
        "answer": 34,
        "options": [
            34,
            27,
            32,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 65 miles in 5 hours and 52 minutes?",
        "options": [
            4.222536963023828,
            5.509376311945488,
            11.079545454545455,
            5.831773022214284
        ],
        "answer": 11.079545454545455
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in mph if you travel 90 miles in 10 hours and 8 minutes?",
        "options": [
            8.881578947368421,
            8.291389858637832,
            4.283156010293132,
            1.723806938097335
        ],
        "answer": 8.881578947368421
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 34000000 million bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 909000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            696,
            558,
            37.404,
            136
        ],
        "answer": 37.404
    },
    {
        "question": "Pierce began counting from 0. She skip-counted by tens. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 310,
        "options": [
            0,
            311,
            312,
            310
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 9 years old in the year 1447.In his greatest win, he looted 714664535 of 4224985971 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1490,
            1502,
            1624,
            1438
        ],
        "answer": 1438
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 tubelight, 69 pair of shoes, 71 couch, 15 human beings, and 5 crows? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            123,
            95,
            7,
            84
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 52. When the sun is at 109 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 25,
        "options": [
            88,
            73,
            25,
            58
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            20,
            -30,
            30,
            10
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 couch, 27 chair, 12 cycles, 10 plants, and 13 cockroaches? How many of them are non-living things?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            32,
            45,
            44,
            22
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If cow can eat 19 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a snail eat?",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            19,
            14,
            33,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 couch, 27 chair, 12 cycles, 10 plants, and 13 cockroaches? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            24,
            22,
            23,
            32
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            20,
            14,
            6,
            -20
        ],
        "answer": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 5 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -25,
            16,
            25,
            9
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "Evans wants to put a fruit in a basket.The basket is 5.316 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the fruit?",
        "answer": 2.7,
        "options": [
            2.8000000000000003,
            27.0,
            5.316,
            2.7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 empty boxes, 95 bed, 83 sofa, 4 pigeons, and 3 plants? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            8,
            7,
            87,
            109
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 20 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -30,
            11,
            30,
            19
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 6 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            7,
            -17,
            10,
            17
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 41000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 27000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            183,
            1518518.519,
            906,
            793
        ],
        "answer": 1518518.519
    },
    {
        "question": "If elephant can eat 16 chocolates , how many chocolates can a pigeon eat?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            16,
            7,
            23,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a tuesday and returns to the bank 5months later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Wednesday",
        "options": [
            "Wednesday",
            "Friday",
            "tuesday",
            "Friday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ford began counting from 0. She skip-counted by tens. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 320,
        "options": [
            320,
            322,
            0,
            321
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Aditya wants to buy a a ring. If his finger circumference is 10cm, what available a ring may fit him?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            33,
            17,
            43,
            39
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If dog can eat 10 cake , how many cake can a pigeon eat?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            10,
            2,
            12,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Badminton game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            3,
            1,
            0,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international squash game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            0,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kabir began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fives. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 255,
        "options": [
            256,
            0,
            257,
            255
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $8 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-fifth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 9.1 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            351,
            100,
            40.4,
            66
        ],
        "answer": 40.4
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 16 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            21,
            22,
            -22,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 22
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 4000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 131000000 million has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            523,
            190,
            45,
            30.534
        ],
        "answer": 30.534
    },
    {
        "question": "If cow can eat 38 grapes , how many grapes can a pigeon eat?",
        "answer": 86,
        "options": [
            38,
            86,
            124,
            48
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 sofa, 16 bed, 93 pair of shoes, 9 algae spots, and 10 dog? How many of them are not having life in them?",
        "answer": 114,
        "options": [
            115,
            114,
            102,
            21
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            15,
            -26,
            26,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international volley ball game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            6,
            8,
            5,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 3 bed, 59 flower vase, 12 refrigerator, 4 trees, and 14 human beings? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            11,
            51,
            37,
            22
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            4,
            28,
            24,
            -28
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 couch, 27 chair, 12 cycles, 10 plants, and 13 cockroaches? How many of them are move faster?",
        "answer": 21,
        "options": [
            23,
            41,
            50,
            21
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Ice Hockey game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 4 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            2,
            9,
            3,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            11,
            -29,
            29,
            18
        ],
        "answer": 29
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 28. When the sun is at 25 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 58,
        "options": [
            5,
            27,
            12,
            58
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 15 couch, 66 flower vase, 15 cycles, 14 cat, and 15 dog? How many of them are living things?",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            30,
            29,
            81,
            29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 27 ohms and 17 ohms respectively connected in series. If the voltage at R1 is 18 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            18,
            459,
            44,
            17,
            41
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If dog can eat 17 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a giraffee eat?",
        "answer": 27,
        "options": [
            17,
            27,
            44,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Advik wants to buy a pair of pants. If his waist size is 10cm, what available pair of pants may fit him?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            23,
            20,
            18,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 8 flower vase, 46 refrigerator, 87 couch, 2 snail, and 14 bed bugs? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            100,
            5,
            135
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Morgan wants to put a car in a car parking space.The car parking space is 3.344 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the car?",
        "answer": 1.68,
        "options": [
            1.78,
            16.8,
            3.344,
            1.68
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $5 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-third mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 6.8 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            22.4,
            353,
            259,
            146
        ],
        "answer": 22.4
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international squash game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 0,
        "options": [
            0,
            -1,
            0,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If giraffee can eat 16 chocolates , how many chocolates can a pigeon eat?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            16,
            6,
            22,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $6 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-eighth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 44.1 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            363,
            350.8,
            413,
            368
        ],
        "answer": 350.8
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international Table-Tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            2,
            0,
            3,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of Owens increased from 491 per month to 989 per month while the salary of Sanders increased from 590 to 665 and of Arjun increased from 417 to 978 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Arjun",
        "options": [
            "Owens",
            "Sanders",
            "Arjun",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Dunn wants to put a Pizza Box in a Refrigerator.The Refrigerator is 6.156 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Pizza Box?",
        "answer": 4.47,
        "options": [
            44.699999999999996,
            4.47,
            6.156,
            4.569999999999999
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 7 feet by 6 feet?",
        "options": [
            116,
            7619,
            6048,
            4181
        ],
        "answer": 6048
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 7 feet by 3 feet?",
        "options": [
            3111,
            3024,
            9175,
            6910
        ],
        "answer": 3024
    },
    {
        "question": "If elephant can eat 6 cake , how many cake can a a child eat?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            6,
            1,
            7,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $46 to the charity and a total of $9465 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was tripled?",
        "options": [
            481,
            600,
            732,
            205
        ],
        "answer": 205
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 empty boxes, 37 chair, 82 refrigerator, 8 cockroaches, and 5 dog? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 88,
        "options": [
            88,
            141,
            141,
            132
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If dog can eat 21 apples , how many apples can a snail eat?",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            21,
            14,
            35,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Murphy wants to buy a necklace. If his neck circumference is 31cm, what available necklace may fit him?",
        "answer": 33,
        "options": [
            33,
            21,
            11,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 6 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            3,
            -24,
            24,
            21
        ],
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "Myers wants to buy a hoodie. If his chest size is 14cm, what available hoodie may fit him?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            14,
            24,
            20,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Collins wants to buy a shirt. If his body size is 11cm, what available shirt may fit him?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            37,
            37,
            29,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Attendees at a charity dinner each gave at least $74 to the charity and a total of $6768 was collected. What is the maximum number of people who could have attended when the total amount collected was doubled?",
        "options": [
            575,
            91,
            752,
            999
        ],
        "answer": 91
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -30,
            13,
            17,
            30
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $10 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional one-sixth mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 14.5 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            91.0,
            309,
            396,
            257
        ],
        "answer": 91.0
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            20,
            14,
            6,
            -20
        ],
        "answer": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 11 empty boxes, 37 chair, 82 refrigerator, 8 cockroaches, and 5 dog? How many of them are having life in them ?",
        "answer": 13,
        "options": [
            13,
            14,
            90,
            48
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 14 empty boxes, 20 bed, 15 refrigerator, 8 dog, and 7 pigeons? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            63,
            55,
            62,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 13 flower vase, 95 mat, 40 empty boxes, 10 dog, and 14 cockroaches? How many of them are non-tangible?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            115,
            131,
            125
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Rodriguez wants to buy a hat. If his head circumference is 21cm, what available hat may fit him?",
        "answer": 36,
        "options": [
            36,
            15,
            2,
            28
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jimenez wants to buy a necklace. If his neck circumference is 35cm, what available necklace may fit him?",
        "answer": 36,
        "options": [
            23,
            3,
            23,
            36
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason deposits money at a bank on a Thursday and returns to the bank 7336days later to withdraw the money.On what day of the week did Jason withdraw the money from the bank?",
        "answer": "Thursday",
        "options": [
            "Monday",
            "Sunday",
            "Thursday",
            "Wednesday"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            20,
            14,
            6,
            -20
        ],
        "answer": 20
    },
    {
        "question": " Consider two resistances R1 and R2 of 15 ohms and 23 ohms respectively connected in parallel. If the voltage at R1 is 2 then the current/voltage at R2 can be ?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            23,
            15,
            2,
            38
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Shanaya began counting from 0. She skip-counted by fours. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 116,
        "options": [
            116,
            117,
            0,
            118
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If dog can eat 26 muskmelon , how many muskmelon can a cat eat?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            26,
            16,
            42,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If ants can eat 94 grapes , how many grapes can a cat eat?",
        "answer": 137,
        "options": [
            94,
            137,
            231,
            43
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": " Out of 6000000000 billion bacteria grown for an experiment, 1 in 330000 thousand has a particular mutation. Approximately how many of the bacteria have the mutation?",
        "options": [
            18181.818,
            418,
            175,
            404
        ],
        "answer": 18181.818
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            19,
            9,
            10,
            -19
        ],
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 10 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            21,
            -21,
            19,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 21
    },
    {
        "question": "Romero wants to put a picture in a frame.The frame is 8.129 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the picture?",
        "answer": 3.23,
        "options": [
            3.23,
            8.129,
            32.3,
            3.33
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Brooks earns $11 for each ticket that he sells, and a bonus of $1 per ticket for each ticket he sells over 100. If Brooks was paid $1461, how many tickets did he sell approximately?",
        "options": [
            130,
            101,
            399,
            119
        ],
        "answer": 130
    },
    {
        "question": "If a taxi charges $7 for the first mile, and $1.00 for each additional quarter mile, how much does the taxi charge for a 39.2 mile ride?",
        "options": [
            280,
            159.8,
            415,
            459
        ],
        "answer": 159.8
    },
    {
        "question": "Myers wants to buy a hat. If his head circumference is 6cm, what available hat may fit him?",
        "answer": 35,
        "options": [
            4,
            35,
            12,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If snail can eat 21 chocolates , how many chocolates can a ants eat?",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            21,
            15,
            36,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international cricket game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 11 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side A",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            19,
            5,
            0,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Aarav wants to put a house in a street.The street is 9.069 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the house?",
        "answer": 6.06,
        "options": [
            6.159999999999999,
            60.599999999999994,
            9.069,
            6.06
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If man can eat 11 lemons , how many lemons can a elephant eat?",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            11,
            17,
            28,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 13. When the sun is at 119 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            3,
            84,
            66,
            39
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Veer wants to put a Drawer in a Table.The Table is 9.681 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the Drawer?",
        "answer": 6.72,
        "options": [
            9.681,
            6.72,
            6.819999999999999,
            67.2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your average speed in kpm if you travel 28 miles in 5 hours and 20 minutes?",
        "options": [
            1.4325082327921757,
            0.14,
            6.1680422935961605,
            8.966450584005933
        ],
        "answer": 0.14
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 5 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            -25,
            16,
            25,
            9
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "The salary of Davis increased from 855 per month to 880 per month while the salary of Harrison increased from 505 to 798 and of Murray increased from 369 to 867 per month. What is the greatest increase in salary among these three?",
        "answer": "Murray",
        "options": [
            "Davis",
            "Harrison",
            "Murray",
            "none of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 7 years old in the year 1324.In his greatest win, he looted 169327656 of 4195264474 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1317,
            1783,
            1794,
            1661
        ],
        "answer": 1317
    },
    {
        "question": "Ritvik began counting from 0. She skip-counted by twos. Which of the possible numbers she could have encountered?",
        "answer": 200,
        "options": [
            0,
            200,
            201,
            202
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Baker wants to put a luggage in a car trunk.The car trunk is 3.632 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the luggage?",
        "answer": 1.81,
        "options": [
            18.1,
            3.632,
            1.81,
            1.9100000000000001
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many 1-inch square tiles would it take to cover the floor of a closet that has dimensions 8 feet by 7 feet?",
        "options": [
            8064,
            8524,
            7637,
            968
        ],
        "answer": 8064
    },
    {
        "question": "Brown wants to put a chocolate in a jar.The jar is 5.092 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the chocolate?",
        "answer": 3.68,
        "options": [
            3.68,
            5.092,
            3.7800000000000002,
            36.800000000000004
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Grant wants to put a book in a bag.The bag is 7.794 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the book?",
        "answer": 2.43,
        "options": [
            2.43,
            7.794,
            2.5300000000000002,
            24.3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a living room there are 5 mat, 10 table, 90 chair, 6 trees, and 4 fungi spots? How many of them are stationary for life time",
        "answer": 52,
        "options": [
            112,
            52,
            112,
            111
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 22 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            4,
            28,
            24,
            -28
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 12 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            20,
            -30,
            30,
            10
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "Howard wants to put a picture in a frame.The frame is 9.465 metres wide. What can be the minimum width of the picture?",
        "answer": 8.28,
        "options": [
            82.8,
            9.465,
            8.379999999999999,
            8.28
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 7 years old in the year 1324.In his greatest win, he looted 169327656 of 4195264474 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1317,
            1783,
            1794,
            1661
        ],
        "answer": 1317
    },
    {
        "question": "In an international tennis game, two teams A and B are playing against each other but unfortunately 1 players on the ground got injured. How many players can be there on the side B",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            0,
            1,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of a building is 53. When the sun is at 100 degrees to the building, what can be the size of the shadow casted by the building?",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            74,
            61,
            67,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "If a person uses a polish paper of thickness 6 over time. Its thickness can possibly increase/decrease by how much?",
        "options": [
            3,
            -24,
            24,
            21
        ],
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander was a great fighter and held a larger empire than any king born before or after him. He started learning new skills when he was 19 years old in the year 1308.In his greatest win, he looted 603538598 of 1360988150 and transferred them from vatican city to Jordan city.When did alexander {}??",
        "options": [
            1474,
            1289,
            1747,
            1731
        ],
        "answer": 1289
    }
]